<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf8'?>
<!DOCTYPE VOTABLE SYSTEM "http://cdsweb.u-strasbg.fr/xml/VOTable.dtd" >
<VOTABLE version="1.1">
<DESCRIPTION>
   Results generated from the NASA Astrophysics Data System: https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu
   For more information and support please contact ads@cfa.harvard.edu
</DESCRIPTION>
<RESOURCE type="results">
<TABLE>
<DESCRIPTION>
   ADS Search Results.
   Selected and retrieved 500 records.
</DESCRIPTION>
<FIELD ID="bibcode" datatype="char" arraysize="19">
<DESCRIPTION>The bibcode identifier for the record</DESCRIPTION>
</FIELD>
<FIELD ID="title" datatype="char" arraysize="*">
<DESCRIPTION>Title of the paper</DESCRIPTION>
</FIELD>
<FIELD ID="creator" datatype="char" arraysize="*">
<DESCRIPTION>List of authors</DESCRIPTION>
</FIELD>
<FIELD ID="source" datatype="char" arraysize="*">
<DESCRIPTION>Publication infromation</DESCRIPTION>
</FIELD>
<FIELD ID="date" datatype="char" arraysize="10">
<DESCRIPTION>Publication Date</DESCRIPTION>
</FIELD>
<FIELD ID="url" datatype="char" arraysize="*">
<DESCRIPTION>Resource URL</DESCRIPTION>
</FIELD>
<DATA>
<TABLEDATA>
<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...930L...4W</TD>
<TD>Discovery of ATLAS17jrp as an Optical-, X-Ray-, and Infrared-bright Tidal Disruption Event in a Star-forming Galaxy</TD>
<TD>Wang, Yibo; Jiang, Ning; Wang, Tinggui; Zhu, Jiazheng; Dou, Liming; Lin, Zheyu; Sun, Luming; Liu, Hui; Sheng, Zhenfeng</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 930, Issue 1, id.L4, 7 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...930L...4W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...930..143M</TD>
<TD>Long-term Evolution of a Supernova Remnant Hosting a Double Neutron Star Binary</TD>
<TD>Matsuoka, Tomoki; Lee, Shiu-Hang; Maeda, Keiichi; Takiwaki, Tomoya; Moriya, Takashi J.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 930, Issue 2, id.143, 17 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...930..143M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...930..127G</TD>
<TD>Evolution of a Peculiar Type Ibn Supernova SN 2019wep</TD>
<TD>Gangopadhyay, Anjasha; Misra, Kuntal; Hosseinzadeh, Griffin; Arcavi, Iair; Pellegrino, Craig; Wang, Xiaofeng; Andrew Howell, D.; Burke, Jamison; Zhang, Jujia; Kawabata, Koji; Singh, Mridweeka; Dastidar, Raya; Hiramatsu, Daichi; McCully, Curtis; Mo, Jun; Chen, Zhihao; Xiang, Danfeng</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 930, Issue 2, id.127, 15 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...930..127G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...930..119W</TD>
<TD>Wave-driven Outbursts and Variability of Low-mass Supernova Progenitors</TD>
<TD>Wu, Samantha C.; Fuller, Jim</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 930, Issue 2, id.119, 14 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...930..119W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...930..107M</TD>
<TD>Galactic Positrons from Thermonuclear Supernovae</TD>
<TD>Mera Evans, T. B.; Hoeflich, P.; Diehl, R.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 930, Issue 2, id.107, 12 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...930..107M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...930...53L</TD>
<TD>A Rapid and Large-amplitude X-Ray Dimming Event in a z ≈ 2.6 Radio-quiet Quasar</TD>
<TD>Liu, Hezhen; Luo, B.; Brandt, W. N.; Huang, Jian; Pu, Xingting; Yi, Weimin; Yu, Li-Ming</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 930, Issue 1, id.53, 13 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...930...53L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...930...34T</TD>
<TD>SN 2020jfo: A Short-plateau Type II Supernova from a Low-mass Progenitor</TD>
<TD>Teja, Rishabh Singh; Singh, Avinash; Sahu, D. K.; Anupama, G. C.; Kumar, Brajesh; A. J., Nayana</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 930, Issue 1, id.34, 19 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...930...34T</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...930...31B</TD>
<TD>Characterization of Supernovae Based on the Spectral-Temporal Energy Distribution: Two Possible SN Ib Subtypes</TD>
<TD>Bengyat, Ofek; Gal-Yam, Avishay</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 930, Issue 1, id.31, 11 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...930...31B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...930...12H</TD>
<TD>The Curious Case of ASASSN-20hx: A Slowly Evolving, UV- and X-Ray-Luminous, Ambiguous Nuclear Transient</TD>
<TD>Hinkle, Jason T.; Holoien, Thomas W. -S.; Shappee, Benjamin. J.; Neustadt, Jack M. M.; Auchettl, Katie; Vallely, Patrick J.; Shahbandeh, Melissa; Kluge, Matthias; Kochanek, Christopher S.; Stanek, K. Z.; Huber, Mark E.; Post, Richard S.; Bersier, David; Ashall, Christopher; Tucker, Michael A.; Williams, Jonathan P.; de Jaeger, Thomas; Do, Aaron; Fausnaugh, Michael; Gruen, Daniel; Hopp, Ulrich; Myles, Justin; Obermeier, Christian; Payne, Anna V.; Thompson, Todd A.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 930, Issue 1, id.12, 24 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...930...12H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...930....9M</TD>
<TD>The Donor of the Black Hole X-Ray Binary MAXI J1820+070</TD>
<TD>Mikołajewska, Joanna; Zdziarski, Andrzej A.; Ziółkowski, Janusz; Torres, Manuel A. P.; Casares, Jorge</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 930, Issue 1, id.9, 8 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...930....9M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022AJ....163..239N</TD>
<TD>Zwicky Transient Facility and Globular Clusters: The RR Lyrae gri-band Period-Luminosity-Metallicity and Period-Wesenheit-Metallicity Relations</TD>
<TD>Ngeow, Chow-Choong; Bhardwaj, Anupam; Dekany, Richard; Duev, Dmitry A.; Graham, Matthew J.; Groom, Steven L.; Mahabal, Ashish A.; Masci, Frank J.; Medford, Michael S.; Riddle, Reed</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 163, Issue 5, id.239, 22 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022AJ....163..239N</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022AJ....163..221J</TD>
<TD>Optical Characterization of Two Cataclysmic Variables: RBS 0490 and SDSS J075939.79+191417.3</TD>
<TD>Joshi, Arti; Pandey, J. C.; Rawat, Nikita; Raj, Ashish; Wang, Wei; Singh, H. P.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 163, Issue 5, id.221, 11 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022AJ....163..221J</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022AJ....163..216B</TD>
<TD>Limits on the Detection of Planet Nine in the Dark Energy Survey</TD>
<TD>Belyakov, Matthew; Bernardinelli, Pedro H.; Brown, Michael E.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 163, Issue 5, id.216, 6 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022AJ....163..216B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022AJ....163..209S</TD>
<TD>HEALPix Alchemy: Fast All-Sky Geometry and Image Arithmetic in a Relational Database for Multimessenger Astronomy Brokers</TD>
<TD>Singer, Leo P.; Parazin, B.; Coughlin, Michael W.; Bloom, Joshua S.; Crellin-Quick, Arien; Goldstein, Daniel A.; van der Walt, Stéfan</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 163, Issue 5, id.209, 13 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022AJ....163..209S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...661A.124M</TD>
<TD>THA 15−31: Discovery with VLT/X-shooter and Swift/UVOT of a new symbiotic star of the accreting-only variety</TD>
<TD>Munari, U.; Alcalá, J. M.; Frasca, A.; Masetti, N.; Traven, G.; Akras, S.; Zampieri, L.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 661, id.A124, 12 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...661A.124M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...661A.113G</TD>
<TD>Radial velocity variability and the evolution of hot subdwarf stars</TD>
<TD>Geier, S.; Dorsch, M.; Pelisoli, I.; Reindl, N.; Heber, U.; Irrgang, A.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 661, id.A113, 15 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...661A.113G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...661A..42S</TD>
<TD>Identification of SRGt 062340.2-265751 as a bright, strongly variable, novalike cataclysmic variable</TD>
<TD>Schwope, Axel; Buckley, David A. H.; Kawka, Adela; König, Ole; Lutovinov, Alexander; Maitra, Chandreyee; Mereminskiy, Ilya; Miller-Jones, James; Pichardo Marcano, Manuel; Rau, Arne; Semena, Andrei; Townsend, Lee J.; Wilms, Jörn</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 661, id.A42, 9 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...661A..42S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...661A..39Z</TD>
<TD>Identification of three cataclysmic variables detected by the ART-XC and eROSITA telescopes on board the SRG during the all-sky X-ray survey</TD>
<TD>Zaznobin, I.; Sazonov, S.; Burenin, R.; Uskov, G.; Semena, A.; Gilfanov, M.; Medvedev, P.; Sunyaev, R.; Eselevich, M.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 661, id.A39, 9 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...661A..39Z</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...661A..32M</TD>
<TD>Peculiar X-ray transient SRGA J043520.9+552226/AT2019wey discovered with SRG/ART-XC</TD>
<TD>Mereminskiy, I. A.; Dodin, A. V.; Lutovinov, A. A.; Semena, A. N.; Arefiev, V. A.; Atapin, K. E.; Belinski, A. A.; Burenin, R. A.; Burlak, M. V.; Eselevich, M. V.; Fedotieva, A. A.; Gilfanov, M. R.; Ikonnikova, N. P.; Krivonos, R. A.; Lapshov, I. Yu.; Lyapin, A. R.; Medvedev, P. S.; Molkov, S. V.; Postnov, K. A.; Pshirkov, M. S.; Sazonov, S. Yu.; Shakura, N. I.; Shtykovsky, A. E.; Sunyaev, R. A.; Tatarnikov, A. M.; Tkachenko, A. Yu.; Zheltoukhov, S. G.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 661, id.A32, 9 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...661A..32M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...661A..28L</TD>
<TD>SRG/ART-XC discovery of SRGA J204318.2+443815: Towards the complete population of faint X-ray pulsars</TD>
<TD>Lutovinov, A. A.; Tsygankov, S. S.; Mereminskiy, I. A.; Molkov, S. V.; Semena, A. N.; Arefiev, V. A.; Bikmaev, I. F.; Djupvik, A. A.; Gilfanov, M. R.; Karasev, D. I.; Lapshov, I. Yu.; Medvedev, P. S.; Shtykovsky, A. E.; Sunyaev, R. A.; Tkachenko, A. Yu.; Anand, S.; Ashley, M. C. B.; De, K.; Kasliwal, M. M.; Kulkarni, S. R.; van Roestel, J.; Yao, Y.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 661, id.A28, 9 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...661A..28L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022PhRvD.105h3004S</TD>
<TD>Linking the rates of neutron star binaries and short gamma-ray bursts</TD>
<TD>Sarin, Nikhil; Lasky, Paul D.; Vivanco, Francisco Hernandez; Stevenson, Simon P.; Chattopadhyay, Debatri; Smith, Rory; Thrane, Eric</TD>
<TD>Physical Review D, Volume 105, Issue 8, article id.083004</TD>
<TD>2022-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022PhRvD.105h3004S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022PASP..134d5002C</TD>
<TD>Wayne State University's Dan Zowada Memorial Observatory: Characterization and Pipeline of a 0.5 m Robotic Telescope</TD>
<TD>Carr, Robert; Cinabro, David; Cackett, Edward; Moutard, David; Carroll, Russell</TD>
<TD>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 134, Issue 1034, id.045002, 9 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022PASP..134d5002C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022NatAs...6..428L</TD>
<TD>The case for space environmentalism</TD>
<TD>Lawrence, Andy; Rawls, Meredith L.; Jah, Moriba; Boley, Aaron; Di Vruno, Federico; Garrington, Simon; Kramer, Michael; Lawler, Samantha; Lowenthal, James; McDowell, Jonathan; McCaughrean, Mark</TD>
<TD>Nature Astronomy, Volume 6, p. 428-435</TD>
<TD>2022-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022NatAs...6..428L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.511.5948P</TD>
<TD>Post maximum light and late time optical imaging polarimetry of type I superluminous supernova 2020znr</TD>
<TD>Poidevin, F.; Omand, C. M. B.; Pérez-Fournon, I.; Clavero, R.; Shirley, R.; Marques-Chaves, R.; Jimenez Angel, C.; Geier, S.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 511, Issue 4, pp.5948-5963</TD>
<TD>2022-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.511.5948P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.511.5936K</TD>
<TD>Observationally driven Galactic double white dwarf population for LISA</TD>
<TD>Korol, Valeriya; Hallakoun, Na'ama; Toonen, Silvia; Karnesis, Nikolaos</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 511, Issue 4, pp.5936-5947</TD>
<TD>2022-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.511.5936K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.511.5823R</TD>
<TD>Multiwavelength radiation models for low-luminosity GRBs and the implications for UHECRs</TD>
<TD>Rudolph, A.; Bošnjak, Ž.; Palladino, A.; Sadeh, I.; Winter, W.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 511, Issue 4, pp.5823-5842</TD>
<TD>2022-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.511.5823R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.511.5328G</TD>
<TD>AT2019azh: an unusually long-lived, radio-bright thermal tidal disruption event</TD>
<TD>Goodwin, A. J.; van Velzen, S.; Miller-Jones, J. C. A.; Mummery, A.; Bietenholz, M. F.; Wederfoort, A.; Hammerstein, E.; Bonnerot, C.; Hoffmann, J.; Yan, L.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 511, Issue 4, pp.5328-5345</TD>
<TD>2022-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.511.5328G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.511.5251N</TD>
<TD>Sensitive Chandra coverage of a representative sample of weak-line quasars: revealing the full range of X-ray properties</TD>
<TD>Ni, Q.; Brandt, W. N.; Luo, B.; Garmire, G. P.; Hall, P. B.; Plotkin, R. M.; Shemmer, O.; Timlin, J. D.; Vito, F.; Wu, J.; Yi, W.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 511, Issue 4, pp.5251-5264</TD>
<TD>2022-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.511.5251N</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.511.5085M</TD>
<TD>What powers the radio emission in TDE AT2019dsg: A long-lived jet or the disruption itself?</TD>
<TD>Matsumoto, Tatsuya; Piran, Tsvi; Krolik, Julian H.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 511, Issue 4, pp.5085-5092</TD>
<TD>2022-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.511.5085M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.511.4971M</TD>
<TD>Identifying blue large amplitude pulsators from Gaia DR2 and ZTF DR3</TD>
<TD>McWhirter, Paul Ross; Lam, Marco C.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 511, Issue 4, pp.4971-4980</TD>
<TD>2022-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.511.4971M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.511.4417V</TD>
<TD>Simulating time-varying strong lenses</TD>
<TD>Vernardos, G.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 511, Issue 3, pp.4417-4429</TD>
<TD>2022-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.511.4417V</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.511.3881F</TD>
<TD>Enhancement of double-close-binary quadruples</TD>
<TD>Fezenko, Gavin B.; Hwang, Hsiang-Chih; Zakamska, Nadia L.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 511, Issue 3, pp.3881-3894</TD>
<TD>2022-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.511.3881F</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.511.3408D</TD>
<TD>An analytical, fully relativistic framework for tidal disruption event streams in Schwarzschild geometry</TD>
<TD>Dittmann, Alexander J.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 511, Issue 3, pp.3408-3419</TD>
<TD>2022-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.511.3408D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.511.3034V</TD>
<TD>The role of plasma instabilities in relativistic radiation-mediated shocks: stability analysis and particle-in-cell simulations</TD>
<TD>Vanthieghem, A.; Mahlmann, J. F.; Levinson, A.; Philippov, A.; Nakar, E.; Fiuza, F.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 511, Issue 2, pp.3034-3045</TD>
<TD>2022-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.511.3034V</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.511.3005J</TD>
<TD>Accretion disc sizes from continuum reverberation mapping of AGN selected from the ZTF survey</TD>
<TD>Jha, Vivek Kumar; Joshi, Ravi; Chand, Hum; Wu, Xue-Bing; Ho, Luis C.; Rastogi, Shantanu; Ma, Qinchun</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 511, Issue 2, pp.3005-3016</TD>
<TD>2022-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.511.3005J</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.511.2885B</TD>
<TD>Tidal disruption events in post-starburst galaxies: the importance of a complete stellar mass function</TD>
<TD>Bortolas, Elisa</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 511, Issue 2, pp.2885-2896</TD>
<TD>2022-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.511.2885B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.511.2782C</TD>
<TD>Mapping the cosmic expansion history from LIGO-Virgo-KAGRA in synergy with DESI and SPHEREx</TD>
<TD>Cigarrán Díaz, Cristina; Mukherjee, Suvodip</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 511, Issue 2, pp.2782-2795</TD>
<TD>2022-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.511.2782C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.511.2708S</TD>
<TD>SN 2020kyg and the rates of faint Iax supernovae from ATLAS</TD>
<TD>Srivastav, Shubham; Smartt, S. J.; Huber, M. E.; Chambers, K. C.; Angus, C. R.; Chen, T. -W.; Callan, F. P.; Gillanders, J. H.; McBrien, O. R.; Sim, S. A.; Fulton, M.; Hjorth, J.; Smith, K. W.; Young, D. R.; Auchettl, K.; Anderson, J. P.; Pignata, G.; de Boer, T. J. L.; Lin, C. -C.; Magnier, E. A.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 511, Issue 2, pp.2708-2731</TD>
<TD>2022-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.511.2708S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.511.2405S</TD>
<TD>The Gravitational-wave Optical Transient Observer (GOTO): prototype performance and prospects for transient science</TD>
<TD>Steeghs, D.; Galloway, D. K.; Ackley, K.; Dyer, M. J.; Lyman, J.; Ulaczyk, K.; Cutter, R.; Mong, Y. -L.; Dhillon, V.; O'Brien, P.; Ramsay, G.; Poshyachinda, S.; Kotak, R.; Nuttall, L. K.; Pallé, E.; Breton, R. P.; Pollacco, D.; Thrane, E.; Aukkaravittayapun, S.; Awiphan, S.; Burhanudin, U.; Chote, P.; Chrimes, A.; Daw, E.; Duffy, C.; Eyles-Ferris, R.; Gompertz, B.; Heikkilä, T.; Irawati, P.; Kennedy, M. R.; Killestein, T.; Kuncarayakti, H.; Levan, A. J.; Littlefair, S.; Makrygianni, L.; Marsh, T.; Mata-Sanchez, D.; Mattila, S.; Maund, J.; McCormac, J.; Mkrtichian, D.; Mullaney, J.; Noysena, K.; Patel, M.; Rol, E.; Sawangwit, U.; Stanway, E. R.; Starling, R.; Strøm, P.; Tooke, S.; West, R.; White, D. J.; Wiersema, K.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 511, Issue 2, pp.2405-2422</TD>
<TD>2022-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.511.2405S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.511.2201S</TD>
<TD>Filling the gap between synchronized and non-synchronized sdBs in short-period sdBV+dM binaries with TESS: TIC 137608661, a new system with a well-defined rotational splitting</TD>
<TD>Silvotti, Roberto; Németh, Péter; Telting, John H.; Baran, Andrzej S.; Østensen, Roy H.; Ostrowski, Jakub; Sahoo, Sumanta K.; Prins, Saskia</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 511, Issue 2, pp.2201-2217</TD>
<TD>2022-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.511.2201S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.511.1992L</TD>
<TD>AGN light echoes and the accretion disc self-gravity limit</TD>
<TD>Lobban, Andrew; King, Andrew</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 511, Issue 2, pp.1992-1998</TD>
<TD>2022-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.511.1992L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.511.1647F</TD>
<TD>Relentless and complex transits from a planetesimal debris disc</TD>
<TD>Farihi, J.; Hermes, J. J.; Marsh, T. R.; Mustill, A. J.; Wyatt, M. C.; Guidry, J. A.; Wilson, T. G.; Redfield, S.; Izquierdo, P.; Toloza, O.; Gänsicke, B. T.; Aungwerojwit, A.; Kaewmanee, C.; Dhillon, V. S.; Swan, A.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 511, Issue 2, pp.1647-1666</TD>
<TD>2022-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.511.1647F</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022KosNT..28a...3V</TD>
<TD>Machine learning technique for morphological classification of galaxies from SDSS. II. The image-based morphological catalogs of galaxies at 0.02&lt;z&lt;0.1</TD>
<TD>Vavilova, I. B.; Khramtsov, V.; Dobrycheva, D. V.; Vasylenko, M. Yu.; Elyiv, A. A.; Melnyk, O. V.</TD>
<TD>Space Science &amp;amp; Technology, Vol. 28, No. 1, pp.03-22 (2022)</TD>
<TD>2022-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022KosNT..28a...3V</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022JETP..134..399A</TD>
<TD>Deep-Underwater Cherenkov Detector in Lake Baikal</TD>
<TD>Avrorin, A. V.; Avrorin, A. D.; Ayinutdinov, V. M.; Allakhverdyan, V. A.; Banash, P.; Bardachova, Z.; Belolaptikov, I. A.; Borina, I. V.; Brudanin, V. B.; Budnev, N. M.; Gafarov, A. R.; Golubkov, K. V.; Gorshkov, N. S.; Gres', T. I.; Dwornitski, R.; Dzhilkibaev, Zh. -A. M.; Dik, V. Ya.; Domogatskii, G. V.; Doroshenko, A. A.; Dyachok, A. N.; Elzhov, T. V.; Zaborov, D. N.; Katulin, M. S.; Kebkal, K. G.; Kebkal, O. G.; Kozhin, V. A.; Kolbin, M. M.; Konishchev, K. V.; Kopanski, K. A.; Korobchenko, A. V.; Koshechkin, A. P.; Kruglov, M. V.; Kryukov, M. K.; Kulepov, V. F.; Maletski, P.; Malyshkin, Yu. M.; Milenin, M. B.; Mirgazov, R. R.; Nazari, V.; Naumov, D. V.; Noga, V.; Petukhov, D. P.; Pliskovskii, E. N.; Rozanov, M. I.; Rushay, V. D.; Ryabov, E. V.; Safronov, G. B.; Sirenko, A. E.; Skurikhin, A. V.; Solovjev, A. G.; Sorokovikov, M. N.; Stromakov, A. P.; Suvorova, O. V.; Sushenok, E. O.; Tabolenko, V. A.; Tarashchanskii, B. A.; Fait, L.; Fialkovskii, S. V.; Khramov, E. V.; Shaibonov, B. A.; Shelepov, M. D.; Šimkovic, F.; Stekl, I.; Etskerova, E.; Yablokova, Yu. V.; Yakovlev, S. A.</TD>
<TD>Journal of Experimental and Theoretical Physics, Volume 134, Issue 4, p.399-416</TD>
<TD>2022-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022JETP..134..399A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022IJMPD..3130008A</TD>
<TD>The SVOM mission</TD>
<TD>Atteia, J. -L.; Cordier, B.; Wei, J.</TD>
<TD>International Journal of Modern Physics D, Volume 31, Issue 5, id. 2230008</TD>
<TD>2022-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022IJMPD..3130008A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022EPJC...82..280S</TD>
<TD>Generalised Ellis-Bronnikov wormholes in f(R) gravity</TD>
<TD>Sokoliuk, Oleksii; Mandal, Sanjay; Sahoo, P. K.; Baransky, Alexander</TD>
<TD>The European Physical Journal C, Volume 82, Issue 4, article id.280</TD>
<TD>2022-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022EPJC...82..280S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022CoSka..52a..64S</TD>
<TD>Editorial</TD>
<TD>Skopal, A.; Komžík, R.</TD>
<TD>Contributions of the Astronomical Observatory Skalnaté Pleso, vol. 52, no. 1, p. 64-64.</TD>
<TD>2022-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022CoSka..52a..64S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJS..259...53C</TD>
<TD>The First Data Release of CNIa0.02-A Complete Nearby (Redshift &lt;0.02) Sample of Type Ia Supernova Light Curves</TD>
<TD>Chen, Ping; Dong, Subo; Kochanek, C. S.; Stanek, K. Z.; Post, R. S.; Stritzinger, M. D.; Prieto, J. L.; Filippenko, Alexei V.; Kollmeier, Juna A.; Elias-Rosa, N.; Katz, Boaz; Tomasella, Lina; Bose, S.; Ashall, Chris; Benetti, S.; Bersier, D.; Brimacombe, Joseph; Brink, Thomas G.; Brown, P.; Buckley, David A. H.; Cappellaro, Enrico; Christie, Grant W.; Fraser, Morgan; Gromadzki, Mariusz; Holoien, Thomas W. -S.; Hu, Shaoming; Kankare, Erkki; Koff, Robert; Lundqvist, P.; Mattila, S.; Milne, P. A.; Morrell, Nidia; Muñoz, J. A.; Mutel, Robert; Natusch, Tim; Nicolas, Joel; Pastorello, A.; Prentice, Simon; Roth, Tyler; Shappee, B. J.; Stone, Geoffrey; Thompson, Todd A.; Villanueva, Steven; Zheng, WeiKang</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 259, Issue 2, id.53, 27 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJS..259...53C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...929..184S</TD>
<TD>The Nascent Milliquasar VT J154843.06+220812.6: Tidal Disruption Event or Extreme Accretion State Change?</TD>
<TD>Somalwar, Jean J.; Ravi, Vikram; Dong, Dillon; Graham, Matthew; Hallinan, Gregg; Law, Casey; Lu, Wenbin; Myers, Steven T.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 929, Issue 2, id.184, 24 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...929..184S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...929..163P</TD>
<TD>Is the High-energy Neutrino Event IceCube-200530A Associated with a Hydrogen-rich Superluminous Supernova?</TD>
<TD>Pitik, Tetyana; Tamborra, Irene; Angus, Charlotte R.; Auchettl, Katie</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 929, Issue 2, id.163, 13 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...929..163P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...929..133J</TD>
<TD>Effects of an Immortal Stellar Population in AGN Disks</TD>
<TD>Jermyn, Adam S.; Dittmann, Alexander J.; McKernan, B.; Ford, K. E. S.; Cantiello, Matteo</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 929, Issue 2, id.133, 9 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...929..133J</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...929..129G</TD>
<TD>EXORCISM: A Spectroscopic Survey of Young Eruptive Variables (EXor and Candidates)</TD>
<TD>Giannini, T.; Giunta, A.; Gangi, M.; Carini, R.; Lorenzetti, D.; Antoniucci, S.; Caratti o Garatti, A.; Cassará, L.; Nisini, B.; Rossi, A.; Testa, V.; Vitali, F.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 929, Issue 2, id.129, 28 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...929..129G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...929..108G</TD>
<TD>MALS SALT-NOT Survey of MIR-selected Powerful Radio-bright AGN at 0 &lt; z &lt; 3.5</TD>
<TD>Gupta, N.; Shukla, G.; Srianand, R.; Krogager, J. -K.; Noterdaeme, P.; Baker, A. J.; Combes, F.; Fynbo, J. P. U.; Momjian, E.; Hilton, M.; Hussain, T.; Moodley, K.; Petitjean, P.; Chen, H. -W.; Deka, P.; Dutta, R.; Jose, J.; Józsa, G. I. G.; Kaski, C.; Klöckner, H. -R.; Knowles, K.; Sikhosana, S.; Wagenveld, J.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 929, Issue 1, id.108, 41 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...929..108G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...929...19G</TD>
<TD>Accretion Disk Size Measurements of Active Galactic Nuclei Monitored by the Zwicky Transient Facility</TD>
<TD>Guo, Wei-Jian; Li, Yan-Rong; Zhang, Zhi-Xiang; Ho, Luis C.; Wang, Jian-Min</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 929, Issue 1, id.19, 17 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...929...19G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...929...16G</TD>
<TD>Modeling the GRB 170202A Fireball from Continuous Observations with the Zadko and the Virgin Island Robotic Telescopes</TD>
<TD>Gendre, B.; Orange, N. B.; Moore, E.; Klotz, A.; Coward, D. M.; Giblin, T.; Gokuldass, P.; Morris, D.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 929, Issue 1, id.16, 10 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...929...16G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...928..158B</TD>
<TD>Hubble Space Telescope Imaging of Luminous Extragalactic Infrared Transients and Variables from the Spitzer Infrared Intensive Transients Survey</TD>
<TD>Bond, Howard E.; Jencson, Jacob E.; Whitelock, Patricia A.; Adams, Scott M.; Bally, John; Cody, Ann Marie; Gehrz, Robert D.; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Masci, Frank J.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 928, Issue 2, id.158, 24 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...928..158B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...928..139Z</TD>
<TD>Dependence of Pulsation Mode of Cepheids on Metallicity</TD>
<TD>Zhang, Zehao; Jiang, Biwei; Ren, Yi; Chen, Xiaodian; Wang, Shu</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 928, Issue 2, id.139, 7 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...928..139Z</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...928..122M</TD>
<TD>Optical to X-Ray Signatures of Dense Circumstellar Interaction in Core-collapse Supernovae</TD>
<TD>Margalit, Ben; Quataert, Eliot; Ho, Anna Y. Q.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 928, Issue 2, id.122, 26 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...928..122M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...660A.138S</TD>
<TD>PGIR 20eid (SN 2020qmp): A Type IIP Supernova at 15.6 Mpc discovered by the Palomar Gattini-IR survey</TD>
<TD>Srinivasaragavan, G. P.; Sfaradi, I.; Jencson, J.; De, K.; Horesh, A.; Kasliwal, M. M.; Tinyanont, S.; Hankins, M.; Schulze, S.; Ashley, M. C. B.; Graham, M. J.; Karambelkar, V.; Lau, R.; Mahabal, A. A.; Moore, A. M.; Ofek, E. O.; Sharma, Y.; Sollerman, J.; Soon, J.; Soria, R.; Travouillon, T.; Walters, R.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 660, id.A138, 14 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...660A.138S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...660A.119Z</TD>
<TD>Discovery of late-time X-ray flare and anomalous emission line enhancement after the nuclear optical outburst in a narrow-line Seyfert 1 Galaxy</TD>
<TD>Zhang, W. J.; Shu, X. W.; Sheng, Z. F.; Sun, L. M.; Dou, L. M.; Jiang, N.; Wang, J. G.; Hu, X. Y.; Wang, Y. B.; Wang, T. G.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 660, id.A119, 16 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...660A.119Z</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...660A..72B</TD>
<TD>WD 1145+017: Alternative models of the atmosphere, dust clouds, and gas rings</TD>
<TD>Budaj, J.; Maliuk, A.; Hubeny, I.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 660, id.A72, 14 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...660A..72B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022Symm...14..518B</TD>
<TD>Neutron Stars with Baryon Number Violation, Probing Dark Sectors</TD>
<TD>Berryman, Jeffrey M.; Gardner, Susan; Zakeri, Mohammadreza</TD>
<TD>Symmetry, vol. 14, issue 3, p. 518</TD>
<TD>2022-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022Symm...14..518B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022RAA....22c5024X</TD>
<TD>V0644 Ser: An Active Ultrashort Period Contact Binary Star</TD>
<TD>Xu, Hu-Shan; Zhu, Li-Ying; Thawicharat, Sarotsakulchai; Boonrucksar, Soonthornthum</TD>
<TD>Research in Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 22, Issue 3, id.035024, 11 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022RAA....22c5024X</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022RAA....22c5022D</TD>
<TD>Physical Properties of 29 sdB+dM Eclipsing Binaries in Zwicky Transient Facility</TD>
<TD>Dai, Min; Chen, Xiao-Dian; Wang, Kun; Luo, Yang-Ping; Wang, Shu; Deng, Li-Cai</TD>
<TD>Research in Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 22, Issue 3, id.035022, 25 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022RAA....22c5022D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022RAA....22c5021Y</TD>
<TD>New Massive Contact Twin Binary in a Radio-quiet H II Region Associated with the M17 Complex</TD>
<TD>Yin, Jia; Chen, Zhiwei; Yao, Yongqiang; Chen, Jian; Li, Bin; Jiang, Zhibo</TD>
<TD>Research in Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 22, Issue 3, id.035021, 16 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022RAA....22c5021Y</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022PSJ.....3...71H</TD>
<TD>The Population of Interstellar Objects Detectable with the LSST and Accessible for In Situ Rendezvous with Various Mission Designs</TD>
<TD>Hoover, Devin J.; Seligman, Darryl Z.; Payne, Matthew J.</TD>
<TD>The Planetary Science Journal, Volume 3, Issue 3, id.71, 12 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022PSJ.....3...71H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022PASP..134c5003L</TD>
<TD>Low-cost Access to the Deep, High-cadence Sky: the Argus Optical Array</TD>
<TD>Law, Nicholas M.; Corbett, Hank; Galliher, Nathan W.; Gonzalez, Ramses; Vasquez, Alan; Walters, Glenn; Machia, Lawrence; Ratzloff, Jeff; Ackley, Kendall; Bizon, Chris; Clemens, Christopher; Cox, Steven; Eikenberry, Steven; Howard, Ward S.; Glazier, Amy; Mann, Andrew W.; Quimby, Robert; Reichart, Daniel; Trilling, David</TD>
<TD>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 134, Issue 1033, id.035003, 15 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022PASP..134c5003L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.511L..66W</TD>
<TD>Discovery of hot subdwarfs covered with helium-burning ash</TD>
<TD>Werner, Klaus; Reindl, Nicole; Geier, Stephan; Pritzkuleit, Max</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 511, Issue 1, pp.L66-L71</TD>
<TD>2022-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.511L..66W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.511.1210D</TD>
<TD>Out of one, many: distinguishing time delays from lensed supernovae</TD>
<TD>Denissenya, Mikhail; Bag, Satadru; Kim, Alex G.; Linder, Eric V.; Shafieloo, Arman</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 511, Issue 1, pp.1210-1217</TD>
<TD>2022-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.511.1210D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.511..241G</TD>
<TD>Supernova siblings and their parent galaxies in the Zwicky Transient Facility Bright Transient Survey</TD>
<TD>Graham, Melissa L.; Fremling, Christoffer; Perley, Daniel A.; Biswas, Rahul; Phillips, Christopher A.; Sollerman, Jesper; Nugent, Peter E.; Nance, Sarafina; Dhawan, Suhail; Nordin, Jakob; Goobar, Ariel; Miller, Adam; Neill, James D.; Hall, Xander J.; Hankins, Matthew J.; Duev, Dmitry A.; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Rigault, Mickael; Bellm, Eric C.; Hale, David; Mróz, Przemek; Kulkarni, S. R.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 511, Issue 1, pp.241-254</TD>
<TD>2022-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.511..241G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.511...83G</TD>
<TD>TOI-530b: a giant planet transiting an M-dwarf detected by TESS</TD>
<TD>Gan, Tianjun; Lin, Zitao; Wang, Sharon Xuesong; Mao, Shude; Fouqué, Pascal; Fan, Jiahao; Bedell, Megan; Stassun, Keivan G.; Giacalone, Steven; Fukui, Akihiko; Murgas, Felipe; Ciardi, David R.; Howell, Steve B.; Collins, Karen A.; Shporer, Avi; Arnold, Luc; Barclay, Thomas; Charbonneau, David; Christiansen, Jessie; Crossfield, Ian J. M.; Dressing, Courtney D.; Elliott, Ashley; Esparza-Borges, Emma; Evans, Phil; Gnilka, Crystal L.; Gonzales, Erica J.; Howard, Andrew W.; Isogai, Keisuke; Kawauchi, Kiyoe; Kurita, Seiya; Liu, Beibei; Livingston, John H.; Matson, Rachel A.; Narita, Norio; Palle, Enric; Parviainen, Hannu; Rackham, Benjamin V.; Rodriguez, David R.; Rose, Mark; Rudat, Alexander; Schlieder, Joshua E.; Scott, Nicholas J.; Vezie, Michael; Ricker, George R.; Vanderspek, Roland; Latham, David W.; Seager, Sara; Winn, Joshua N.; Jenkins, Jon M.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 511, Issue 1, pp.83-99</TD>
<TD>2022-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.511...83G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.511...54H</TD>
<TD>SkyMapper colours of Seyfert galaxies and changing-look AGN - II. Newly discovered changing-look AGN</TD>
<TD>Hon, Wei Jeat; Wolf, Christian; Onken, Christopher A.; Webster, Rachel; Auchettl, Katie</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 511, Issue 1, pp.54-70</TD>
<TD>2022-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.511...54H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.510.4872E</TD>
<TD>Erratum: Birth of the ELMs: a ZTF survey for evolved cataclysmic variables turning into extremely low-mass white dwarfs</TD>
<TD>El-Badry, Kareem; Rix, Hans-Walter; Quataert, Eliot; Kupfer, Thomas; Shen, Ken J.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 510, Issue 4, pp.4872-4872</TD>
<TD>2022-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.510.4872E</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.510.4779S</TD>
<TD>Type Ia supernova magnitude step from the local dark matter environment</TD>
<TD>Steigerwald, Heinrich; Rodrigues, Davi; Profumo, Stefano; Marra, Valerio</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 510, Issue 4, pp.4779-4795</TD>
<TD>2022-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.510.4779S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.510.4265K</TD>
<TD>Optical and near-infrared spectroscopy of Nova V2891 Cygni: evidence for shock-induced dust formation</TD>
<TD>Kumar, Vipin; Srivastava, Mudit K.; Banerjee, Dipankar P. K.; Woodward, C. E.; Munari, Ulisse; Evans, Aneurin; Joshi, Vishal; Dallaporta, Sergio; Page, Kim L.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 510, Issue 3, pp.4265-4283</TD>
<TD>2022-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.510.4265K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.510.4242B</TD>
<TD>Accretion-induced merger leading to core-collapse supernovae in old stellar populations</TD>
<TD>Braudo, Jessica; Bear, Ealeal; Soker, Noam</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 510, Issue 3, pp.4242-4248</TD>
<TD>2022-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.510.4242B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.510.3758B</TD>
<TD>Transients from ONe white dwarf - neutron star/black hole mergers</TD>
<TD>Bobrick, Alexey; Zenati, Yossef; Perets, Hagai B.; Davies, Melvyn B.; Church, Ross</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 510, Issue 3, pp.3758-3777</TD>
<TD>2022-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.510.3758B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.510.3575H</TD>
<TD>Identifying RR Lyrae in the ZTF DR3 data set</TD>
<TD>Huang, Kuan-Wei; Koposov, Sergey E.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 510, Issue 3, pp.3575-3588</TD>
<TD>2022-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.510.3575H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022JSAES.11403688G</TD>
<TD>A multi-method approach to constrain the age of eruption and post-depositional processes in a Lower Jurassic ignimbrite from the Marifil Volcanic Complex, eastern North Patagonian Massif</TD>
<TD>González, Santiago N.; Greco, Gerson A.; Galetto, Antonella; Bordes, Sofia; Basei, Miguel A. S.; Parada, Martín N.; Giacosa, Raúl E.; Pons, M. Josefina</TD>
<TD>Journal of South American Earth Sciences, Volume 114, article id. 103688.</TD>
<TD>2022-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022JSAES.11403688G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022JOSS....7.3612R</TD>
<TD>DBSP_DRP: A Python package for automated spectroscopic data reduction of DBSP data</TD>
<TD>Mandigo-Stoba, Milan Sharma; Fremling, Christoffer; Kasliwal, Mansi M.</TD>
<TD>Journal of Open Source Software, vol. 7, issue 71, p. 3612</TD>
<TD>2022-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022JOSS....7.3612R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022JHEP...03..037D</TD>
<TD>J/ψ polarization in semi-inclusive DIS at low and high transverse momentum</TD>
<TD>D'Alesio, Umberto; Maxia, Luca; Murgia, Francesco; Pisano, Cristian; Rajesh, Sangem</TD>
<TD>Journal of High Energy Physics, Volume 2022, Issue 03, article id. 37</TD>
<TD>2022-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022JHEP...03..037D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJS..259...13Q</TD>
<TD>Linking Extragalactic Transients and Their Host Galaxy Properties: Transient Sample, Multiwavelength Host Identification, and Database Construction</TD>
<TD>Qin, Yu-Jing; Zabludoff, Ann; Kisley, Marina; Liu, Yuantian; Arcavi, Iair; Barnard, Kobus; Behroozi, Peter; French, K. Decker; McCully, Curtis; Merchant, Nirav</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 259, Issue 1, id.13, 57 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJS..259...13Q</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJS..259...11X</TD>
<TD>A Catalog of LAMOST Variable Sources Based on Time-domain Photometry of ZTF</TD>
<TD>Xu, Tingting; Liu, Chao; Wang, Feng; Huang, Weirong; Deng, Hui; Mei, Ying; Cao, Zhong</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 259, Issue 1, id.11, 14 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJS..259...11X</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...928...63C</TD>
<TD>AT 2019avd: A Tidal Disruption Event with a Two-phase Evolution</TD>
<TD>Chen, Jin-Hong; Dou, Li-Ming; Shen, Rong-Feng</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 928, Issue 1, id.63, 15 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...928...63C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...928...20B</TD>
<TD>New Variable Hot Subdwarf Stars Identified from Anomalous Gaia Flux Errors, Observed by TESS, and Classified via Fourier Diagnostics</TD>
<TD>Barlow, Brad N.; Corcoran, Kyle A.; Parker, Isabelle M.; Kupfer, Thomas; Németh, Péter; Hermes, J. J.; Lopez, Isaac D.; Frondorf, Will J.; Vestal, David; Holden, Jazzmyn</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 928, Issue 1, id.20, 22 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...928...20B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...927L..19W</TD>
<TD>Revisiting the Rates and Demographics of Tidal Disruption Events: Effects of the Disk Formation Efficiency</TD>
<TD>Wong, Thomas Hong Tsun; Pfister, Hugo; Dai, Lixin</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 927, Issue 1, id.L19, 14 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...927L..19W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...927..222L</TD>
<TD>Revealing the Field Sub-subgiant Population Using a Catalog of Active Giant Stars and Gaia EDR3</TD>
<TD>Leiner, Emily M.; Geller, Aaron M.; Gully-Santiago, Michael A.; Gosnell, Natalie M.; Tofflemire, Benjamin M.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 927, Issue 2, id.222, 12 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...927..222L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...927..191B</TD>
<TD>Identifying Lensed Quasars and Measuring Their Time Delays from Unresolved Light Curves</TD>
<TD>Bag, Satadru; Shafieloo, Arman; Liao, Kai; Treu, Tommaso</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 927, Issue 2, id.191, 22 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...927..191B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...927..180P</TD>
<TD>The Type Icn SN 2021csp: Implications for the Origins of the Fastest Supernovae and the Fates of Wolf-Rayet Stars</TD>
<TD>Perley, Daniel A.; Sollerman, Jesper; Schulze, Steve; Yao, Yuhan; Fremling, Christoffer; Gal-Yam, Avishay; Ho, Anna Y. Q.; Yang, Yi; Kool, Erik C.; Irani, Ido; Yan, Lin; Andreoni, Igor; Baade, Dietrich; Bellm, Eric C.; Brink, Thomas G.; Chen, Ting-Wan; Cikota, Aleksandar; Coughlin, Michael W.; Dahiwale, Aishwarya; Dekany, Richard; Duev, Dmitry A.; Filippenko, Alexei V.; Hoeflich, Peter; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Kulkarni, S. R.; Lunnan, Ragnhild; Masci, Frank J.; Maund, Justyn R.; Medford, Michael S.; Riddle, Reed; Rosnet, Philippe; Shupe, David L.; Strotjohann, Nora Linn; Tzanidakis, Anastasios; Zheng, WeiKang</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 927, Issue 2, id.180, 23 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...927..180P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...927..163C</TD>
<TD>Kilonova Detectability with Wide-field Instruments</TD>
<TD>Chase, Eve A.; O'Connor, Brendan; Fryer, Christopher L.; Troja, Eleonora; Korobkin, Oleg; Wollaeger, Ryan T.; Ristic, Marko; Fontes, Christopher J.; Hungerford, Aimee L.; Herring, Angela M.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 927, Issue 2, id.163, 16 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...927..163C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...927..158V</TD>
<TD>The Pulsating Helium-atmosphere White Dwarfs. I. New DBVs from the Sloan Digital Sky Survey</TD>
<TD>Vanderbosch, Zachary P.; Hermes, J. J.; Winget, Don E.; Montgomery, Michael H.; Bell, Keaton J.; Nitta, Atsuko; Kepler, S. O.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 927, Issue 2, id.158, 16 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...927..158V</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...927..150R</TD>
<TD>Microlensing Events in the Galactic Plane Using the Zwicky Transient Facility</TD>
<TD>Rodriguez, Antonio C.; Mróz, Przemek; Kulkarni, Shrinivas R.; Andreoni, Igor; Bellm, Eric C.; Dekany, Richard; Drake, Andrew J.; Duev, Dmitry A.; Graham, Matthew J.; Masci, Frank J.; Prince, Thomas A.; Riddle, Reed; Shupe, David L.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 927, Issue 2, id.150, 11 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...927..150R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...927..148C</TD>
<TD>A Physical Model of Delayed Rebrightenings in Shock-interacting Supernovae without Narrow-line Emission</TD>
<TD>Coughlin, Eric R.; Zrake, Jonathan</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 927, Issue 2, id.148, 25 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...927..148C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...927..139O</TD>
<TD>Identification of an X-Ray Pulsar in the BeXRB System IGR J18219-1347</TD>
<TD>O'Connor, B.; Göğüş, E.; Huppenkothen, D.; Kouveliotou, C.; Gorgone, N.; Townsend, L. J.; Calamida, A.; Fruchter, A.; Buckley, D. A. H.; Baring, M. G.; Kennea, J. A.; Younes, G.; Arzoumanian, Z.; Bellm, E.; Cenko, S. B.; Gendreau, K.; Granot, J.; Hailey, C.; Harrison, F.; Hartmann, D.; Kaper, L.; Kutyrev, A.; Slane, P. O.; Stern, D.; Troja, E.; van der Horst, A. J.; Wijers, R. A. M. J.; Woudt, P.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 927, Issue 2, id.139, 13 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...927..139O</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...927..125C</TD>
<TD>Recurrent Strong Outbursts of an EXor-like Young Eruptive Star Gaia20eae</TD>
<TD>Cruz-Sáenz de Miera, Fernando; Kóspál, Ágnes; Ábrahám, Péter; Park, Sunkyung; Nagy, Zsófia; Siwak, Michał; Kun, Mária; Fiorellino, Eleonora; Szabó, Zsófia Marianna; Antoniucci, Simone; Giannini, Teresa; Nisini, Brunella; Szabados, László; Kriskovics, Levente; Ordasi, András; Szakáts, Róbert; Vida, Krisztián; Vinkó, József; Zieliński, Paweł; Wyrzykowski, Łukasz; García-Álvarez, David; Dróżdż, Marek; Ogłoza, Waldemar; Sonbas, Eda</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 927, Issue 1, id.125, 15 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...927..125C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...927...78D</TD>
<TD>A Carbon/Oxygen-dominated Atmosphere Days after Explosion for the "Super-Chandrasekhar" Type Ia SN 2020esm</TD>
<TD>Dimitriadis, Georgios; Foley, Ryan J.; Arendse, Nikki; Coulter, David A.; Jacobson-Galán, Wynn V.; Siebert, Matthew R.; Izzo, Luca; Jones, David O.; Kilpatrick, Charles D.; Pan, Yen-Chen; Taggart, Kirsty; Auchettl, Katie; Gall, Christa; Hjorth, Jens; Kasen, Daniel; Piro, Anthony L.; Raimundo, Sandra I.; Ramirez-Ruiz, Enrico; Rest, Armin; Swift, Jonathan J.; Woosley, Stan E.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 927, Issue 1, id.78, 16 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...927...78D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...927...50R</TD>
<TD>A Systematic Exploration of Kilonova Candidates from Neutron Star Mergers during the Third Gravitational-wave Observing Run</TD>
<TD>Rastinejad, J. C.; Paterson, K.; Fong, W.; Sand, D. J.; Lundquist, M. J.; Hosseinzadeh, G.; Christensen, E.; Daly, P. N.; Gibbs, A. R.; Hall, S.; Shelly, F.; Yang, S.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 927, Issue 1, id.50, 16 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...927...50R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...927...45C</TD>
<TD>Gaia GraL: Gaia DR2 Gravitational Lens Systems. VII. XMM-Newton Observations of Lensed Quasars</TD>
<TD>Connor, Thomas; Stern, Daniel; Krone-Martins, Alberto; Djorgovski, S. G.; Graham, Matthew J.; Walton, Dominic J.; Delchambre, Ludovic; Ducourant, Christine; Teixeira, Ramachrisna; Le Campion, Jean-François; den Brok, Jakob Sebastian; Dobie, Dougal; Galluccio, Laurent; Jalan, Priyanka; Klioner, Sergei A.; Klüter, Jonas; Mahabal, Ashish A.; Negi, Vibhore; Nierenberg, Anna; Petit, Quentin; Scarano, Sergio, Jr.; Slezak, Eric; Sluse, Dominique; Spíndola-Duarte, Carolina; Surdej, Jean; Wambsganss, Joachim</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 927, Issue 1, id.45, 11 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...927...45C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...927...25M</TD>
<TD>Properties of Type Ibn Supernovae: Implications for the Progenitor Evolution and the Origin of a Population of Rapid Transients</TD>
<TD>Maeda, Keiichi; Moriya, Takashi J.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 927, Issue 1, id.25, 17 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...927...25M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...927...12P</TD>
<TD>Long-term Photometric and Low-resolution Spectroscopic Analysis of Five Contact Binaries</TD>
<TD>Panchal, A.; Joshi, Y. C.; De Cat, Peter; Tiwari, S. N.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 927, Issue 1, id.12, 18 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...927...12P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...927...10I</TD>
<TD>Less Than 1% of Core-collapse Supernovae in the Local Universe Occur in Elliptical Galaxies</TD>
<TD>Irani, I.; Prentice, S. J.; Schulze, S.; Gal-Yam, A.; Teffs, Jacob; Mazzali, Paolo; Sollerman, J.; Gonzalez, E. P.; Taggart, K.; De, Kishalay; Fremling, Christoffer; Perley, Daniel A.; Strotjohann, Nora L.; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Howell, A.; Dhawan, S.; Tzanidakis, Anastasios; Hiramatsu, Daichi; Kool, Erik C.; Anderson, J. P.; Müller-Bravo, T. E.; Dekany, Richard; Gromadzki, Mariusz; Carini, Roberta; Galbany, L.; Drake, Andrew J.; Burke, Jamison; Pellegrino, Craig; Della Valle, Massimo; Medford, Michael S.; Rusholme, Ben; Young, D. R.; Gutiérrez, Claudia P.; Inserra, Cosimo; Omer, Rafia; Shupe, David L.; Chen, T. -W.; Shin, Kyung Min; Yaron, Ofer; McCully, Curtis; Nicholl, Matt; Riddle, Reed</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 927, Issue 1, id.10, 22 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...927...10I</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022AJ....163..115H</TD>
<TD>LkHα 225 (V1318 Cyg) South in Outburst</TD>
<TD>Hillenbrand, Lynne A.; Isaacson, Howard; Rodriguez, Antonio C.; Connelley, Michael; Reipurth, Bo; Kuhn, Michael A.; Beck, Tracy; Perez, Diego Rodriguez</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 163, Issue 3, id.115, 22 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022AJ....163..115H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...659A.199R</TD>
<TD>SUPPNet: Neural network for stellar spectrum normalisation</TD>
<TD>Różański, T.; Niemczura, E.; Lemiesz, J.; Posiłek, N.; Różański, P.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 659, id.A199, 20 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...659A.199R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...659A.171P</TD>
<TD>On the trail of a comet's tail: A particle tracking algorithm for comet 67P/Churyumov-Gerasimenko</TD>
<TD>Pfeifer, Marius; Agarwal, Jessica; Schröter, Matthias</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 659, id.A171, 16 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...659A.171P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...659A.145G</TD>
<TD>A WISE view on extreme AGB stars</TD>
<TD>Groenewegen, M. A. T.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 659, id.A145, 31 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...659A.145G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...659A...8Z</TD>
<TD>The first study of four doubly eclipsing systems</TD>
<TD>Zasche, P.; Henzl, Z.; Kára, J.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 659, id.A8, 8 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...659A...8Z</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022RAA....22b5004L</TD>
<TD>Identifications of RR Lyrae Stars and Quasars from the Simulated Data of Mephisto-W Survey</TD>
<TD>Lei, Lei; Chen, Bing-Qiu; Li, Jin-Da; Wu, Jin-Tai; Jiang, Si-Yi; Liu, Xiao-Wei</TD>
<TD>Research in Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 22, Issue 2, id.025004, 8 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022RAA....22b5004L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022PASP..134b4505K</TD>
<TD>New Modules for the SEDMachine to Remove Contaminations from Cosmic Rays and Non-target Light: BYECR and CONTSEP</TD>
<TD>Kim, Y. -L.; Rigault, M.; Neill, J. D.; Briday, M.; Copin, Y.; Lezmy, J.; Nicolas, N.; Riddle, R.; Sharma, Y.; Smith, M.; Sollerman, J.; Walters, R.</TD>
<TD>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 134, Issue 1032, id.024505, 9 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022PASP..134b4505K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022PASP..134b4201C</TD>
<TD>Citizen ASAS-SN Data Release. I. Variable Star Classification Using Citizen Science</TD>
<TD>Christy, C. T.; Jayasinghe, T.; Stanek, K. Z.; Kochanek, C. S.; Way, Z.; Prieto, J. L.; Shappee, B. J.; Holoien, T. W. -S.; Thompson, T. A.; Schneider, A.</TD>
<TD>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 134, Issue 1032, id.024201, 20 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022PASP..134b4201C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022PASJ...74L...1F</TD>
<TD>TOI-2285b: A 1.7 Earth-radius planet near the habitable zone around a nearby M dwarf</TD>
<TD>Fukui, Akihiko; Kimura, Tadahiro; Hirano, Teruyuki; Narita, Norio; Kodama, Takanori; Hori, Yasunori; Ikoma, Masahiro; Pallé, Enric; Murgas, Felipe; Parviainen, Hannu; Kawauchi, Kiyoe; Mori, Mayuko; Esparza-Borges, Emma; Bieryla, Allyson; Irwin, Jonathan; Safonov, Boris S.; Stassun, Keivan G.; Alvarez-Hernandez, Leticia; Béjar, Víctor J. S.; Casasayas-Barris, Núria; Chen, Guo; Crouzet, Nicolas; de Leon, Jerome P.; Isogai, Keisuke; Kagetani, Taiki; Klagyivik, Peter; Korth, Judith; Kurita, Seiya; Kusakabe, Nobuhiko; Livingston, John; Luque, Rafael; Madrigal-Aguado, Alberto; Morello, Giuseppe; Nishiumi, Taku; Orell-Miquel, Jaume; Oshagh, Mahmoudreza; Sánchez-Benavente, Manuel; Stangret, Monika; Terada, Yuka; Watanabe, Noriharu; Zou, Yujie; Tamura, Motohide; Kurokawa, Takashi; Kuzuhara, Masayuki; Nishikawa, Jun; Omiya, Masashi; Vievard, Sébastien; Ueda, Akitoshi; Latham, David W.; Quinn, Samuel N.; Strakhov, Ivan S.; Belinski, Alexandr A.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Ricker, George R.; Seager, Sara; Vanderspek, Roland; Winn, Joshua N.; Charbonneau, David; Ciardi, David R.; Collins, Karen A.; Doty, John P.; Bachelet, Etienne; Harbeck, Daniel</TD>
<TD>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Volume 74, Issue 1, pp.L1-L8</TD>
<TD>2022-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022PASJ...74L...1F</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022PASA...39....7S</TD>
<TD>Multimessenger astronomy with a kHz-band gravitational-wave observatory</TD>
<TD>Sarin, Nikhil; Lasky, Paul D.</TD>
<TD>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Australia, Volume 39, article id. e007</TD>
<TD>2022-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022PASA...39....7S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.510.2305H</TD>
<TD>Deep Extragalactic VIsible Legacy Survey: Data Release 1 blended spectra search for candidate strong gravitational lenses</TD>
<TD>Holwerda, B. W.; Knabel, S.; Thorne, J. E.; Bellstedt, S.; Siudek, M.; Davies, L. J. M.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 510, Issue 2, pp.2305-2326</TD>
<TD>2022-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.510.2305H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.510.2228D</TD>
<TD>The Zwicky Transient Facility Type Ia supernova survey: first data release and results</TD>
<TD>Dhawan, S.; Goobar, A.; Smith, M.; Johansson, J.; Rigault, M.; Nordin, J.; Biswas, R.; Goldstein, D.; Nugent, P.; Kim, Y. -L.; Miller, A. A.; Graham, M. J.; Medford, M.; Kasliwal, M. M.; Kulkarni, S. R.; Duev, Dmitry A.; Bellm, E.; Rosnet, P.; Riddle, R.; Sollerman, J.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 510, Issue 2, pp.2228-2241</TD>
<TD>2022-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.510.2228D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.510.2025P</TD>
<TD>Observable gravitational waves from tidal disruption events and their electromagnetic counterpart</TD>
<TD>Pfister, Hugo; Toscani, Martina; Wong, Thomas Hong Tsun; Dai, Jane Lixin; Lodato, Giuseppe; Rossi, Elena M.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 510, Issue 2, pp.2025-2040</TD>
<TD>2022-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.510.2025P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.510.1791N</TD>
<TD>Optical flux and colour variability of blazars in the ZTF survey</TD>
<TD>Negi, Vibhore; Joshi, Ravi; Chand, Krishan; Chand, Hum; Wiita, Paul; Ho, Luis C.; Singh, Ravi S.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 510, Issue 2, pp.1791-1800</TD>
<TD>2022-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.510.1791N</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.510.1002D</TD>
<TD>The return of the spin period in DW Cnc and evidence of new high state outbursts</TD>
<TD>Duffy, C.; Ramsay, G.; Steeghs, D.; Kennedy, M. R.; West, R. G.; Wheatley, P. J.; Dhillon, V. S.; Ackley, K.; Dyer, M. J.; Galloway, D. K.; Gill, S.; Acton, J. S.; Burleigh, M. R.; Casewell, S. L.; Goad, M. R.; Henderson, B. A.; Tilbrook, R. H.; Strøm, P. A.; Anderson, D. R.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 510, Issue 1, pp.1002-1009</TD>
<TD>2022-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.510.1002D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.510..366T</TD>
<TD>The large-scale environment of thermonuclear and core-collapse supernovae</TD>
<TD>Tsaprazi, Eleni; Jasche, Jens; Goobar, Ariel; Peiris, Hiranya V.; Andreoni, Igor; Coughlin, Michael W.; Fremling, Christoffer U.; Graham, Matthew J.; Kasliwal, Mansi; Kulkarni, Shri R.; Mahabal, Ashish A.; Riddle, Reed; Sollerman, Jesper; Tzanidakis, Anastasios</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 510, Issue 1, pp.366-372</TD>
<TD>2022-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.510..366T</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.509.6028C</TD>
<TD>An imaging polarimetry survey of Type Ia supernovae: are peculiar extinction and polarization properties produced by circumstellar or interstellar matter?</TD>
<TD>Chu, Matthew R.; Cikota, Aleksandar; Baade, Dietrich; Patat, Ferdinando; Filippenko, Alexei V.; Wheeler, J. Craig; Maund, Justyn; Bulla, Mattia; Yang, Yi; Höflich, Peter; Wang, Lifan</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 509, Issue 4, pp.6028-6046</TD>
<TD>2022-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.509.6028C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.509.5340B</TD>
<TD>Two c's in a pod: cosmology-independent measurement of the Type Ia supernova colour-luminosity relation with a sibling pair</TD>
<TD>Biswas, Rahul; Goobar, Ariel; Dhawan, Suhail; Schulze, Steve; Johansson, Joel; Bellm, Eric C.; Dekany, Richard; Drake, Andrew J.; Duev, Dmitry A.; Fremling, Christoffer; Graham, Matthew; Kim, Young-Lo; Kool, Erik C.; Kulkarni, Shrinivas R.; Mahabal, Ashish A.; Perley, Daniel; Rigault, Mickael; Rusholme, Ben; Sollerman, Jesper; Shupe, David L.; Smith, Matthew; Walters, Richard S.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 509, Issue 4, pp.5340-5356</TD>
<TD>2022-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.509.5340B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.509.5275S</TD>
<TD>The ZTF-BTS Type Ia supernovae luminosity function is consistent with a single progenitor channel for the explosions</TD>
<TD>Sharon, Amir; Kushnir, Doron</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 509, Issue 4, pp.5275-5297</TD>
<TD>2022-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.509.5275S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022JOSS....7.3612M</TD>
<TD>DBSP_DRP: A Python package for automated spectroscopic data reduction of DBSP data</TD>
<TD>Mandigo-Stoba, Milan Sharma; Fremling, Christoffer; Kasliwal, Mansi</TD>
<TD>Journal of Open Source Software, vol. 7, issue 70, id. 3612</TD>
<TD>2022-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022JOSS....7.3612M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ExA....53....1S</TD>
<TD>Astronomical big data processing using machine learning: A comprehensive review</TD>
<TD>Sen, Snigdha; Agarwal, Sonali; Chakraborty, Pavan; Singh, Krishna Pratap</TD>
<TD>Experimental Astronomy, Volume 53, Issue 1, p.1-43</TD>
<TD>2022-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ExA....53....1S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJS..258...43M</TD>
<TD>A Fresh Look at AGB Stars in Galactic Open Clusters with Gaia: Impact on Stellar Models and the Initial-Final Mass Relation</TD>
<TD>Marigo, Paola; Bossini, Diego; Trabucchi, Michele; Addari, Francesco; Girardi, Léo; Cummings, Jeffrey D.; Pastorelli, Giada; Dal Tio, Piero; Costa, Guglielmo; Bressan, Alessandro</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 258, Issue 2, id.43, 37 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJS..258...43M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...926L..35O</TD>
<TD>The Unanticipated Phenomenology of the Blazar PKS 2131-021: A Unique Supermassive Black Hole Binary Candidate</TD>
<TD>O'Neill, S.; Kiehlmann, S.; Readhead, A. C. S.; Aller, M. F.; Blandford, R. D.; Liodakis, I.; Lister, M. L.; Mróz, P.; O'Dea, C. P.; Pearson, T. J.; Ravi, V.; Vallisneri, M.; Cleary, K. A.; Graham, M. J.; Grainge, K. J. B.; Hodges, M. W.; Hovatta, T.; Lähteenmäki, A.; Lamb, J. W.; Lazio, T. J. W.; Max-Moerbeck, W.; Pavlidou, V.; Prince, T. A.; Reeves, R. A.; Tornikoski, M.; Vergara de la Parra, P.; Zensus, J. A.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 926, Issue 2, id.L35, 21 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...926L..35O</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...926L..11S</TD>
<TD>Optical Rebrightening of Extragalactic Transients from the Zwicky Transient Facility</TD>
<TD>Soraisam, Monika; Matheson, Thomas; Lee, Chien-Hsiu; Saha, Abhijit; Narayan, Gautham; Wolf, Nicholas; Scott, Adam; Figuereo, Stephanie; Nuñez, Rafael; McKinnon, Kevin; Guhathakurta, Puragra; Brink, Thomas G.; Filippenko, Alexei V.; Smith, Nathan</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 926, Issue 2, id.L11, 11 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...926L..11S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...926..210R</TD>
<TD>New Clues to the Evolution of Dwarf Carbon Stars From Their Variability and X-Ray Emission</TD>
<TD>Roulston, Benjamin R.; Green, Paul J.; Montez, Rodolfo; Filippazzo, Joseph; Drake, Jeremy J.; Toonen, Silvia; Anderson, Scott F.; Eracleous, Michael; Frank, Adam</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 926, Issue 2, id.210, 14 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...926..210R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...926..184J</TD>
<TD>A Systematic Analysis of Stellar Populations in the Host Galaxies of Changing-look AGNs</TD>
<TD>Jin, Jun-Jie; Wu, Xue-Bing; Feng, Xiao-Tong</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 926, Issue 2, id.184, 23 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...926..184J</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...926..152F</TD>
<TD>An Infrared Search for Kilonovae with the WINTER Telescope. I. Binary Neutron Star Mergers</TD>
<TD>Frostig, Danielle; Biscoveanu, Sylvia; Mo, Geoffrey; Karambelkar, Viraj; Dal Canton, Tito; Chen, Hsin-Yu; Kasliwal, Mansi; Katsavounidis, Erik; Lourie, Nathan P.; Simcoe, Robert A.; Vitale, Salvatore</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 926, Issue 2, id.152, 15 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...926..152F</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...926..125P</TD>
<TD>Circumstellar Interaction Powers the Light Curves of Luminous Rapidly Evolving Optical Transients</TD>
<TD>Pellegrino, C.; Howell, D. A.; Vinkó, J.; Gangopadhyay, A.; Xiang, D.; Arcavi, I.; Brown, P.; Burke, J.; Hiramatsu, D.; Hosseinzadeh, G.; Li, Z.; McCully, C.; Misra, K.; Newsome, M.; Gonzalez, E. Padilla; Pritchard, T. A.; Valenti, S.; Wang, X.; Zhang, T.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 926, Issue 2, id.125, 16 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...926..125P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...926..112B</TD>
<TD>Radio and X-Ray Observations of the Luminous Fast Blue Optical Transient AT 2020xnd</TD>
<TD>Bright, Joe S.; Margutti, Raffaella; Matthews, David; Brethauer, Daniel; Coppejans, Deanne; Wieringa, Mark H.; Metzger, Brian D.; DeMarchi, Lindsay; Laskar, Tanmoy; Romero, Charles; Alexander, Kate D.; Horesh, Assaf; Migliori, Giulia; Chornock, Ryan; Berger, E.; Bietenholz, Michael; Devlin, Mark J.; Dicker, Simon R.; Jacobson-Galán, W. V.; Mason, Brian S.; Milisavljevic, Dan; Motta, Sara E.; Mroczkowski, Tony; Ramirez-Ruiz, Enrico; Rhodes, Lauren; Sarazin, Craig L.; Sfaradi, Itai; Sievers, Jonathan</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 926, Issue 2, id.112, 15 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...926..112B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...926...98D</TD>
<TD>Late-onset Circumstellar Medium Interactions are Rare: An Unbiased GALEX View of Type Ia Supernovae</TD>
<TD>Dubay, Liam O.; Tucker, Michael A.; Do, Aaron; Shappee, Benjamin J.; Anand, Gagandeep S.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 926, Issue 1, id.98, 19 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...926...98D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...926...68G</TD>
<TD>Gaia 20eae: A Newly Discovered Episodically Accreting Young Star</TD>
<TD>Ghosh, Arpan; Sharma, Saurabh; Ninan, Joe P.; Ojha, Devendra K.; Bhatt, Bhuwan C.; Kanodia, Shubham; Mahadevan, Suvrath; Stefansson, Gudmundur; Yadav, R. K.; Gour, A. S.; Pandey, Rakesh; Sinha, Tirthendu; Panwar, Neelam; Wisniewski, John P.; Cañas, Caleb I.; Lin, Andrea S. J.; Roy, Arpita; Hearty, Fred; Ramsey, Lawrence; Robertson, Paul; Schwab, Christian</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 926, Issue 1, id.68, 14 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...926...68G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...926...20T</TD>
<TD>The Early Phases of Supernova 2020pni: Shock Ionization of the Nitrogen-enriched Circumstellar Material</TD>
<TD>Terreran, G.; Jacobson-Galán, W. V.; Groh, J. H.; Margutti, R.; Coppejans, D. L.; Dimitriadis, G.; Kilpatrick, C. D.; Matthews, D. J.; Siebert, M. R.; Angus, C. R.; Brink, T. G.; Filippenko, A. V.; Foley, R. J.; Jones, D. O.; Tinyanont, S.; Gall, C.; Pfister, H.; Zenati, Y.; Ansari, Z.; Auchettl, K.; El-Badry, K.; Magnier, E. A.; Zheng, W.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 926, Issue 1, id.20, 22 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...926...20T</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...926...10R</TD>
<TD>The Fast Evolving, Tremendous Blue Superoutburst in ASASSN-21au Reveals a Dichotomy in the Outbursts of Long-period AM CVns</TD>
<TD>Rivera Sandoval, L. E.; Heinke, C. O.; Hameury, J. M.; Cavecchi, Y.; Vanmunster, T.; Tordai, T.; Romanov, F. D.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 926, Issue 1, id.10, 9 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...926...10R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...925L..12K</TD>
<TD>Discovery of a Double-detonation Thermonuclear Supernova Progenitor</TD>
<TD>Kupfer, Thomas; Bauer, Evan B.; van Roestel, Jan; Bellm, Eric C.; Bildsten, Lars; Fuller, Jim; Prince, Thomas A.; Heber, Ulrich; Geier, Stephan; Green, Matthew J.; Kulkarni, Shrinivas R.; Bloemen, Steven; Laher, Russ R.; Rusholme, Ben; Schneider, David</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 925, Issue 2, id.L12, 10 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...925L..12K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...925..217D</TD>
<TD>SN 2020sck: Deflagration in a Carbon-Oxygen White Dwarf</TD>
<TD>Dutta, Anirban; Sahu, D. K.; Anupama, G. C.; Joharle, Simran; Kumar, Brajesh; Nayana, A. J.; Singh, Avinash; Kumar, Harsh; Bhalerao, Varun; Barway, Sudhansu</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 925, Issue 2, id.217, 19 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...925..217D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...925..171H</TD>
<TD>A Matched Survey for the Enigmatic Low Radio Frequency Transient ILT J225347+862146</TD>
<TD>Huang, Yuping; Anderson, Marin M.; Hallinan, Gregg; W. Lazio, T. Joseph; Price, Danny C.; Sharma, Yashvi</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 925, Issue 2, id.171, 18 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...925..171H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022AJ....163..102B</TD>
<TD>A Search for Planet Nine using the Zwicky Transient Facility Public Archive</TD>
<TD>Brown, Michael E.; Batygin, Konstantin</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 163, Issue 2, id.102, 6 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022AJ....163..102B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022AJ....163...95S</TD>
<TD>Finding Fast Transients in Real Time Using a Novel Light-curve Analysis Algorithm</TD>
<TD>Strausbaugh, Robert; Cucchiara, Antonino; Dow, Michael, Jr.; Webb, Sara; Zhang, Jielai; Goode, Simon; Cooke, Jeff</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 163, Issue 2, id.95, 13 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022AJ....163...95S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022AJ....163...89C</TD>
<TD>An Eccentric Brown Dwarf Eclipsing an M dwarf</TD>
<TD>Cañas, Caleb I.; Mahadevan, Suvrath; Bender, Chad F.; Salazar Rivera, Noah Isaac; Monson, Andrew; Beard, Corey; Lubin, Jack; Robertson, Paul; Gupta, Arvind F.; Cochran, William D.; Fredrick, Connor; Hearty, Fred; Jones, Sinclaire; Kanodia, Shubham; Lin, Andrea S. J.; Ninan, Joe P.; Ramsey, Lawrence W.; Schwab, Christian; Stefánsson, Guđmundur</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 163, Issue 2, id.89, 16 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022AJ....163...89C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022AJ....163...57Q</TD>
<TD>Photometric Classification of Early-time Supernova Light Curves with SCONE</TD>
<TD>Qu, Helen; Sako, Masao</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 163, Issue 2, id.57, 14 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022AJ....163...57Q</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022SCPMA..6510411W</TD>
<TD>Forecast for cosmological parameter estimation with gravitational-wave standard sirens from the LISA-Taiji network</TD>
<TD>Wang, Ling-Feng; Jin, Shang-Jie; Zhang, Jing-Fei; Zhang, Xin</TD>
<TD>Science China Physics, Mechanics &amp;amp; Astronomy, Volume 65, Issue 1, article id.210411</TD>
<TD>2022-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022SCPMA..6510411W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022RAA....22a5014W</TD>
<TD>The Variability of the Narrow-line Seyfert 1 Galaxies from the Pan-STARRS's View</TD>
<TD>Wang, Hong-Tao; Su, Yan-Ping; Ge, Xue; Chen, Yong-Yun; Yu, Xiao-Ling</TD>
<TD>Research in Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 22, Issue 1, id.015014, 8 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022RAA....22a5014W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022PASP..134a5005Z</TD>
<TD>Role of Topocentric Parallax in Near-Earth Object Initial Orbit Determination</TD>
<TD>Zhai, Chengxing; Shao, Michael; Saini, Navtej S.; Choi, Philip; Trahan, Russell; Nazli, Kutay; Zhan, Max; Evans, Nez</TD>
<TD>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 134, Issue 1031, id.015005, 15 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022PASP..134a5005Z</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022Natur.601..201G</TD>
<TD>A WC/WO star exploding within an expanding carbon-oxygen-neon nebula</TD>
<TD>Gal-Yam, A.; Bruch, R.; Schulze, S.; Yang, Y.; Perley, D. A.; Irani, I.; Sollerman, J.; Kool, E. C.; Soumagnac, M. T.; Yaron, O.; Strotjohann, N. L.; Zimmerman, E.; Barbarino, C.; Kulkarni, S. R.; Kasliwal, M. M.; De, K.; Yao, Y.; Fremling, C.; Yan, L.; Ofek, E. O.; Fransson, C.; Filippenko, A. V.; Zheng, W.; Brink, T. G.; Copperwheat, C. M.; Foley, R. J.; Brown, J.; Siebert, M.; Leloudas, G.; Cabrera-Lavers, A. L.; Garcia-Alvarez, D.; Marante-Barreto, A.; Frederick, S.; Hung, T.; Wheeler, J. C.; Vinkó, J.; Thomas, B. P.; Graham, M. J.; Duev, D. A.; Drake, A. J.; Dekany, R.; Bellm, E. C.; Rusholme, B.; Shupe, D. L.; Andreoni, I.; Sharma, Y.; Riddle, R.; van Roestel, J.; Knezevic, N.</TD>
<TD>Nature, Volume 601, Issue 7892, p.201-204</TD>
<TD>2022-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022Natur.601..201G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.509.4171K</TD>
<TD>Eclipsing white dwarf binaries in Gaia and the Zwicky Transient Faaccility</TD>
<TD>Keller, Pascal M.; Breedt, Elmé; Hodgkin, Simon; Belokurov, Vasily; Wild, James; García-Soriano, Ignacio; Wise, Jacob L.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 509, Issue 3, pp.4171-4188</TD>
<TD>2022-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.509.4171K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.509.3427D</TD>
<TD>ASAS-SN search for optical counterparts of gravitational-wave events from the third observing run of Advanced LIGO/Virgo</TD>
<TD>de Jaeger, T.; Shappee, B. J.; Kochanek, C. S.; Stanek, K. Z.; Beacom, J. F.; Holoien, T. W. -S.; Thompson, Todd A.; Franckowiak, A.; Holmbo, S.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 509, Issue 3, pp.3427-3440</TD>
<TD>2022-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.509.3427D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.509.2566M</TD>
<TD>Variable star classification across the Galactic bulge and disc with the VISTA Variables in the Vía Láctea survey</TD>
<TD>Molnar, Thomas A.; Sanders, Jason L.; Smith, Leigh C.; Belokurov, Vasily; Lucas, Philip; Minniti, Dante</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 509, Issue 2, pp.2566-2592</TD>
<TD>2022-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.509.2566M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.509.2362L</TD>
<TD>Minute-cadence observations of the LAMOST fields with the TMTS: I. Methodology of detecting short-period variables and results from the first-year survey</TD>
<TD>Lin, Jie; Wang, Xiaofeng; Mo, Jun; Xi, Gaobo; Zhang, Jicheng; Jiang, Xiaojun; Shi, Jianrong; Zhang, Xiaobin; Zhang, Xiaoming; Wei, Zixuan; Ye, Limeng; Wu, Chengyuan; Yan, Shengyu; Chen, Zhihao; Li, Wenxiong; Li, Xue; Lin, Weili; Lin, Han; Sai, Hanna; Xiang, Danfeng; Zhang, Xinghan</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 509, Issue 2, pp.2362-2376</TD>
<TD>2022-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.509.2362L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.509.1269O</TD>
<TD>Light-curve fingerprints: an automated approach to the extraction of X-ray variability patterns with feature aggregation - an example application to GRS 1915+105</TD>
<TD>Orwat-Kapola, Jakub K.; Bird, Antony J.; Hill, Adam B.; Altamirano, Diego; Huppenkothen, Daniela</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 509, Issue 1, pp.1269-1290</TD>
<TD>2022-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.509.1269O</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.509..914C</TD>
<TD>El-CID: a filter for gravitational-wave electromagnetic counterpart identification</TD>
<TD>Chatterjee, Deep; Narayan, Gautham; Aleo, Patrick D.; Malanchev, Konstantin; Muthukrishna, Daniel</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 509, Issue 1, pp.914-930</TD>
<TD>2022-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.509..914C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022JAI....1140001D</TD>
<TD>Astrometric and Photometric Standard Candidates for the Upcoming 4-m International Liquid Mirror Telescope Survey</TD>
<TD>Dukiya, Naveen; Misra, Kuntal; Pradhan, Bikram; Negi, Vibhore; Ailawadhi, Bhavya; Kumar, Brajesh; Hickson, Paul; Surdej, Jean</TD>
<TD>Journal of Astronomical Instrumentation, Volume 11, Issue 4, id. 2240001</TD>
<TD>2022-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022JAI....1140001D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022Icar..37214723R</TD>
<TD>A photometric study of members of the NEOs Atiras population</TD>
<TD>Rondón, E.; Lazzaro, D.; Carvano, J.; Monteiro, F.; Arcoverde, P.; Evangelista, M.; Michimani, J.; Mesquita, W.; Rodrigues, T.</TD>
<TD>Icarus, Volume 372, article id. 114723.</TD>
<TD>2022-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022Icar..37214723R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022Icar..37114696I</TD>
<TD>Simulated SPHEREx spectra of asteroids and their implications for asteroid size and reflectance estimation</TD>
<TD>Ivezić, Željko; Ivezić, Vedrana; Moeyens, Joachim; Lisse, Carey M.; Bus, Schelte J.; Jones, Lynne; Crill, Brendan P.; Doré, Olivier; Emery, Joshua P.</TD>
<TD>Icarus, Volume 371, article id. 114696.</TD>
<TD>2022-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022Icar..37114696I</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022IJMPD..3140014D</TD>
<TD>Never bet against Einstein</TD>
<TD>de Paolis, Francesco</TD>
<TD>International Journal of Modern Physics D, Volume 31, Issue 11, id. 2240014</TD>
<TD>2022-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022IJMPD..3140014D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022CQGra..39b5004S</TD>
<TD>The science case for LIGO-India</TD>
<TD>Saleem, M.; Rana, Javed; Gayathri, V.; Vijaykumar, Aditya; Goyal, Srashti; Sachdev, Surabhi; Suresh, Jishnu; Sudhagar, S.; Mukherjee, Arunava; Gaur, Gurudatt; Sathyaprakash, Bangalore; Pai, Archana; Adhikari, Rana X.; Ajith, P.; Bose, Sukanta</TD>
<TD>Classical and Quantum Gravity, Volume 39, Issue 2, id.025004, 24 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022CQGra..39b5004S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJS..258...21W</TD>
<TD>Mid-infrared Outbursts in Nearby Galaxies (MIRONG). II. Optical Spectroscopic Follow-up</TD>
<TD>Wang, Yibo; Jiang, Ning; Wang, Tinggui; Yan, Lin; Sheng, Zhenfeng; Dou, Liming; Ding, Jiani; Cai, Zheng; Sun, Luming; Yang, Chenwei; Shu, Xinwen</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 258, Issue 1, id.21, 16 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJS..258...21W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJS..258...20A</TD>
<TD>The Milky Way Revealed by Variable Stars. I. Sample Selection of RR Lyrae Stars and Evidence for Merger History</TD>
<TD>Ablimit, Iminhaji; Zhao, Gang; Teklimakan, Uy.; Shi, Jian-Rong; Abdusalam, Kunduz</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 258, Issue 1, id.20, 13 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJS..258...20A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJS..258...16P</TD>
<TD>TESS Eclipsing Binary Stars. I. Short-cadence Observations of 4584 Eclipsing Binaries in Sectors 1-26</TD>
<TD>Prša, Andrej; Kochoska, Angela; Conroy, Kyle E.; Eisner, Nora; Hey, Daniel R.; IJspeert, Luc; Kruse, Ethan; Fleming, Scott W.; Johnston, Cole; Kristiansen, Martti H.; LaCourse, Daryll; Mortensen, Danielle; Pepper, Joshua; Stassun, Keivan G.; Torres, Guillermo; Abdul-Masih, Michael; Chakraborty, Joheen; Gagliano, Robert; Guo, Zhao; Hambleton, Kelly; Hong, Kyeongsoo; Jacobs, Thomas; Jones, David; Kostov, Veselin; Lee, Jae Woo; Omohundro, Mark; Orosz, Jerome A.; Page, Emma J.; Powell, Brian P.; Rappaport, Saul; Reed, Phill; Schnittman, Jeremy; Schwengeler, Hans Martin; Shporer, Avi; Terentev, Ivan A.; Vanderburg, Andrew; Welsh, William F.; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Doty, John P.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Latham, David W.; Ricker, George R.; Seager, Sara; Schlieder, Joshua E.; Shiao, Bernie; Vanderspek, Roland; Winn, Joshua N.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 258, Issue 1, id.16, 22 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJS..258...16P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJS..258...13B</TD>
<TD>Give Me a Few Hours: Exploring Short Timescales in Rubin Observatory Cadence Simulations</TD>
<TD>Bellm, Eric C.; Burke, Colin J.; Coughlin, Michael W.; Andreoni, Igor; Raiteri, Claudia M.; Bonito, Rosaria</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 258, Issue 1, id.13, 6 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJS..258...13B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJS..258....5A</TD>
<TD>Optimizing Cadences with Realistic Light-curve Filtering for Serendipitous Kilonova Discovery with Vera Rubin Observatory</TD>
<TD>Andreoni, Igor; Coughlin, Michael W.; Almualla, Mouza; Bellm, Eric C.; Bianco, Federica B.; Bulla, Mattia; Cucchiara, Antonino; Dietrich, Tim; Goobar, Ariel; Kool, Erik C.; Li, Xiaolong; Ragosta, Fabio; Sagués-Carracedo, Ana; Singer, Leo P.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 258, Issue 1, id.5, 8 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJS..258....5A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...925...92N</TD>
<TD>Near-Chandrasekhar-mass Type Ia Supernovae from the Double-degenerate Channel</TD>
<TD>Neopane, Sudarshan; Bhargava, Khanak; Fisher, Robert; Ferrari, Mckenzie; Yoshida, Shin'ichirou; Toonen, Silvia; Bravo, Eduardo</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 925, Issue 1, id.92, 13 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...925...92N</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...925...89C</TD>
<TD>Formation of the Double White Dwarf Binary PTF J0533+0209 through Stable Mass Transfer?</TD>
<TD>Chen, Hai-Liang; Tauris, Thomas M.; Chen, Xuefei; Han, Zhanwen</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 925, Issue 1, id.89, 8 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...925...89C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...925...67L</TD>
<TD>The UV/Optical Peak and X-Ray Brightening in TDE Candidate AT 2019azh: A Case of Stream-Stream Collision and Delayed Accretion</TD>
<TD>Liu, Xiao-Long; Dou, Li-Ming; Chen, Jin-Hong; Shen, Rong-Feng</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 925, Issue 1, id.67, 15 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...925...67L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...925...58M</TD>
<TD>Inferring Kilonova Population Properties with a Hierarchical Bayesian Framework. I. Nondetection Methodology and Single-event Analyses</TD>
<TD>Mohite, Siddharth R.; Rajkumar, Priyadarshini; Anand, Shreya; Kaplan, David L.; Coughlin, Michael W.; Sagués-Carracedo, Ana; Saleem, Muhammed; Creighton, Jolien; Brady, Patrick R.; Ahumada, Tomás; Almualla, Mouza; Andreoni, Igor; Bulla, Mattia; Graham, Matthew J.; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Kaye, Stephen; Laher, Russ R.; Shin, Kyung Min; Shupe, David L.; Singer, Leo P.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 925, Issue 1, id.58, 13 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...925...58M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...924L..35L</TD>
<TD>Follow-up Observations of the Prolonged, Super-Eddington, Tidal Disruption Event Candidate 3XMM J150052.0+015452: the Slow Decline Continues</TD>
<TD>Lin, Dacheng; Godet, Olivier; Webb, Natalie A.; Barret, Didier; Irwin, Jimmy A.; Komossa, S.; Ramirez-Ruiz, Enrico; Maksym, W. Peter; Grupe, Dirk; Carrasco, Eleazar R.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 924, Issue 2, id.L35, 8 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...924L..35L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...924L..30M</TD>
<TD>Impact of the SpaceX Starlink Satellites on the Zwicky Transient Facility Survey Observations</TD>
<TD>Mróz, Przemek; Otarola, Angel; Prince, Thomas A.; Dekany, Richard; Duev, Dmitry A.; Graham, Matthew J.; Groom, Steven L.; Masci, Frank J.; Medford, Michael S.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 924, Issue 2, id.L30, 6 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...924L..30M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...924..121A</TD>
<TD>Types of Transients in the Centers of Post-starburst and Quiescent Balmer-strong Galaxies</TD>
<TD>Arcavi, Iair; Nyiha, Irura; French, K. Decker</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 924, Issue 2, id.121, 11 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...924..121A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...924...79E</TD>
<TD>A Detailed Analysis of GW190521 with Phenomenological Waveform Models</TD>
<TD>Estellés, Héctor; Husa, Sascha; Colleoni, Marta; Mateu-Lucena, Maite; Planas, Maria de Lluc; García-Quirós, Cecilio; Keitel, David; Ramos-Buades, Antoni; Mehta, Ajit Kumar; Buonanno, Alessandra; Ossokine, Serguei</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 924, Issue 2, id.79, 18 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...924...79E</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...924...55G</TD>
<TD>An Early-time Optical and Ultraviolet Excess in the Type-Ic SN 2020oi</TD>
<TD>Gagliano, Alexander; Izzo, Luca; Kilpatrick, Charles D.; Mockler, Brenna; Jacobson-Galán, Wynn Vicente; Terreran, Giacomo; Dimitriadis, Georgios; Zenati, Yossef; Auchettl, Katie; Drout, Maria R.; Narayan, Gautham; Foley, Ryan J.; Margutti, R.; Rest, Armin; Jones, D. O.; Aganze, Christian; Aleo, Patrick D.; Burgasser, Adam J.; Coulter, D. A.; Gerasimov, Roman; Gall, Christa; Hjorth, Jens; Hsu, Chih-Chun; Magnier, Eugene A.; Mandel, Kaisey S.; Piro, Anthony L.; Rojas-Bravo, César; Siebert, Matthew R.; Stacey, Holland; Stroh, Michael Cullen; Swift, Jonathan J.; Taggart, Kirsty; Tinyanont, Samaporn; Tinyanont, Samaporn</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 924, Issue 2, id.55, 29 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...924...55G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...924...54P</TD>
<TD>Data-driven Expectations for Electromagnetic Counterpart Searches Based on LIGO/Virgo Public Alerts</TD>
<TD>Petrov, Polina; Singer, Leo P.; Coughlin, Michael W.; Kumar, Vishwesh; Almualla, Mouza; Anand, Shreya; Bulla, Mattia; Dietrich, Tim; Foucart, Francois; Guessoum, Nidhal</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 924, Issue 2, id.54, 10 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...924...54P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...924...15J</TD>
<TD>Final Moments. I. Precursor Emission, Envelope Inflation, and Enhanced Mass Loss Preceding the Luminous Type II Supernova 2020tlf</TD>
<TD>Jacobson-Galán, W. V.; Dessart, L.; Jones, D. O.; Margutti, R.; Coppejans, D. L.; Dimitriadis, G.; Foley, R. J.; Kilpatrick, C. D.; Matthews, D. J.; Rest, S.; Terreran, G.; Aleo, P. D.; Auchettl, K.; Blanchard, P. K.; Coulter, D. A.; Davis, K. W.; de Boer, T. J. L.; DeMarchi, L.; Drout, M. R.; Earl, N.; Gagliano, A.; Gall, C.; Hjorth, J.; Huber, M. E.; Ibik, A. L.; Milisavljevic, D.; Pan, Y. -C.; Rest, A.; Ridden-Harper, R.; Rojas-Bravo, C.; Siebert, M. R.; Smith, K. W.; Taggart, K.; Tinyanont, S.; Wang, Q.; Zenati, Y.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 924, Issue 1, id.15, 25 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...924...15J</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...924....2B</TD>
<TD>The Hubble Constant from Strongly Lensed Supernovae with Standardizable Magnifications</TD>
<TD>Birrer, Simon; Dhawan, Suhail; Shajib, Anowar J.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 924, Issue 1, id.2, 21 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...924....2B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022AJ....163...29L</TD>
<TD>Characterizing Sparse Asteroid Light Curves with Gaussian Processes</TD>
<TD>Lindberg, Christina Willecke; Huppenkothen, Daniela; Jones, R. Lynne; Bolin, Bryce T.; Jurić, Mario; Golkhou, V. Zach; Bellm, Eric C.; Drake, Andrew J.; Graham, Matthew J.; Laher, Russ R.; Mahabal, Ashish A.; Masci, Frank J.; Riddle, Reed; Shin, Kyung Min</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 163, Issue 1, id.29, 23 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022AJ....163...29L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022AJ....163...23C</TD>
<TD>Identify Light-curve Signals with Deep Learning Based Object Detection Algorithm. I. Transit Detection</TD>
<TD>Cui, Kaiming; Liu, Junjie; Feng, Fabo; Liu, Jifeng</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 163, Issue 1, id.23, 10 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022AJ....163...23C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;C....3800511G</TD>
<TD>GPU-enabled searches for periodic signals of unknown shape</TD>
<TD>Gowanlock, M.; Butler, N. R.; Trilling, D. E.; McNeill, A.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy and Computing, Volume 38, article id. 100511.</TD>
<TD>2022-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;C....3800511G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...657A..64S</TD>
<TD>Maximum luminosities of normal stripped-envelope supernovae are brighter than explosion models allow</TD>
<TD>Sollerman, J.; Yang, S.; Perley, D.; Schulze, S.; Fremling, C.; Kasliwal, M.; Shin, K.; Racine, B.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 657, id.A64, 10 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...657A..64S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021SCPMA..6420401B</TD>
<TD>The Gravitational-wave physics II: Progress</TD>
<TD>Bian, Ligong; Cai, Rong-Gen; Cao, Shuo; Cao, Zhoujian; Gao, He; Guo, Zong-Kuan; Lee, Kejia; Li, Di; Liu, Jing; Lu, Youjun; Pi, Shi; Wang, Jian-Min; Wang, Shao-Jiang; Wang, Yan; Yang, Tao; Yang, Xing-Yu; Yu, Shenghua; Zhang, Xin</TD>
<TD>Science China Physics, Mechanics &amp;amp; Astronomy, Volume 64, Issue 12, article id.120401</TD>
<TD>2021-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021SCPMA..6420401B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021RAA....21..292W</TD>
<TD>LAMOST Time-Domain survey: first results of four K2 plates</TD>
<TD>Wang, Song; Zhang, Hao-Tong; Bai, Zhong-Rui; Yuan, Hai-Long; Xiang, Mao-Sheng; Zhang, Bo; Hou, Wen; Zuo, Fang; Du, Bing; Li, Tan-Da; Yang, Fan; Cui, Kai-Ming; Wang, Yi-Lun; Li, Jiao; Kovalev, Mikhail; Li, Chun-Qian; Tian, Hao; Zong, Wei-Kai; Han, Heng-Geng; Liu, Chao; Luo, A. -Li; Shi, Jian-Rong; Fu, Jian-Ning; Bi, Shao-Lan; Han, Zhan-Wen; Liu, Ji-Feng</TD>
<TD>Research in Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 21, Issue 11, id.292, 20 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021RAA....21..292W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021Natur.600S..88K</TD>
<TD>How to tell a compelling story in scientific presentations</TD>
<TD>Kirchoff, Bruce</TD>
<TD>Nature, Volume 600, Issue 7890, p.S88-S89</TD>
<TD>2021-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021Natur.600S..88K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.508.5734M</TD>
<TD>A method for finding anomalous astronomical light curves and their analogues</TD>
<TD>Martínez-Galarza, J. Rafael; Bianco, Federica B.; Crake, Dennis; Tirumala, Kushal; Mahabal, Ashish A.; Graham, Matthew J.; Giles, Daniel</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 508, Issue 4, pp.5734-5756</TD>
<TD>2021-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.508.5734M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.508.5671L</TD>
<TD>Accretion of tidally disrupted asteroids on to white dwarfs: direct accretion versus disc processing</TD>
<TD>Li, Daohai; Mustill, Alexander J.; Davies, Melvyn B.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 508, Issue 4, pp.5671-5686</TD>
<TD>2021-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.508.5671L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.508.5138P</TD>
<TD>Real-time discovery of AT2020xnd: a fast, luminous ultraviolet transient with minimal radioactive ejecta</TD>
<TD>Perley, Daniel A.; Ho, Anna Y. Q.; Yao, Yuhan; Fremling, Christoffer; Anderson, Joseph P.; Schulze, Steve; Kumar, Harsh; Anupama, G. C.; Barway, Sudhanshu; Bellm, Eric C.; Bhalerao, Varun; Chen, Ting-Wan; Duev, Dmitry A.; Galbany, Lluís; Graham, Matthew J.; Gromadzki, Mariusz; Gutiérrez, Claudia P.; Ihanec, Nada; Inserra, Cosimo; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Kool, Erik C.; Kulkarni, S. R.; Laher, Russ R.; Masci, Frank J.; Neill, James D.; Nicholl, Matt; Pursiainen, Miika; van Roestel, Joannes; Sharma, Yashvi; Sollerman, Jesper; Walters, Richard; Wiseman, Philip</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 508, Issue 4, pp.5138-5147</TD>
<TD>2021-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.508.5138P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.508.4342P</TD>
<TD>Transitional events in the spectrophotometric regime between stripped envelope and superluminous supernovae</TD>
<TD>Prentice, S. J.; Inserra, C.; Schulze, S.; Nicholl, M.; Mazzali, P. A.; Vergani, S. D.; Galbany, L.; Anderson, J. P.; Ashall, C.; Chen, T. W.; Deckers, M.; Delgado Mancheño, M.; González Díaz, R.; González-Gaitán, S.; Gromadzki, M.; Gutiérrez, C. P.; Harvey, L.; Kozyreva, A.; Magee, M. R.; Maguire, K.; Müller-Bravo, T. E.; Muñoz Torres, S.; Pessi, P. J.; Sollerman, J.; Teffs, J.; Terwel, J. H.; Young, D. R.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 508, Issue 3, pp.4342-4358</TD>
<TD>2021-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.508.4342P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.508.4106E</TD>
<TD>Birth of the ELMs: a ZTF survey for evolved cataclysmic variables turning into extremely low-mass white dwarfs</TD>
<TD>El-Badry, Kareem; Rix, Hans-Walter; Quataert, Eliot; Kupfer, Thomas; Shen, Ken J.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 508, Issue 3, pp.4106-4139</TD>
<TD>2021-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.508.4106E</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.508.3975K</TD>
<TD>Detection of periodic signals in AGN red noise light curves: empirical tests on the Auto-Correlation Function and Phase Dispersion Minimization</TD>
<TD>Krishnan, S.; Markowitz, A. G.; Schwarzenberg-Czerny, A.; Middleton, M. J.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 508, Issue 3, pp.3975-3994</TD>
<TD>2021-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.508.3975K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.508.3820S</TD>
<TD>First tidal disruption events discovered by SRG/eROSITA: X-ray/optical properties and X-ray luminosity function at z &lt; 0.6</TD>
<TD>Sazonov, S.; Gilfanov, M.; Medvedev, P.; Yao, Y.; Khorunzhev, G.; Semena, A.; Sunyaev, R.; Burenin, R.; Lyapin, A.; Meshcheryakov, A.; Uskov, G.; Zaznobin, I.; Postnov, K. A.; Dodin, A. V.; Belinski, A. A.; Cherepashchuk, A. M.; Eselevich, M.; Dodonov, S. N.; Grokhovskaya, A. A.; Kotov, S. S.; Bikmaev, I. F.; Zhuchkov, R. Ya; Gumerov, R. I.; van Velzen, S.; Kulkarni, S.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 508, Issue 3, pp.3820-3847</TD>
<TD>2021-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.508.3820S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.508.3275P</TD>
<TD>TACOS: TESS AM CVn Outbursts Survey</TD>
<TD>Pichardo Marcano, Manuel; Rivera Sandoval, Liliana E.; Maccarone, Thomas J.; Scaringi, Simone</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 508, Issue 3, pp.3275-3289</TD>
<TD>2021-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.508.3275P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.508.2524K</TD>
<TD>Gravitational self-lensing in populations of massive black hole binaries</TD>
<TD>Kelley, Luke Zoltan; D'Orazio, Daniel J.; Di Stefano, Rosanne</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 508, Issue 2, pp.2524-2536</TD>
<TD>2021-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.508.2524K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.508.2386S</TD>
<TD>Simulating highly eccentric common envelope jet supernova impostors</TD>
<TD>Schreier, Ron; Hillel, Shlomi; Shiber, Sagiv; Soker, Noam</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 508, Issue 2, pp.2386-2398</TD>
<TD>2021-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.508.2386S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ExA....52..309M</TD>
<TD>Time domain astronomy with the THESEUS satellite</TD>
<TD>Mereghetti, S.; Balman, S.; Caballero-Garcia, M.; Del Santo, M.; Doroshenko, V.; Erkut, M. H.; Hanlon, L.; Hoeflich, P.; Markowitz, A.; Osborne, J. P.; Pian, E.; Rivera Sandoval, L.; Webb, N.; Amati, L.; Ambrosi, E.; Beardmore, A. P.; Blain, A.; Bozzo, E.; Burderi, L.; Campana, S.; Casella, P.; D'Aí, A.; D'Ammando, F.; De Colle, F.; Della Valle, M.; De Martino, D.; Di Salvo, T.; Doyle, M.; Esposito, P.; Frontera, F.; Gandhi, P.; Ghisellini, G.; Gotz, D.; Grinberg, V.; Guidorzi, C.; Hudec, R.; Iaria, R.; Izzo, L.; Jaisawal, G. K.; Jonker, P. G.; Kong, A. K. H.; Krumpe, M.; Kumar, P.; Manousakis, A.; Marino, A.; Martin-Carrillo, A.; Mignani, R.; Miniutti, G.; Mundell, C. G.; Mukai, K.; Nucita, A. A.; O'Brien, P. T.; Orlandini, M.; Orio, M.; Palazzi, E.; Papitto, A.; Pintore, F.; Piranomonte, S.; Porquet, D.; Ricci, C.; Riggio, A.; Rigoselli, M.; Rodriguez, J.; Saha, T.; Sanna, A.; Santangelo, A.; Saxton, R.; Sidoli, L.; Stiele, H.; Tagliaferri, G.; Tavecchio, F.; Tiengo, A.; Tsygankov, S.; Turriziani, S.; Wijnands, R.; Zane, S.; Zhang, B.</TD>
<TD>Experimental Astronomy, Volume 52, Issue 3, p.309-406</TD>
<TD>2021-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ExA....52..309M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021CQGra..38w5004A</TD>
<TD>Current observations are insufficient to confidently associate the binary black hole merger GW190521 with AGN J124942.3 + 344929</TD>
<TD>Ashton, Gregory; Ackley, Kendall; Hernandez, Ignacio Magaña; Piotrzkowski, Brandon</TD>
<TD>Classical and Quantum Gravity, Volume 38, Issue 23, id.235004, 13 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021CQGra..38w5004A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJS..257...65S</TD>
<TD>A Catalog of 323 Cataclysmic Variables from LAMOST DR6</TD>
<TD>Sun, Yongkang; Cheng, Zhenghao; Ye, Shuo; Ding, Ruobin; Peng, Yijiang; Zhang, Jiawen; Huo, Zhenyan; Cui, Wenyuan; Wang, Xiaofeng; Shi, Jianrong; Lin, Jie; Wu, Chengyuan; Li, Linlin; Feng, Shuai; Yu, Yang; Ma, Xiaoran; Li, Xin; Liu, Cheng; Zhang, Ziping; Shao, Zhenzhen</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 257, Issue 2, id.65, 13 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJS..257...65S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...923L..34B</TD>
<TD>Masses of White Dwarf Binary Companions to Type Ia Supernovae Measured from Runaway Velocities</TD>
<TD>Bauer, Evan B.; Chandra, Vedant; Shen, Ken J.; Hermes, J. J.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 923, Issue 2, id.L34, 7 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...923L..34B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...923L..32D</TD>
<TD>Constraints on the Electromagnetic Counterpart of the Neutron-star-Black-hole Merger GW200115</TD>
<TD>Dichiara, S.; Becerra, R. L.; Chase, E. A.; Troja, E.; Lee, W. H.; Watson, A. M.; Butler, N. R.; O'Connor, B.; Pereyra, M.; López, K. O. C.; Lien, A. Y.; Gottlieb, A.; Kutyrev, A. S.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 923, Issue 2, id.L32, 6 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...923L..32D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...923L...8J</TD>
<TD>Discovery of the Fastest Early Optical Emission from Overluminous SN Ia 2020hvf: A Thermonuclear Explosion within a Dense Circumstellar Environment</TD>
<TD>Jiang, Ji-an; Maeda, Keiichi; Kawabata, Miho; Doi, Mamoru; Shigeyama, Toshikazu; Tanaka, Masaomi; Tominaga, Nozomu; Nomoto, Ken'ichi; Niino, Yuu; Sako, Shigeyuki; Ohsawa, Ryou; Schramm, Malte; Yamanaka, Masayuki; Kobayashi, Naoto; Takahashi, Hidenori; Nakaoka, Tatsuya; Kawabata, Koji S.; Isogai, Keisuke; Aoki, Tsutomu; Kondo, Sohei; Mori, Yuki; Arimatsu, Ko; Kasuga, Toshihiro; Okumura, Shin-ichiro; Urakawa, Seitaro; Reichart, Daniel E.; Taguchi, Kenta; Arima, Noriaki; Beniyama, Jin; Uno, Kohki; Hamada, Taisei</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 923, Issue 1, id.L8, 14 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...923L...8J</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...923L...6K</TD>
<TD>An Isolated White Dwarf with a 70 s Spin Period</TD>
<TD>Kilic, Mukremin; Kosakowski, Alekzander; Moss, Adam G.; Bergeron, P.; Conly, Annamarie A.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 923, Issue 1, id.L6, 6 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...923L...6K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...923..243G</TD>
<TD>Swift/XRT Deep Galactic Plane Survey Discovery of a New Intermediate Polar Cataclysmic Variable, Swift J183920.1-045350</TD>
<TD>Gorgone, Nicholas M.; Woudt, Patrick A.; Buckley, David; Mukai, Koji; Kouveliotou, Chryssa; Huppenkothen, Daniela; Göğüş, Ersin; Bellm, Eric; Linford, Justin D.; van der Horst, Alexander J.; Baring, Matthew G.; Hartmann, Dieter; Barrett, Paul; Cenko, Bradley; Graham, Melissa; Granot, Johnathan; Harrison, Fiona; Kennea, Jamie; O'Connor, Brendan M.; Potter, Stephen; Stern, Daniel; Slane, Patrick; Wijers, Ralph</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 923, Issue 2, id.243, 13 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...923..243G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...923..226Y</TD>
<TD>LTD064402+245919: A Subgiant with a 1-3 M &lt;SUB&gt;⊙&lt;/SUB&gt; Undetected Companion Identified from LAMOST-TD Data</TD>
<TD>Yang, Fan; Zhang, Bo; Long, Richard J.; Lu, You-Jun; Shan, Su-Su; Wei, Xing; Fu, Jian-Ning; Zhang, Xian-Fei; Zhao, Zhi-Chao; Bai, Yu; Yi, Tuan; Zheng, Ling-Lin; Zhou, Ze-Ming; Liu, Ji-Feng</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 923, Issue 2, id.226, 8 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...923..226Y</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...923..173P</TD>
<TD>Supercritical Accretion of Stellar-mass Compact Objects in Active Galactic Nuclei</TD>
<TD>Pan, Zhen; Yang, Huan</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 923, Issue 2, id.173, 14 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...923..173P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...923..171P</TD>
<TD>V899 Mon: A Peculiar Eruptive Young Star Close to the End of Its Outburst</TD>
<TD>Park, Sunkyung; Kóspál, Ágnes; Cruz-Sáenz de Miera, Fernando; Siwak, Michał; Dróżdż, Marek; Ignácz, Bernadett; Jaffe, Daniel T.; Könyves-Tóth, Réka; Kriskovics, Levente; Lee, Jae-Joon; Lee, Jeong-Eun; Mace, Gregory N.; Ogłoza, Waldemar; Pál, András; Potter, Stephen B.; Szabó, Zsófia Marianna; Sefako, Ramotholo; Worters, Hannah L.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 923, Issue 2, id.171, 25 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...923..171P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...923..167W</TD>
<TD>SN 2018agk: A Prototypical Type Ia Supernova with a Smooth Power-law Rise in Kepler (K2)</TD>
<TD>Wang, Qinan; Rest, Armin; Zenati, Yossef; Ridden-Harper, Ryan; Dimitriadis, Georgios; Narayan, Gautham; Villar, V. Ashley; Magee, Mark R.; Foley, Ryan J.; Shaya, Edward J.; Garnavich, Peter; Wang, Lifan; Hu, Lei; Bódi, Attila; Armstrong, Patrick; Auchettl, Katie; Barclay, Thomas; Barentsen, Geert; Bognár, Zsófia; Brimacombe, Joseph; Bulger, Joanna; Burke, Jamison; Challis, Peter; Chambers, Kenneth; Coulter, David A.; Csörnyei, Géza; Cseh, Borbála; Deckers, Maxime; Dotson, Jessie L.; Galbany, Lluís; González-Gaitán, Santiago; Gromadzki, Mariusz; Gully-Santiago, Michael; Hanyecz, Ottó; Hedges, Christina; Hiramatsu, Daichi; Hosseinzadeh, Griffin; Howell, D. Andrew; Howell, Steve B.; Huber, Mark E.; Jha, Saurabh W.; Jones, David O.; Könyves-Tóth, Réka; Kalup, Csilla; Kilpatrick, Charles D.; Kriskovics, Levente; Li, Wenxiong; Lowe, Thomas B.; Margheim, Steven; McCully, Curtis; Mitra, Ayan; Muñoz, Jose A.; Nicholl, Matt; Nordin, Jakob; Pál, András; Pan, Yen-Chen; Piro, Anthony L.; Rest, Sofia; Rino-Silvestre, João; Rojas-Bravo, César; Sárneczky, Krisztián; Siebert, Matthew R.; Smartt, Stephen J.; Smith, Ken; Sódor, Ádám; Stritzinger, Maximilian D.; Szabó, Róbert; Szakáts, Róbert; Tucker, Brad E.; Vinkó, József; Wang, Xiaofeng; Wheeler, J. Craig; Young, David R.; Zenteno, Alfredo; Zhang, KaiCheng; Zsidi, Gabriella</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 923, Issue 2, id.167, 22 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...923..167W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...923..100M</TD>
<TD>Transients from the Cataclysmic Deaths of Cataclysmic Variables</TD>
<TD>Metzger, Brian D.; Zenati, Yossef; Chomiuk, Laura; Shen, Ken J.; Strader, Jay</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 923, Issue 1, id.100, 18 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...923..100M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...923...86C</TD>
<TD>Local Environments of Low-redshift Supernovae</TD>
<TD>Cronin, Serena A.; Utomo, Dyas; Leroy, Adam K.; Behrens, Erica A.; Chastenet, Jérémy; Holland-Ashford, Tyler; Koch, Eric W.; Lopez, Laura A.; Sandstrom, Karin M.; Williams, Thomas G.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 923, Issue 1, id.86, 22 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...923...86C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...922L..42D</TD>
<TD>The Remarkable Spin-down and Ultrafast Outflows of the Highly Pulsed Supersoft Source of Nova Herculis 2021</TD>
<TD>Drake, Jeremy J.; Ness, Jan-Uwe; Page, Kim L.; Luna, G. J. M.; Beardmore, Andrew P.; Orio, Marina; Osborne, Julian P.; Mróz, Przemek; Starrfield, Sumner; Banerjee, Dipankar P. K.; Balman, Solen; Darnley, M. J.; Bhargava, Y.; Dewangan, G. C.; Singh, K. P.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 922, Issue 2, id.L42, 9 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...922L..42D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...922L..34T</TD>
<TD>AT 2018lqh: Black Hole Born from a Rotating Star?</TD>
<TD>Tsuna, Daichi; Kashiyama, Kazumi; Shigeyama, Toshikazu</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 922, Issue 2, id.L34, 6 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...922L..34T</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...922..269R</TD>
<TD>The Challenges Ahead for Multimessenger Analyses of Gravitational Waves and Kilonova: A Case Study on GW190425</TD>
<TD>Raaijmakers, Geert; Nissanke, Samaya; Foucart, Francois; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Bulla, Mattia; Fernández, Rodrigo; Henkel, Amelia; Hinderer, Tanja; Hotokezaka, Kenta; Lukošiūtė, Kamilė; Venumadhav, Tejaswi; Antier, Sarah; Coughlin, Michael W.; Dietrich, Tim; Edwards, Thomas D. P.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 922, Issue 2, id.269, 17 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...922..269R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...922..248X</TD>
<TD>Long-term Variability of the Composite Galaxy SDSS J103911-000057: A True Type-2 AGN Candidate</TD>
<TD>XueGuang, Zhang; YingFei, Zhang; PeiZhen, Cheng; BaoHan, Wang; Yi-Li, Lv; HaiChao, Yu</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 922, Issue 2, id.248, 10 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...922..248X</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...922..247O</TD>
<TD>AT 2018lqh and the Nature of the Emerging Population of Day-scale Duration Optical Transients</TD>
<TD>Ofek, E. O.; Adams, S. M.; Waxman, E.; Sharon, A.; Kushnir, D.; Horesh, A.; Ho, A.; Kasliwal, M. M.; Yaron, O.; Gal-Yam, A.; Kulkarni, S. R.; Bellm, E.; Masci, F.; Shupe, D.; Dekany, R.; Graham, M.; Riddle, R.; Duev, D.; Andreoni, I.; Mahabal, A.; Drake, A.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 922, Issue 2, id.247, 10 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...922..247O</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...922..245B</TD>
<TD>Phases of Mass Transfer from Hot Subdwarfs to White Dwarf Companions and Their Photometric Properties</TD>
<TD>Bauer, Evan B.; Kupfer, Thomas</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 922, Issue 2, id.245, 13 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...922..245B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...922..205A</TD>
<TD>Carnegie Supernova Project: The First Homogeneous Sample of Super-Chandrasekhar-mass/2003fg-like Type Ia Supernovae</TD>
<TD>Ashall, C.; Lu, J.; Hsiao, E. Y.; Hoeflich, P.; Phillips, M. M.; Galbany, L.; Burns, C. R.; Contreras, C.; Krisciunas, K.; Morrell, N.; Stritzinger, M. D.; Suntzeff, N. B.; Taddia, F.; Anais, J.; Baron, E.; Brown, P. J.; Busta, L.; Campillay, A.; Castellón, S.; Corco, C.; Davis, S.; Folatelli, G.; Förster, F.; Freedman, W. L.; Gonzaléz, C.; Hamuy, M.; Holmbo, S.; Kirshner, R. P.; Kumar, S.; Marion, G. H.; Mazzali, P.; Morokuma, T.; Nugent, P. E.; Persson, S. E.; Piro, A. L.; Roth, M.; Salgado, F.; Sand, D. J.; Seron, J.; Shahbandeh, M.; Shappee, B. J.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 922, Issue 2, id.205, 32 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...922..205A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...922..141O</TD>
<TD>Are Stripped Envelope Supernovae Really Deficient in &lt;SUP&gt;56&lt;/SUP&gt;Ni?</TD>
<TD>Ouchi, Ryoma; Maeda, Keiichi; Anderson, Joseph P.; Sawada, Ryo</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 922, Issue 2, id.141, 15 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...922..141O</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021AJ....162..299P</TD>
<TD>Mysterious Dust-emitting Object Orbiting TIC 400799224</TD>
<TD>Powell, Brian P.; Kostov, Veselin B.; Rappaport, Saul A.; Tokovinin, Andrei; Shporer, Avi; Collins, Karen A.; Corbett, Hank; Borkovits, Tamás; Gary, Bruce L.; Chiang, Eugene; Rodriguez, Joseph E.; Law, Nicholas M.; Barclay, Thomas; Gagliano, Robert; Vanderburg, Andrew; Olmschenk, Greg; Kruse, Ethan; Schlieder, Joshua E.; Soto, Alan Vasquez; Goeke, Erin; Jacobs, Thomas L.; Kristiansen, Martti H.; LaCourse, Daryll M.; Omohundro, Mark; Schwengeler, Hans M.; Terentev, Ivan A.; Schmitt, Allan R.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 162, Issue 6, id.299, 19 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021AJ....162..299P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021AJ....162..296X</TD>
<TD>Gemini/GMOS Transmission Spectroscopy of the Grazing Planet Candidate WD 1856+534 b</TD>
<TD>Xu, Siyi; Diamond-Lowe, Hannah; MacDonald, Ryan J.; Vanderburg, Andrew; Blouin, Simon; Dufour, P.; Gao, Peter; Kreidberg, Laura; Leggett, S. K.; Mann, Andrew W.; Morley, Caroline V.; Stephens, Andrew W.; O'Connor, Christopher E.; Thao, Pa Chia; Lewis, Nikole K.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 162, Issue 6, id.296, 15 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021AJ....162..296X</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021AJ....162..247K</TD>
<TD>Prospects for Detecting Exoplanets around Double White Dwarfs with LISA and Taiji</TD>
<TD>Kang, Yacheng; Liu, Chang; Shao, Lijing</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 162, Issue 6, id.247, 12 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021AJ....162..247K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021AJ....162..244F</TD>
<TD>Exploring the Solar System with the NOIRLab Source Catalog I: Detecting Objects with CANFind</TD>
<TD>Fasbender, Katie M.; Nidever, David L.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 162, Issue 6, id.244, 14 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021AJ....162..244F</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021AJ....162..231C</TD>
<TD>Alert Classification for the ALeRCE Broker System: The Real-time Stamp Classifier</TD>
<TD>Carrasco-Davis, R.; Reyes, E.; Valenzuela, C.; Förster, F.; Estévez, P. A.; Pignata, G.; Bauer, F. E.; Reyes, I.; Sánchez-Sáez, P.; Cabrera-Vives, G.; Eyheramendy, S.; Catelan, M.; Arredondo, J.; Castillo-Navarrete, E.; Rodríguez-Mancini, D.; Ruz-Mieres, D.; Moya, A.; Sabatini-Gacitúa, L.; Sepúlveda-Cobo, C.; Mahabal, A. A.; Silva-Farfán, J.; Camacho-Iñiguez, E.; Galbany, L.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 162, Issue 6, id.231, 27 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021AJ....162..231C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021A&amp;ARv..29....9S</TD>
<TD>A buyer's guide to the Hubble constant</TD>
<TD>Shah, Paul; Lemos, Pablo; Lahav, Ofer</TD>
<TD>The Astronomy and Astrophysics Review, Volume 29, Issue 1, article id.9</TD>
<TD>2021-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021A&amp;ARv..29....9S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021A&amp;ARv..29....2P</TD>
<TD>Star formation and nuclear activity in luminous infrared galaxies: an infrared through radio review</TD>
<TD>Pérez-Torres, Miguel; Mattila, Seppo; Alonso-Herrero, Almudena; Aalto, Susanne; Efstathiou, Andreas</TD>
<TD>The Astronomy and Astrophysics Review, Volume 29, Issue 1, article id.2</TD>
<TD>2021-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021A&amp;ARv..29....2P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021A&amp;A...656A.132S</TD>
<TD>SRG X-ray orbital observatory. Its telescopes and first scientific results</TD>
<TD>Sunyaev, R.; Arefiev, V.; Babyshkin, V.; Bogomolov, A.; Borisov, K.; Buntov, M.; Brunner, H.; Burenin, R.; Churazov, E.; Coutinho, D.; Eder, J.; Eismont, N.; Freyberg, M.; Gilfanov, M.; Gureyev, P.; Hasinger, G.; Khabibullin, I.; Kolmykov, V.; Komovkin, S.; Krivonos, R.; Lapshov, I.; Levin, V.; Lomakin, I.; Lutovinov, A.; Medvedev, P.; Merloni, A.; Mernik, T.; Mikhailov, E.; Molodtsov, V.; Mzhelsky, P.; Müller, S.; Nandra, K.; Nazarov, V.; Pavlinsky, M.; Poghodin, A.; Predehl, P.; Robrade, J.; Sazonov, S.; Scheuerle, H.; Shirshakov, A.; Tkachenko, A.; Voron, V.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 656, id.A132, 29 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021A&amp;A...656A.132S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021A&amp;A...656A.125F</TD>
<TD>A case study of ACV variables discovered in the Zwicky Transient Facility survey</TD>
<TD>Faltová, N.; Kallová, K.; Prišegen, M.; Staněk, P.; Supíková, J.; Xia, C.; Bernhard, K.; Hümmerich, S.; Paunzen, E.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 656, id.A125, 17 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021A&amp;A...656A.125F</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021A&amp;A...656A..77O</TD>
<TD>Mass limits of the extremely fast-spinning white dwarf CTCV J2056-3014</TD>
<TD>Otoniel, Edson; Coelho, Jaziel G.; Nunes, Sílvia P.; Malheiro, Manuel; Weber, Fridolin</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 656, id.A77, 5 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021A&amp;A...656A..77O</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021A&amp;A...656A..58L</TD>
<TD>Different to the core: The pre-supernova structures of massive single and binary-stripped stars</TD>
<TD>Laplace, E.; Justham, S.; Renzo, M.; Götberg, Y.; Farmer, R.; Vartanyan, D.; de Mink, S. E.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 656, id.A58, 29 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021A&amp;A...656A..58L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021A&amp;A...656A..47P</TD>
<TD>Contribution of flares from tidal disruptions of stars to high-redshift AGN</TD>
<TD>Padmanabhan, Hamsa; Loeb, Abraham</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 656, id.A47, 6 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021A&amp;A...656A..47P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021RAA....21..227Z</TD>
<TD>Variable stars in the 50BiN open cluster survey. II. NGC 869</TD>
<TD>Zhuo, Jing; Deng, Li-Cai; Wang, Kun; Luo, Chang-Qing; Zhang, Xiao-Bin; Li, Cheng-Yuan; Liu, Chao; Chen, Xiao-Dian</TD>
<TD>Research in Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 21, Issue 9, id.227, 7 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021RAA....21..227Z</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021PhRvD.104j3001C</TD>
<TD>Searching for axionlike particles from core-collapse supernovae with Fermi LAT's low-energy technique</TD>
<TD>Crnogorčević, Milena; Caputo, Regina; Meyer, Manuel; Omodei, Nicola; Gustafsson, Michael</TD>
<TD>Physical Review D, Volume 104, Issue 10, article id.103001</TD>
<TD>2021-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021PhRvD.104j3001C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021P&amp;SS..20805341M</TD>
<TD>A colour portrait of the interstellar comet 2I/Borisov</TD>
<TD>Mazzotta Epifani, E.; Dotto, E.; Perna, D.; Ieva, S.; Giunta, A.; Palumbo, P.; Micheli, M.</TD>
<TD>Planetary and Space Science, Volume 208, article id. 105341.</TD>
<TD>2021-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021P&amp;SS..20805341M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021OptLT.14307314R</TD>
<TD>Application of the principal components analysis technique to optical fiber sensors for acetone detection</TD>
<TD>Rodríguez-Garciapiña, J. L.; Beltrán-Pérez, G.; Castillo-Mixcóatl, J.; Muñoz-Aguirre, S.</TD>
<TD>Optics and Laser Technology, Volume 143, article id. 107314.</TD>
<TD>2021-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021OptLT.14307314R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021OJAp....4E..14D</TD>
<TD>Ultra Fast Astronomy: Optimized Detection of Multimessenger Transients</TD>
<TD>Denissenya, Mikhail; Linder, Eric V.</TD>
<TD>The Open Journal of Astrophysics, vol. 4, issue 1, id. 14</TD>
<TD>2021-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021OJAp....4E..14D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.508..803B</TD>
<TD>Spectral separation of the stochastic gravitational-wave background for LISA in the context of a modulated Galactic foreground</TD>
<TD>Boileau, Guillaume; Lamberts, Astrid; Christensen, Nelson; Cornish, Neil J.; Meyer, Renate</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 508, Issue 1, pp.803-826</TD>
<TD>2021-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.508..803B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.508..560K</TD>
<TD>Erratum: Year 1 of the ZTF high-cadence Galactic plane survey: strategy, goals, and early results on new single-mode hot subdwarf B-star pulsators</TD>
<TD>Kupfer, Thomas; Prince, Thomas A.; van Roestel, Jan; Bellm, Eric C.; Bildsten, Lars; Coughlin, Michael W.; Drake, Andrew J.; Graham, Matthew J.; Klein, Courtney; Kulkarni, Shrinivas R.; Masci, Frank J.; Walters, Richard; Andreoni, Igor; Biswas, Rahul; Bradshaw, Corey; Duev, Dmitry A.; Dekany, Richard; Guidry, Joseph A.; Hermes, J. J.; Laher, Russ R.; Riddle, Reed</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 508, Issue 1, pp.560-560</TD>
<TD>2021-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.508..560K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.507.5463M</TD>
<TD>Searching for Fermi GRB optical counterparts with the prototype Gravitational-wave Optical Transient Observer (GOTO)</TD>
<TD>Mong, Y. -L.; Ackley, K.; Galloway, D. K.; Dyer, M.; Cutter, R.; Brown, M. J. I.; Lyman, J.; Ulaczyk, K.; Steeghs, D.; Dhillon, V.; O'Brien, P.; Ramsay, G.; Noysena, K.; Kotak, R.; Breton, R.; Nuttall, L.; Pallé, E.; Pollacco, D.; Thrane, E.; Awiphan, S.; Burhanudin, U.; Chote, P.; Chrimes, A.; Daw, E.; Duffy, C.; Eyles-Ferris, R.; Gompertz, B.; Heikkilä, T.; Irawati, P.; Kennedy, M.; Killestein, T.; Levan, A.; Littlefair, S.; Makrygianni, L.; Marsh, T.; Mata-Sanchez, D.; Mattila, S.; Maund, J.; McCormac, J.; Mkrtichian, D.; Mullaney, J.; Rol, E.; Sawangwit, U.; Stanway, E.; Starling, R.; Strøm, P.; Tooke, S.; Wiersema, K.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 507, Issue 4, pp.5463-5476</TD>
<TD>2021-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.507.5463M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.507.4983S</TD>
<TD>Deep co-added sky from Catalina Sky Survey images</TD>
<TD>Singhal, Akshat; Bhalerao, Varun; Mahabal, Ashish A.; Vaghmare, Kaustubh; Jagade, Santosh; Kulkarni, Sumeet; Vibhute, Ajay; Kembhavi, Ajit K.; Drake, Andrew J.; Djorgovski, S. George; Graham, Matthew J.; Donalek, Ciro; Christensen, Eric; Larson, Stephen; Beshore, Edward C.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 507, Issue 4, pp.4983-4996</TD>
<TD>2021-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.507.4983S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.507.4638C</TD>
<TD>Very Large Array imaging rules out precessing radio jets in three DES-SDSS-selected candidate periodic quasars</TD>
<TD>Chen, Yu-Ching; Liu, Xin; Liao, Wei-Ting; Guo, Hengxiao</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 507, Issue 3, pp.4638-4645</TD>
<TD>2021-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.507.4638C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApSS..56550528X</TD>
<TD>An instantaneous metal organic framework to prepare ultra-high pore volume porous carbon for lithium ion capacitors</TD>
<TD>Xu, Ziqiang; Li, Junxiang; Li, Xinran; Chen, Zhi; Chen, Cheng; Ali Shah, Syed Abbas; Wu, Mengqiang</TD>
<TD>Applied Surface Science, Volume 565, article id. 150528.</TD>
<TD>2021-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApSS..56550528X</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...922L...9H</TD>
<TD>Physical Characterization of Main-belt Comet (248370) 2005 QN&lt;SUB&gt;173&lt;/SUB&gt;</TD>
<TD>Hsieh, Henry H.; Chandler, Colin O.; Denneau, Larry; Fitzsimmons, Alan; Erasmus, Nicolas; Kelley, Michael S. P.; Knight, Matthew M.; Lister, Tim A.; Pittichová, Jana; Sheppard, Scott S.; Thirouin, Audrey; Trujillo, Chadwick A.; Usher, Helen; Gomez, Edward; Chatelain, Joey; Greenstreet, Sarah; Angel, Tony; Miles, Richard; Roche, Paul; Wooding, Ben</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 922, Issue 1, id.L9, 10 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...922L...9H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...922L...8C</TD>
<TD>Recurrent Activity from Active Asteroid (248370) 2005 QN&lt;SUB&gt;173&lt;/SUB&gt;: A Main-belt Comet</TD>
<TD>Chandler, Colin Orion; Trujillo, Chadwick A.; Hsieh, Henry H.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 922, Issue 1, id.L8, 10 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...922L...8C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...922...33R</TD>
<TD>Unexpected Short-period Variability in Dwarf Carbon Stars from the Zwicky Transient Facility</TD>
<TD>Roulston, Benjamin R.; Green, Paul J.; Toonen, Silvia; Hermes, J. J.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 922, Issue 1, id.33, 16 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...922...33R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...922...21S</TD>
<TD>Circumstellar Medium Constraints on the Environment of Two Nearby Type Ia Supernovae: SN 2017cbv and SN 2020nlb</TD>
<TD>Sand, D. J.; Sarbadhicary, S. K.; Pellegrino, C.; Misra, K.; Dastidar, R.; Brown, P. J.; Itagaki, K.; Valenti, S.; Swift, Jonathan J.; Andrews, J. E.; Bostroem, K. A.; Burke, J.; Chomiuk, L.; Dong, Y.; Galbany, L.; Graham, M. L.; Hiramatsu, D.; Howell, D. A.; Hsiao, E. Y.; Janzen, D.; Jencson, J. E.; Lundquist, M. J.; McCully, C.; Reichart, D.; Smith, Nathan; Wang, Lingzhi; Wyatt, S.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 922, Issue 1, id.21, 14 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...922...21S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...922....5L</TD>
<TD>Discovery of a 310 Day Period from the Enshrouded Massive System NaSt1 (WR 122)</TD>
<TD>Lau, Ryan M.; Tinyanont, Samaporn; Hankins, Matthew J.; Ashley, Michael C. B.; De, Kishalay; Filippenko, Alexei V.; Hillenbrand, Lynne A.; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Mauerhan, Jon C.; Moffat, Anthony F. J.; Moore, Anna M.; Smith, Nathan; Soon, Jamie; Soria, Roberto; Travouillon, Tony; van der Hucht, Karel A.; Williams, Peredur M.; Zheng, WeiKang</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 922, Issue 1, id.5, 15 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...922....5L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...921L...6K</TD>
<TD>Faintest of Them All: ZTF 21aaoryiz/SN 2021fcg-Discovery of an Extremely Low Luminosity Type Iax Supernova</TD>
<TD>Karambelkar, Viraj R.; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Maguire, Kate; Anand, Shreya G.; Andreoni, Igor; De, Kishalay; Drake, Andrew; Duev, Dmitry A.; Graham, Matthew J.; Kool, Erik C.; Laher, Russ R.; Magee, Mark R.; Mahabal, Ashish A.; Medford, Michael S.; Perley, Daniel; Rigault, Mickael; Rusholme, Ben; Schulze, Steve; Sharma, Yashvi; Sollerman, Jesper; Tzanidakis, Anastasios; Walters, Richard; Yao, Yuhan</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 921, Issue 1, id.L6, 8 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...921L...6K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...921..165S</TD>
<TD>Photometric Variability of the Pre-main-sequence Stars toward the Sh 2-190 Region</TD>
<TD>Sinha, Tirthendu; Sharma, Saurabh; Panwar, Neelam; Matsunaga, N.; Ogura, K.; Kobayashi, N.; Yadav, R. K.; Ghosh, A.; Pandey, R.; Bisht, P. S.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 921, Issue 2, id.165, 16 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...921..165S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...921..156Z</TD>
<TD>No Detectable Kilonova Counterpart is Expected for O3 Neutron Star-Black Hole Candidates</TD>
<TD>Zhu, Jin-Ping; Wu, Shichao; Yang, Yuan-Pei; Zhang, Bing; Yu, Yun-Wei; Gao, He; Cao, Zhoujian; Liu, Liang-Duan</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 921, Issue 2, id.156, 9 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...921..156Z</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...921..151L</TD>
<TD>A Pixon-based Method for Reverberation-mapping Analysis in Active Galactic Nuclei</TD>
<TD>Li, Yan-Rong; Xiao, Ming; Wang, Jian-Min</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 921, Issue 2, id.151, 12 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...921..151L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...921..145S</TD>
<TD>Exploring the Stellar Rotation of Early-type Stars in the LAMOST Medium-resolution Survey. II. Statistics</TD>
<TD>Sun, Weijia; Duan, Xiao-Wei; Deng, Licai; de Grijs, Richard</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 921, Issue 2, id.145, 13 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...921..145S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...921..140S</TD>
<TD>Ross 19B: An Extremely Cold Companion Discovered via the Backyard Worlds: Planet 9 Citizen Science Project</TD>
<TD>Schneider, Adam C.; Meisner, Aaron M.; Gagné, Jonathan; Faherty, Jacqueline K.; Marocco, Federico; Burgasser, Adam J.; Kirkpatrick, J. Davy; Kuchner, Marc J.; Gramaize, Léopold; Rothermich, Austin; Brooks, Hunter; Vrba, Frederick J.; Bardalez Gagliuffi, Daniella; Caselden, Dan; Cushing, Michael C.; Gelino, Christopher R.; Line, Michael R.; Casewell, Sarah L.; Debes, John H.; Aganze, Christian; Ayala, Andrew; Gerasimov, Roman; Gonzales, Eileen C.; Hsu, Chih-Chun; Kiman, Rocio; Popinchalk, Mark; Theissen, Christopher; Backyard Worlds: Planet 9 Collaboration</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 921, Issue 2, id.140, 13 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...921..140S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...921...42S</TD>
<TD>Gaia GraL: Gaia DR2 Gravitational Lens Systems. VI. Spectroscopic Confirmation and Modeling of Quadruply Imaged Lensed Quasars</TD>
<TD>Stern, D.; Djorgovski, S. G.; Krone-Martins, A.; Sluse, D.; Delchambre, L.; Ducourant, C.; Teixeira, R.; Surdej, J.; Boehm, C.; den Brok, J.; Dobie, D.; Drake, A.; Galluccio, L.; Graham, M. J.; Jalan, P.; Klüter, J.; Le Campion, J. -F.; Mahabal, A.; Mignard, F.; Murphy, T.; Nierenberg, A.; Scarano, S., Jr.; Simon, J.; Slezak, E.; Spindola-Duarte, C.; Wambsganss, J.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 921, Issue 1, id.42, 16 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...921...42S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021Ap&amp;SS.366..111K</TD>
<TD>Discovery of deep eclipses in the cataclysmic variable ZTF17aaaeefu (2MASS J00594349+6454419)</TD>
<TD>Kozhevnikov, V. P.</TD>
<TD>Astrophysics and Space Science, Volume 366, Issue 11, article id.111</TD>
<TD>2021-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021Ap&amp;SS.366..111K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021AcA....71..205P</TD>
<TD>Classical Cepheids in the Milky Way</TD>
<TD>Pietrukowicz, P.; Soszyński, I.; Udalski, A.</TD>
<TD>Acta Astronomica, vol 71, no 3, p. 205-222</TD>
<TD>2021-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021AcA....71..205P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021AcA....71..189S</TD>
<TD>Over 24 000 δ Scuti Stars in the Galactic Bulge and Disk from the OGLE Survey</TD>
<TD>Soszyński, I.; Pietrukowicz, P.; Skowron, J.; Udalski, A.; Szymański, M. K.; Skowron, D. M.; Poleski, R.; Kozłowski, S.; Mróz, P.; Ulaczyk, K.; Rybicki, K.; Iwanek, P.; Wrona, M.; Gromadzki, M.</TD>
<TD>Acta Astronomica, vol 71, no 3, p. 189-204</TD>
<TD>2021-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021AcA....71..189S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021AJ....162..206S</TD>
<TD>Searching for Changing-state AGNs in Massive Data Sets. I. Applying Deep Learning and Anomaly-detection Techniques to Find AGNs with Anomalous Variability Behaviors</TD>
<TD>Sánchez-Sáez, P.; Lira, H.; Martí, L.; Sánchez-Pi, N.; Arredondo, J.; Bauer, F. E.; Bayo, A.; Cabrera-Vives, G.; Donoso-Oliva, C.; Estévez, P. A.; Eyheramendy, S.; Förster, F.; Hernández-García, L.; Arancibia, A. M. Muñoz; Pérez-Carrasco, M.; Sepúlveda, M.; Vergara, J. R.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 162, Issue 5, id.206, 16 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021AJ....162..206S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021AJ....162..205H</TD>
<TD>TESS and ZTF Observations of an Eclipsing Z Cam-type Dwarf Nova IPHAS J051814.34+294113.2</TD>
<TD>Han, Z. -T.; Soonthornthum, B.; Qian, S. -B.; Fang, X. -H.; Wang, Q. -S.; Sarotsakulchai, T.; Zhu, L. -Y.; Dong, A. -J.; Zhi, Q. -J.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 162, Issue 5, id.205, 11 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021AJ....162..205H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021A&amp;A...655A.105S</TD>
<TD>The Type II supernova SN 2020jfo in M 61, implications for progenitor system, and explosion dynamics</TD>
<TD>Sollerman, J.; Yang, S.; Schulze, S.; Strotjohann, N. L.; Jerkstrand, A.; Van Dyk, S. D.; Kool, E. C.; Barbarino, C.; Brink, T. G.; Bruch, R.; De, K.; Filippenko, A. V.; Fremling, C.; Patra, K. C.; Perley, D.; Yan, L.; Yang, Y.; Andreoni, I.; Campbell, R.; Coughlin, M.; Kasliwal, M.; Kim, Y. -L.; Rigault, M.; Shin, K.; Tzanidakis, A.; Ashley, M. C. B.; Moore, A. M.; Travouillon, T.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 655, id.A105, 20 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021A&amp;A...655A.105S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021A&amp;A...655A..90Y</TD>
<TD>A low-energy explosion yields the underluminous Type IIP SN 2020cxd</TD>
<TD>Yang, S.; Sollerman, J.; Strotjohann, N. L.; Schulze, S.; Lunnan, R.; Kool, E.; Fremling, C.; Perley, D.; Ofek, E.; Schweyer, T.; Bellm, E. C.; Kasliwal, M. M.; Masci, F. J.; Rigault, M.; Yang, Y.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 655, id.A90, 19 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021A&amp;A...655A..90Y</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021Univ....7..397S</TD>
<TD>Multimessenger Astronomy with Neutrinos</TD>
<TD>Salesa Greus, Francisco; Sánchez Losa, Agustín</TD>
<TD>Universe, vol. 7, issue 11, p. 397</TD>
<TD>2021-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021Univ....7..397S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021PSJ.....2..193P</TD>
<TD>Threat from Within: Excitation of Venus's Co-orbital Asteroids to Earth-crossing Orbits</TD>
<TD>Pokorný, Petr; Kuchner, Marc</TD>
<TD>The Planetary Science Journal, Volume 2, Issue 5, id.193, 13 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021PSJ.....2..193P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021PASJ...73.1375K</TD>
<TD>New candidates for AM Canum Venaticorum stars among ASAS-SN transients</TD>
<TD>Kato, Taichi; Kojiguchi, Naoto</TD>
<TD>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Volume 73, Issue 5, pp.1375-1381</TD>
<TD>2021-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021PASJ...73.1375K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021Obs...141..223L</TD>
<TD>A period study of the W Ursae Majoris-type eclipsing binary GSC 03465-00810</TD>
<TD>Lloyd, C.; Miller, I.; Janzen, D.; Ogmen, Y.</TD>
<TD>The Observatory, Vol. 141, pp. 223-234</TD>
<TD>2021-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021Obs...141..223L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021Obs...141..219.</TD>
<TD>2021 March Meeting of the RAS</TD>
<TD />
<TD>The Observatory, Vol. 141, pp. 219-222</TD>
<TD>2021-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021Obs...141..219.</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021Obs...141..217.</TD>
<TD>2021 February Meeting of the RAS</TD>
<TD />
<TD>The Observatory, Vol. 141, pp. 217-219</TD>
<TD>2021-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021Obs...141..217.</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.507.1401B</TD>
<TD>DDOTI observations of gravitational-wave sources discovered in O3</TD>
<TD>Becerra, R. L.; Dichiara, S.; Watson, A. M.; Troja, E.; Butler, N. R.; Pereyra, M.; Moreno Méndez, E.; De Colle, F.; Lee, W. H.; Kutyrev, A. S.; López, K. O. C.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 507, Issue 1, pp.1401-1420</TD>
<TD>2021-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.507.1401B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.507.1296O</TD>
<TD>Swift/UVOT follow-up of gravitational wave alerts in the O3 era</TD>
<TD>Oates, S. R.; Marshall, F. E.; Breeveld, A. A.; Kuin, N. P. M.; Brown, P. J.; De Pasquale, M.; Evans, P. A.; Fenney, A. J.; Gronwall, C.; Kennea, J. A.; Klingler, N. J.; Page, M. J.; Siegel, M. H.; Tohuvavohu, A.; Ambrosi, E.; Barthelmy, S. D.; Beardmore, A. P.; Bernardini, M. G.; Campana, S.; Caputo, R.; Cenko, S. B.; Cusumano, G.; D'Aì, A.; D'Avanzo, P.; D'Elia, V.; Giommi, P.; Hartmann, D. H.; Krimm, H. A.; Laha, S.; Malesani, D. B.; Melandri, A.; Nousek, J. A.; O'Brien, P. T.; Osborne, J. P.; Pagani, C.; Page, K. L.; Palmer, D. M.; Perri, M.; Racusin, J. L.; Sakamoto, T.; Sbarufatti, B.; Schlieder, J. E.; Tagliaferri, G.; Troja, E.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 507, Issue 1, pp.1296-1317</TD>
<TD>2021-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.507.1296O</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.507..621B</TD>
<TD>Binary evolution pathways of blue large-amplitude pulsators</TD>
<TD>Byrne, C. M.; Stanway, E. R.; Eldridge, J. J.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 507, Issue 1, pp.621-631</TD>
<TD>2021-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.507..621B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.507..385H</TD>
<TD>Simulating a stellar contact binary merger - I. Stellar models</TD>
<TD>Hatfull, Roger W. M.; Ivanova, Natalia; Lombardi, James C.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 507, Issue 1, pp.385-397</TD>
<TD>2021-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.507..385H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.507..374W</TD>
<TD>Predicting the self-lensing population in optical surveys</TD>
<TD>Wiktorowicz, Grzegorz; Middleton, Matthew; Khan, Norman; Ingram, Adam; Gandhi, Poshak; Dickinson, Hugh</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 507, Issue 1, pp.374-384</TD>
<TD>2021-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.507..374W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.507..350D</TD>
<TD>HiPERCAM: a quintuple-beam, high-speed optical imager on the 10.4-m Gran Telescopio Canarias</TD>
<TD>Dhillon, V. S.; Bezawada, N.; Black, M.; Dixon, S. D.; Gamble, T.; Gao, X.; Henry, D. M.; Kerry, P.; Littlefair, S. P.; Lunney, D. W.; Marsh, T. R.; Miller, C.; Parsons, S. G.; Ashley, R. P.; Breedt, E.; Brown, A.; Dyer, M. J.; Green, M. J.; Pelisoli, I.; Sahman, D. I.; Wild, J.; Ives, D. J.; Mehrgan, L.; Stegmeier, J.; Dubbeldam, C. M.; Morris, T. J.; Osborn, J.; Wilson, R. W.; Casares, J.; Muñoz-Darias, T.; Pallé, E.; Rodríguez-Gil, P.; Shahbaz, T.; Torres, M. A. P.; de Ugarte Postigo, A.; Cabrera-Lavers, A.; Corradi, R. L. M.; Domínguez, R. D.; García-Alvarez, D.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 507, Issue 1, pp.350-366</TD>
<TD>2021-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.507..350D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.506.5989F</TD>
<TD>A survey for variable young stars with small telescopes - IV. Rotation periods of YSOs in IC 5070</TD>
<TD>Froebrich, Dirk; Derezea, Efthymia; Scholz, Aleks; Eislöffel, Jochen; Vanaverbeke, Siegfried; Kume, Alfred; Herbert, Carys; Campbell-White, Justyn; Miller, Niall; Stecklum, Bringfried; Makin, Sally V.; Urtly, Thomas; Soldán Alfaro, Francisco C.; Schwendeman, Erik; Stone, Geoffrey; Phillips, Mark; Fleming, George; Gonzalez Farfán, Rafael; Vanmunster, Tonny; Heald, Michael A.; Fernández Mañanes, Esteban; Nelson, Tim; Eggenstein, Heinz-Bernd; Dubois, Franky; Logie, Ludwig; Rau, Steve; Wiersema, Klaas; Quinn, Nick; Rodriguez, Diego; Castillo García, Rafael; Killestein, Thomas; Vale, Tony; Licchelli, Domenico; Deldem, Marc; Piehler, Georg; Moździerski, Dawid; Kotysz, Krzysztof; Kowalska, Katarzyna; Mikołajczyk, Przemysław; Futcher, Stephen R. L.; Long, Timothy P.; Morales Aimar, Mario; Merrikin, Barry; Johnstone, Stephen; Dubovský, Pavol A.; Kudzej, Igor; Pickard, Roger; Billington, Samuel J.; Dover, Lord; Zegmott, Tarik; Evitts, Jack J.; Traspas Munia, Alejandra; Price, Mark C.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 506, Issue 4, pp.5989-6000</TD>
<TD>2021-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.506.5989F</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.506.4877W</TD>
<TD>Carbon-enhanced stars with short orbital and spin periods</TD>
<TD>Whitehouse, L. J.; Farihi, J.; Howarth, I. D.; Mancino, S.; Walters, N.; Swan, A.; Wilson, T. G.; Guo, J.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 506, Issue 4, pp.4877-4892</TD>
<TD>2021-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.506.4877W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.506.4715R</TD>
<TD>A systematic reclassification of Type IIn supernovae</TD>
<TD>Ransome, C. L.; Habergham-Mawson, S. M.; Darnley, M. J.; James, P. A.; Filippenko, A. V.; Schlegel, E. M.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 506, Issue 4, pp.4715-4734</TD>
<TD>2021-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.506.4715R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021JCAP...10..082O</TD>
<TD>Multi-messenger emission from the parsec-scale jet of the flat-spectrum radio quasar PKS 1502+106 coincident with high-energy neutrino IceCube-190730A</TD>
<TD>Oikonomou, Foteini; Petropoulou, Maria; Murase, Kohta; Tohuvavohu, Aaron; Vasilopoulos, Georgios; Buson, Sara; Santander, Marcos</TD>
<TD>Journal of Cosmology and Astroparticle Physics, Volume 2021, Issue 10, id.082, 40 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021JCAP...10..082O</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021AstL...47..695G</TD>
<TD>Observations of Candidates for Eclipsing Cataclysmic Variables with the RTT-150 Telescope</TD>
<TD>Gabdeev, M. M.; Bikmaev, I. F.; Shimansky, V. V.; Zhuchkov, R. Ya.; Irtuganov, E. N.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy Letters, Volume 47, Issue 10, p.695-704</TD>
<TD>2021-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021AstL...47..695G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...920..132P</TD>
<TD>Quantifying Variability of Young Stellar Objects in the Mid-infrared Over 6 Years with the Near-Earth Object Wide-field Infrared Survey Explorer</TD>
<TD>Park, Wooseok; Lee, Jeong-Eun; Contreras Peña, Carlos; Johnstone, Doug; Herczeg, Gregory; Lee, Sieun; Lee, Seonjae; Bhardwaj, Anupam; Moriarty-Schieven, Gerald H.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 920, Issue 2, id.132, 33 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...920..132P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...920..121Y</TD>
<TD>A Comprehensive X-Ray Report on AT2019wey</TD>
<TD>Yao, Yuhan; Kulkarni, S. R.; Gendreau, K. C.; Jaisawal, Gaurava K.; Enoto, Teruaki; Grefenstette, Brian W.; Marshall, Herman L.; García, Javier A.; Ludlam, R. M.; Pike, Sean N.; Ng, Mason; Zhang, Liang; Altamirano, Diego; Jaodand, Amruta; Cenko, S. Bradley; Remillard, Ronald A.; Steiner, James F.; Negoro, Hitoshi; Brightman, Murray; Lien, Amy; Wolff, Michael T.; Ray, Paul S.; Mukai, Koji; Wadiasingh, Zorawar; Arzoumanian, Zaven; Kawai, Nobuyki; Mihara, Tatehiro; Strohmayer, Tod E.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 920, Issue 2, id.121, 18 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...920..121Y</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...920..120Y</TD>
<TD>Multi-wavelength Observations of AT2019wey: a New Candidate Black Hole Low-mass X-ray Binary</TD>
<TD>Yao, Yuhan; Kulkarni, S. R.; Burdge, Kevin B.; Caiazzo, Ilaria; De, Kishalay; Dong, Dillon; Fremling, C.; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Kupfer, Thomas; van Roestel, Jan; Sollerman, Jesper; Bagdasaryan, Ashot; Bellm, Eric C.; Cenko, S. Bradley; Drake, Andrew J.; Duev, Dmitry A.; Graham, Matthew J.; Kaye, Stephen; Masci, Frank J.; Miranda, Nicolas; Prince, Thomas A.; Riddle, Reed; Rusholme, Ben; Soumagnac, Maayane T.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 920, Issue 2, id.120, 14 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...920..120Y</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...920..110S</TD>
<TD>The Final Fates of Close Hot Subdwarf-White Dwarf Binaries: Mergers Involving He/C/O White Dwarfs and the Formation of Unusual Giant Stars with C/O-Dominated Envelopes</TD>
<TD>Schwab, Josiah; Bauer, Evan B.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 920, Issue 2, id.110, 5 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...920..110S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...920...56F</TD>
<TD>A Family Tree of Optical Transients from Narrow-line Seyfert 1 Galaxies</TD>
<TD>Frederick, Sara; Gezari, Suvi; Graham, Matthew J.; Sollerman, Jesper; van Velzen, Sjoert; Perley, Daniel A.; Stern, Daniel; Ward, Charlotte; Hammerstein, Erica; Hung, Tiara; Yan, Lin; Andreoni, Igor; Bellm, Eric C.; Duev, Dmitry A.; Kowalski, Marek; Mahabal, Ashish A.; Masci, Frank J.; Medford, Michael; Rusholme, Ben; Smith, Roger; Walters, Richard</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 920, Issue 1, id.56, 23 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...920...56F</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...920...50A</TD>
<TD>Search for Neutrinos from the Tidal Disruption Events AT2019dsg and AT2019fdr with the ANTARES Telescope</TD>
<TD>Albert, A.; Alves, S.; André, M.; Anghinolfi, M.; Anton, G.; Ardid, M.; Aubert, J. -J.; Aublin, J.; Baret, B.; Basa, S.; Belhorma, B.; Bendahman, M.; Benfenati, F.; Bertin, V.; Biagi, S.; Bissinger, M.; Boumaaza, J.; Bouta, M.; Bouwhuis, M. C.; Brânzaş, H.; Bruijn, R.; Brunner, J.; Busto, J.; Caiffi, B.; Capone, A.; Caramete, L.; Carr, J.; Carretero, V.; Celli, S.; Chabab, M.; Chau, T. N.; El Moursli, R. Cherkaoui; Chiarusi, T.; Circella, M.; Coleiro, A.; Colomer-Molla, M.; Coniglione, R.; Coyle, P.; Creusot, A.; Díaz, A. F.; Wasseige, G. De; Deschamps, A.; Distefano, C.; Palma, I. Di; Domi, A.; Donzaud, C.; Dornic, D.; Drouhin, D.; Eberl, T.; Eeden, T. Van; Khayati, N. El; Enzenhöfer, A.; Fermani, P.; Ferrara, G.; Filippini, F.; Fusco, L.; García, R.; Gatelet, Y.; Gay, P.; Glotin, H.; Gozzini, R.; Graf, K.; Guidi, C.; Hallmann, S.; Haren, H. Van; Heijboer, A. J.; Hello, Y.; Hernández-Rey, J. J.; Hößl, J.; Hofestädt, J.; Huang, F.; Illuminati, G.; James, C. W.; Jisse-Jung, B.; Jong, M. De; Jong, P. De; Jongen, M.; Kadler, M.; Kalekin, O.; Katz, U.; Khan-Chowdhury, N. R.; Kouchner, A.; Kreykenbohm, I.; Kulikovskiy, V.; Lahmann, R.; Le Breton, R.; Lefèvre, D.; Leonora, E.; Levi, G.; Lincetto, M.; Lopez-Coto, D.; Loucatos, S.; Maderer, L.; Manczak, J.; Marcelin, M.; Margiotta, A.; Marinelli, A.; Martínez-Mora, J. A.; Melis, K.; Migliozzi, P.; Moser, M.; Moussa, A.; Muller, R.; Nauta, L.; Navas, S.; Nezri, E.; Fearraigh, B. Ó.; Organokov, M.; Păvălaş, G. E.; Pellegrino, C.; Perrin-Terrin, M.; Piattelli, P.; Pieterse, C.; Poirè, C.; Popa, V.; Pradier, T.; Randazzo, N.; Reck, S.; Riccobene, G.; Romanov, A.; Greus, F. Salesa; Samtleben, D. F. E.; Sánchez-Losa, A.; Sanguineti, M.; Sapienza, P.; Schnabel, J.; Schumann, J.; Schüssler, F.; Spurio, M.; Stolarczyk, Th.; Taiuti, M.; Tayalati, Y.; Tingay, S. J.; Vallage, B.; van Elewyck, V.; Versari, F.; Viola, S.; Vivolo, D.; Wilms, J.; Zavatarelli, S.; Zegarelli, A.; Zornoza, J. D.; Zúñiga, J.; ANTARES Collaboration</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 920, Issue 1, id.50, 6 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...920...50A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...920....9L</TD>
<TD>Reverberation Mapping of Two Luminous Quasars: The Broad-line Region Structure and Black Hole Mass</TD>
<TD>Li, Sha-Sha; Yang, Sen; Yang, Zi-Xu; Chen, Yong-Jie; Songsheng, Yu-Yang; Liu, He-Zhen; Du, Pu; Luo, Bin; Yu, Zhe; Hu, Chen; Jiang, Bo-Wei; Bao, Dong-Wei; Guo, Wei-Jian; Zhang, Zhi-Xiang; Li, Yan-Rong; Xiao, Ming; Lu, Kai-Xing; Ho, Luis C.; Bai, Jin-Ming; Bian, Wei-Hao; Aceituno, Jesús; Minezaki, Takeo; Horne, Keith; Kokubo, Mitsuru; Wang, Jian-Min</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 920, Issue 1, id.9, 17 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...920....9L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...919L..26V</TD>
<TD>ZTFJ0038+2030: A Long-period Eclipsing White Dwarf and a Substellar Companion</TD>
<TD>van Roestel, Jan; Kupfer, Thomas; Bell, Keaton J.; Burdge, Kevin; Mróz, Przemek; Prince, Thomas A.; Bellm, Eric C.; Drake, Andrew; Dekany, Richard; Mahabal, Ashish A.; Porter, Michael; Riddle, Reed; Shin, Kyung Min; Shupe, David L.; Kulkarni, S. R.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 919, Issue 2, id.L26, 9 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...919L..26V</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...919..142B</TD>
<TD>A Bright Ultraviolet Excess in the Transitional 02es-like Type Ia Supernova 2019yvq</TD>
<TD>Burke, J.; Howell, D. A.; Sarbadhicary, S. K.; Sand, D. J.; Amaro, R. C.; Hiramatsu, D.; McCully, C.; Pellegrino, C.; Andrews, J. E.; Brown, P. J.; Itagaki, Koichi; Shahbandeh, M.; Bostroem, K. A.; Chomiuk, L.; Hsiao, E. Y.; Smith, Nathan; Valenti, S.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 919, Issue 2, id.142, 17 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...919..142B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...919..127C</TD>
<TD>Radio Observations of an Ordinary Outflow from the Tidal Disruption Event AT2019dsg</TD>
<TD>Cendes, Y.; Alexander, K. D.; Berger, E.; Eftekhari, T.; Williams, P. K. G.; Chornock, R.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 919, Issue 2, id.127, 9 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...919..127C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...919...87B</TD>
<TD>Phase Separation in Ultramassive White Dwarfs</TD>
<TD>Blouin, Simon; Daligault, Jérôme</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 919, Issue 2, id.87, 8 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...919...87B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...919...85B</TD>
<TD>On the Use of Field RR Lyrae as Galactic Probes. V. Optical and Radial Velocity Curve Templates</TD>
<TD>Braga, V. F.; Crestani, J.; Fabrizio, M.; Bono, G.; Sneden, C.; Preston, G. W.; Storm, J.; Kamann, S.; Latour, M.; Lala, H.; Lemasle, B.; Prudil, Z.; Altavilla, G.; Chaboyer, B.; Dall'Ora, M.; Ferraro, I.; Gilligan, C. K.; Fiorentino, G.; Iannicola, G.; Inno, L.; Kwak, S.; Marengo, M.; Marinoni, S.; Marrese, P. M.; Martínez-Vázquez, C. E.; Monelli, M.; Mullen, J. P.; Matsunaga, N.; Neeley, J.; Stetson, P. B.; Valenti, E.; Zoccali, M.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 919, Issue 2, id.85, 36 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...919...85B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021AJ....162..167F</TD>
<TD>TOI-1749: an M dwarf with a Trio of Planets including a Near-resonant Pair</TD>
<TD>Fukui, A.; Korth, J.; Livingston, J. H.; Twicken, J. D.; Osorio, M. R. Zapatero; Jenkins, J. M.; Mori, M.; Murgas, F.; Ogihara, M.; Narita, N.; Pallé, E.; Stassun, K. G.; Nowak, G.; Ciardi, D. R.; Alvarez-Hernandez, L.; Béjar, V. J. S.; Casasayas-Barris, N.; Crouzet, N.; de Leon, J. P.; Esparza-Borges, E.; Soto, D. Hidalgo; Isogai, K.; Kawauchi, K.; Klagyivik, P.; Kodama, T.; Kurita, S.; Kusakabe, N.; Luque, R.; Madrigal-Aguado, A.; Rodriguez, P. Montanes; Morello, G.; Nishiumi, T.; Orell-Miquel, J.; Oshagh, M.; Parviainen, H.; Sánchez-Benavente, M.; Stangret, M.; Terada, Y.; Watanabe, N.; Chen, G.; Tamura, M.; Bosch-Cabot, P.; Bowen, M.; Eastridge, K.; Freour, L.; Gonzales, E.; Guerra, P.; Jundiyeh, Y.; Kim, T. K.; Kroer, L. V.; Levine, A. M.; Morgan, E. H.; Reefe, M.; Tronsgaard, R.; Wedderkopp, C. K.; Wittrock, J.; Collins, K. A.; Hesse, K.; Latham, D. W.; Ricker, G. R.; Seager, S.; Vanderspek, R.; Winn, J.; Bachelet, E.; Bowman, M.; McCully, C.; Daily, M.; Harbeck, D.; Volgenau, N. H.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 162, Issue 4, id.167, 23 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021AJ....162..167F</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021AJ....162..143M</TD>
<TD>THOR: An Algorithm for Cadence-independent Asteroid Discovery</TD>
<TD>Moeyens, Joachim; Jurić, Mario; Ford, Jes; Bektešević, Dino; Connolly, Andrew J.; Eggl, Siegfried; Ivezić, Željko; Jones, R. Lynne; Kalmbach, J. Bryce; Smotherman, Hayden</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 162, Issue 4, id.143, 16 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021AJ....162..143M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021AJ....162..135K</TD>
<TD>TOI-532b: The Habitable-zone Planet Finder confirms a Large Super Neptune in the Neptune Desert orbiting a metal-rich M-dwarf host</TD>
<TD>Kanodia, Shubham; Stefansson, Gudmundur; Cañas, Caleb I.; Maney, Marissa; Lin, Andrea S. J.; Ninan, Joe P.; Jones, Sinclaire; Monson, Andrew; Parker, Brock A.; Kobulnicky, Henry A.; Rothenberg, Jason; Beard, Corey; Lubin, Jack; Robertson, Paul; Gupta, Arvind F.; Mahadevan, Suvrath; Cochran, William D.; Bender, Chad F.; Diddams, Scott A.; Fredrick, Connor; Halverson, Samuel; Hawley, Suzanne; Hearty, Fred; Hebb, Leslie; Kopparapu, Ravi; Metcalf, Andrew J.; Ramsey, Lawrence W.; Roy, Arpita; Schwab, Christian; Schutte, Maria; Terrien, Ryan C.; Wisniewski, John; Wright, Jason T.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 162, Issue 4, id.135, 13 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021AJ....162..135K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021AJ....162..133S</TD>
<TD>Identifying Periodic Variable Stars and Eclipsing Binary Systems with Long-term Las Cumbres Observatory Photometric Monitoring of ZTF J0139+5245</TD>
<TD>Sanghi, Aniket; Vanderbosch, Zachary P.; Montgomery, Michael H.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 162, Issue 4, id.133, 11 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021AJ....162..133S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021A&amp;A...654A..48H</TD>
<TD>V-band photometry of asteroids from ASAS-SN. Finding asteroids with slow spin</TD>
<TD>Hanuš, J.; Pejcha, O.; Shappee, B. J.; Kochanek, C. S.; Stanek, K. Z.; Holoien, T. W. -S.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 654, id.A48, 11 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021A&amp;A...654A..48H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021A&amp;A...654A..12B</TD>
<TD>Exploring the nature of ambiguous merging systems: GW190425 in low latency</TD>
<TD>Barbieri, C.; Salafia, O. S.; Colpi, M.; Ghirlanda, G.; Perego, A.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 654, id.A12, 17 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021A&amp;A...654A..12B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021Sci...373.1125D</TD>
<TD>A transient radio source consistent with a merger-triggered core collapse supernova</TD>
<TD>Dong, D. Z.; Hallinan, G.; Nakar, E.; Ho, A. Y. Q.; Hughes, A. K.; Hotokezaka, K.; Myers, S. T.; De, K.; Mooley, K. P.; Ravi, V.; Horesh, A.; Kasliwal, M. M.; Kulkarni, S. R.</TD>
<TD>Science, Volume 373, Issue 6559, pp. 1125-1129 (2021).</TD>
<TD>2021-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021Sci...373.1125D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021NatRP...3..732V</TD>
<TD>The origins of massive black holes</TD>
<TD>Volonteri, Marta; Habouzit, Mélanie; Colpi, Monica</TD>
<TD>Nature Reviews Physics, Volume 3, Issue 11, p.732-743</TD>
<TD>2021-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021NatRP...3..732V</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.506.4151M</TD>
<TD>Spectroscopic and photometric analysis of symbiotic candidates - I. Ten candidates on classical symbiotic stars</TD>
<TD>Merc, J.; Gális, R.; Wolf, M.; Velez, P.; Buil, C.; Sims, F.; Bohlsen, T.; Vrašťák, M.; Boussin, C.; Boussier, H.; Cazzato, P.; Diarrasouba, I.; Teyssier, F.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 506, Issue 3, pp.4151-4162</TD>
<TD>2021-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.506.4151M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.506.4031M</TD>
<TD>White dwarf planetary debris dependence on physical structure distributions within asteroid belts</TD>
<TD>McDonald, Catriona H.; Veras, Dimitri</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 506, Issue 3, pp.4031-4047</TD>
<TD>2021-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.506.4031M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.506.3872E</TD>
<TD>Discovery of superslow rotating asteroids with ATLAS and ZTF photometry</TD>
<TD>Erasmus, N.; Kramer, D.; McNeill, A.; Trilling, D. E.; Janse van Rensburg, P.; van Belle, G. T.; Tonry, J. L.; Denneau, L.; Heinze, A.; Weiland, H. J.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 506, Issue 3, pp.3872-3881</TD>
<TD>2021-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.506.3872E</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.506.2482H</TD>
<TD>A microlensing search of 700 million VVV light curves</TD>
<TD>Husseiniova, Andrea; McGill, Peter; Smith, Leigh C.; Evans, N. Wyn</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 506, Issue 2, pp.2482-2502</TD>
<TD>2021-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.506.2482H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.506.2445S</TD>
<TD>Binary neutron star merger in common envelope jets supernovae</TD>
<TD>Soker, Noam</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 506, Issue 2, pp.2445-2452</TD>
<TD>2021-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.506.2445S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.506.1896K</TD>
<TD>The Heraklion Extragalactic Catalogue (HECATE): a value-added galaxy catalogue for multimessenger astrophysics</TD>
<TD>Kovlakas, K.; Zezas, A.; Andrews, J. J.; Basu-Zych, A.; Fragos, T.; Hornschemeier, A.; Kouroumpatzakis, K.; Lehmer, B.; Ptak, A.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 506, Issue 2, pp.1896-1915</TD>
<TD>2021-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.506.1896K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.506.1832M</TD>
<TD>SN 2020cpg: an energetic link between Type IIb and Ib supernovae</TD>
<TD>Medler, K.; Mazzali, P. A.; Teffs, J.; Prentice, S. J.; Ashall, C.; Amenouche, M.; Anderson, J. P.; Burke, J.; Chen, T. W.; Galbany, L.; Gromadzki, M.; Gutiérrez, C. P.; Hiramatsu, D.; Howell, D. A.; Inserra, C.; Kankare, E.; McCully, C.; Müller-Bravo, T. E.; Nicholl, M.; Pellegrino, C.; Sollerman, J.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 506, Issue 2, pp.1832-1849</TD>
<TD>2021-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.506.1832M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.506..919B</TD>
<TD>Rare events of a peculiar thermonuclear supernova that precedes a core-collapse supernova</TD>
<TD>Bear, Ealeal; Soker, Noam</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 506, Issue 1, pp.919-927</TD>
<TD>2021-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.506..919B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021Icar..36514452H</TD>
<TD>The population of near-earth asteroids revisited and updated</TD>
<TD>Harris, Alan W.; Chodas, Paul W.</TD>
<TD>Icarus, Volume 365, article id. 114452.</TD>
<TD>2021-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021Icar..36514452H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021EPJC...81..824G</TD>
<TD>Yukawa-Casimir wormholes</TD>
<TD>Garattini, Remo</TD>
<TD>The European Physical Journal C, Volume 81, Issue 9, article id.824</TD>
<TD>2021-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021EPJC...81..824G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...918L..14K</TD>
<TD>The Discovery of Two LISA Sources within 0.5 kpc</TD>
<TD>Kilic, Mukremin; Brown, Warren R.; Bédard, A.; Kosakowski, Alekzander</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 918, Issue 1, id.L14, 7 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...918L..14K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...918...63A</TD>
<TD>Fast-transient Searches in Real Time with ZTFReST: Identification of Three Optically Discovered Gamma-Ray Burst Afterglows and New Constraints on the Kilonova Rate</TD>
<TD>Andreoni, Igor; Coughlin, Michael W.; Kool, Erik C.; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Kumar, Harsh; Bhalerao, Varun; Carracedo, Ana Sagués; Ho, Anna Y. Q.; Pang, Peter T. H.; Saraogi, Divita; Sharma, Kritti; Shenoy, Vedant; Burns, Eric; Ahumada, Tomás; Anand, Shreya; Singer, Leo P.; Perley, Daniel A.; De, Kishalay; Fremling, U. C.; Bellm, Eric C.; Bulla, Mattia; Crellin-Quick, Arien; Dietrich, Tim; Drake, Andrew; Duev, Dmitry A.; Goobar, Ariel; Graham, Matthew J.; Kaplan, David L.; Kulkarni, S. R.; Laher, Russ R.; Mahabal, Ashish A.; Shupe, David L.; Sollerman, Jesper; Walters, Richard; Yao, Yuhan</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 918, Issue 2, id.63, 16 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...918...63A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...918...46W</TD>
<TD>Mass, Spin, and Ultralight Boson Constraints from the Intermediate-mass Black Hole in the Tidal Disruption Event 3XMM J215022.4-055108</TD>
<TD>Wen, Sixiang; Jonker, Peter G.; Stone, Nicholas C.; Zabludoff, Ann I.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 918, Issue 2, id.46, 15 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...918...46W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...918....3D</TD>
<TD>Blueshifted Hydrogen Emission and Shock Wave of RR Lyrae Variables in SDSS and LAMOST</TD>
<TD>Duan, Xiao-Wei; Chen, Xiaodian; Sun, Weijia; Deng, Licai; Zhang, Huawei; Yang, Fan; Liu, Chao</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 918, Issue 1, id.3, 15 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...918....3D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ARA&amp;A..59...21G</TD>
<TD>Tidal Disruption Events</TD>
<TD>Gezari, Suvi</TD>
<TD>Annual Review of Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 59, pp. 21-58</TD>
<TD>2021-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ARA&amp;A..59...21G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021AJ....162..113V</TD>
<TD>A Systematic Search for Outbursting AM CVn Systems with the Zwicky Transient Facility</TD>
<TD>van Roestel, Jan; Creter, Leah; Kupfer, Thomas; Szkody, Paula; Fuller, Jim; Green, Matthew J.; Rich, R. Michael; Sepikas, John; Burdge, Kevin; Caiazzo, Ilaria; Mróz, Przemek; Prince, Thomas A.; Duev, Dmitry A.; Graham, Matthew J.; Shupe, David L.; Laher, Russ R.; Mahabal, Ashish A.; Masci, Frank J.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 162, Issue 3, id.113, 13 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021AJ....162..113V</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021AJ....162..109S</TD>
<TD>Combining Astrometry and Elemental Abundances: The Case of the Candidate Pre-Gaia Halo Moving Groups G03-37, G18-39, and G21-22</TD>
<TD>Schuler, Simon C.; Andrews, Jeff J.; Clanzy, Vincent R.; Mourabit, Mohammed; Chanamé, Julio; Agüeros, Marcel A.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 162, Issue 3, id.109, 17 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021AJ....162..109S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021AJ....162...94S</TD>
<TD>Cataclysmic Variables in the Second Year of the Zwicky Transient Facility</TD>
<TD>Szkody, Paula; Olde Loohuis, Claire; Koplitz, Brad; van Roestel, Jan; Dicenzo, Brooke; Ho, Anna Y. Q.; Hillenbrand, Lynne A.; Bellm, Eric C.; Dekany, Richard; Drake, Andrew J.; Duev, Dmitry A.; Graham, Matthew J.; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Mahabal, Ashish A.; Masci, Frank J.; Neill, James D.; Riddle, Reed; Rusholme, Benjamin; Sollerman, Jesper; Walters, Richard</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 162, Issue 3, id.94, 17 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021AJ....162...94S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021A&amp;A...653A..22K</TD>
<TD>Deep transfer learning for the classification of variable sources</TD>
<TD>Kim, Dae-Won; Yeo, Doyeob; Bailer-Jones, Coryn A. L.; Lee, Giyoung</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 653, id.A22, 16 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021A&amp;A...653A..22K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021Sci...373..789B</TD>
<TD>A characteristic optical variability time scale in astrophysical accretion disks</TD>
<TD>Burke, Colin J.; Shen, Yue; Blaes, Omer; Gammie, Charles F.; Horne, Keith; Jiang, Yan-Fei; Liu, Xin; McHardy, Ian M.; Morgan, Christopher W.; Scaringi, Simone; Yang, Qian</TD>
<TD>Science, Volume 373, Issue 6556, pp. 789-792 (2021).</TD>
<TD>2021-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021Sci...373..789B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021PhLB..81936429D</TD>
<TD>Bounds on GUP parameters from GW150914 and GW190521</TD>
<TD>Das, Ashmita; Das, Saurya; Mansour, Noor R.; Vagenas, Elias C.</TD>
<TD>Physics Letters B, Volume 819, article id. 136429.</TD>
<TD>2021-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021PhLB..81936429D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021PSJ.....2..131K</TD>
<TD>Six Outbursts of Comet 46P/Wirtanen</TD>
<TD>Kelley, Michael S. P.; Farnham, Tony L.; Li, Jian-Yang; Bodewits, Dennis; Snodgrass, Colin; Allen, Johannes; Bellm, Eric C.; Coughlin, Michael W.; Drake, Andrew J.; Duev, Dmitry A.; Graham, Matthew J.; Kupfer, Thomas; Masci, Frank J.; Reiley, Dan; Walters, Richard; Dominik, M.; Jørgensen, U. G.; Andrews, A. E.; Bach-Møller, N.; Bozza, V.; Burgdorf, M. J.; Campbell-White, J.; Dib, S.; Fujii, Y. I.; Hinse, T. C.; Hundertmark, M.; Khalouei, E.; Longa-Peña, P.; Rabus, M.; Rahvar, S.; Sajadian, S.; Skottfelt, J.; Southworth, J.; Tregloan-Reed, J.; Unda-Sanzana, E.; Mindstep Collaboration</TD>
<TD>The Planetary Science Journal, Volume 2, Issue 4, id.131, 18 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021PSJ.....2..131K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021PASP..133h4202L</TD>
<TD>Error Analysis of the Light Curve Solution of Contact Binaries Based on the W-D Code</TD>
<TD>Liu, Liang</TD>
<TD>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 133, Issue 1026, id.084202, 16 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021PASP..133h4202L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.505.6121M</TD>
<TD>The GALAH survey and symbiotic stars - I. Discovery and follow-up of 33 candidate accreting-only systems</TD>
<TD>Munari, U.; Traven, G.; Masetti, N.; Valisa, P.; Righetti, G. -L.; Hambsch, F. -J.; Frigo, A.; Čotar, K.; De Silva, G. M.; Freeman, K. C.; Lewis, G. F.; Martell, S. L.; Sharma, S.; Simpson, J. D.; Ting, Y. -S.; Wittenmyer, R. A.; Zucker, D. B.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 505, Issue 4, pp.6121-6154</TD>
<TD>2021-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.505.6121M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.505.4890L</TD>
<TD>SN 2015bf: A fast declining type II supernova with flash-ionized signatures</TD>
<TD>Lin, Han; Wang, Xiaofeng; Zhang, Jujia; Lin, Weili; Mo, Jun; Filippenko, Alexei V.; Zheng, WeiKang; Brown, Peter J.; Xiang, Danfeng; Huang, Fang; Cai, Yongzhi; Zhang, Tianmeng; Li, Xue; Rui, Liming; Zhang, Xinghan; Sai, Hanna; Zhao, Xulin; Graham, Melissa L.; Shivvers, I.; Halevi, G.; Yuk, H.; Brink, Thomas G.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 505, Issue 4, pp.4890-4905</TD>
<TD>2021-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.505.4890L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.505.4345B</TD>
<TD>Light-curve classification with recurrent neural networks for GOTO: dealing with imbalanced data</TD>
<TD>Burhanudin, U. F.; Maund, J. R.; Killestein, T.; Ackley, K.; Dyer, M. J.; Lyman, J.; Ulaczyk, K.; Cutter, R.; Mong, Y. -L.; Steeghs, D.; Galloway, D. K.; Dhillon, V.; O'Brien, P.; Ramsay, G.; Noysena, K.; Kotak, R.; Breton, R. P.; Nuttall, L.; Pallé, E.; Pollacco, D.; Thrane, E.; Awiphan, S.; Chote, P.; Chrimes, A.; Daw, E.; Duffy, C.; Eyles-Ferris, R.; Gompertz, B.; Heikkilä, T.; Irawati, P.; Kennedy, M. R.; Levan, A.; Littlefair, S.; Makrygianni, L.; Mata-Sánchez, D.; Mattila, S.; McCormac, J.; Mkrtichian, D.; Mullaney, J.; Sawangwit, U.; Stanway, E.; Starling, R.; Strøm, P.; Tooke, S.; Wiersema, K.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 505, Issue 3, pp.4345-4361</TD>
<TD>2021-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.505.4345B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.505.4235S</TD>
<TD>Predicting electromagnetic counterparts using low-latency gravitational-wave data products</TD>
<TD>Stachie, Cosmin; Coughlin, Michael W.; Dietrich, Tim; Antier, Sarah; Bulla, Mattia; Christensen, Nelson; Essick, Reed; Landry, Philippe; Mours, Benoit; Schianchi, Federico; Toivonen, Andrew</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 505, Issue 3, pp.4235-4248</TD>
<TD>2021-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.505.4235S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.505.2954C</TD>
<TD>The ZTF Source Classification Project - II. Periodicity and variability processing metrics</TD>
<TD>Coughlin, Michael W.; Burdge, Kevin; Duev, Dmitry A.; Katz, Michael L.; van Roestel, Jan; Drake, Andrew; Graham, Matthew J.; Hillenbrand, Lynne; Mahabal, Ashish A.; Masci, Frank J.; Mróz, Przemek; Prince, Thomas A.; Yao, Yuhan; Bellm, Eric C.; Burruss, Rick; Dekany, Richard; Jaodand, Amruta; Kaplan, David L.; Kupfer, Thomas; Laher, Russ R.; Riddle, Reed; Rigault, Mickael; Rodriguez, Hector; Rusholme, Ben; Zolkower, Jeffry</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 505, Issue 2, pp.2954-2965</TD>
<TD>2021-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.505.2954C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.505.2477N</TD>
<TD>A high-rate foreground of sub-second flares from geosynchronous satellites</TD>
<TD>Nir, Guy; Ofek, Eran O.; Ben-Ami, Sagi; Segev, Noam; Polishook, David; Manulis, Ilan</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 505, Issue 2, pp.2477-2484</TD>
<TD>2021-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.505.2477N</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.505.2349S</TD>
<TD>Peculiar-velocity cosmology with Types Ia and II supernovae</TD>
<TD>Stahl, Benjamin E.; de Jaeger, Thomas; Boruah, Supranta S.; Zheng, WeiKang; Filippenko, Alexei V.; Hudson, Michael J.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 505, Issue 2, pp.2349-2360</TD>
<TD>2021-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.505.2349S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.505.2051E</TD>
<TD>LAMOST J0140355 + 392651: an evolved cataclysmic variable donor transitioning to become an extremely low-mass white dwarf</TD>
<TD>El-Badry, Kareem; Quataert, Eliot; Rix, Hans-Walter; Weisz, Daniel R.; Kupfer, Thomas; Shen, Ken J.; Xiang, Maosheng; Yang, Yong; Liu, Xiaowei</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 505, Issue 2, pp.2051-2073</TD>
<TD>2021-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.505.2051E</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.505.2009G</TD>
<TD>Peculiarities of the chemical abundance distribution in galaxies NGC 3963 and NGC 7292</TD>
<TD>Gusev, A. S.; Dodin, A. V.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 505, Issue 2, pp.2009-2019</TD>
<TD>2021-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.505.2009G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.505.1742R</TD>
<TD>The iron yield of normal Type II supernovae</TD>
<TD>Rodríguez, Ó.; Meza, N.; Pineda-García, J.; Ramirez, M.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 505, Issue 2, pp.1742-1774</TD>
<TD>2021-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.505.1742R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021JCAP...08..026F</TD>
<TD>Cosmology with LIGO/Virgo dark sirens: Hubble parameter and modified gravitational wave propagation</TD>
<TD>Finke, Andreas; Foffa, Stefano; Iacovelli, Francesco; Maggiore, Michele; Mancarella, Michele</TD>
<TD>Journal of Cosmology and Astroparticle Physics, Volume 2021, Issue 08, id.026, 97 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021JCAP...08..026F</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021Icar..36414387L</TD>
<TD>NEOExchange - an online portal for NEO and Solar System science</TD>
<TD>Lister, T. A.; Gomez, E.; Chatelain, J.; Greenstreet, S.; MacFarlane, J.; Tedeschi, A.; Kosic, I.</TD>
<TD>Icarus, Volume 364, article id. 114387.</TD>
<TD>2021-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021Icar..36414387L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJS..255...29S</TD>
<TD>The Palomar Transient Factory Core-collapse Supernova Host-galaxy Sample. I. Host-galaxy Distribution Functions and Environment Dependence of Core-collapse Supernovae</TD>
<TD>Schulze, Steve; Yaron, Ofer; Sollerman, Jesper; Leloudas, Giorgos; Gal, Amit; Wright, Angus H.; Lunnan, Ragnhild; Gal-Yam, Avishay; Ofek, Eran O.; Perley, Daniel A.; Filippenko, Alexei V.; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Kulkarni, Shrinivas R.; Neill, James D.; Nugent, Peter E.; Quimby, Robert M.; Sullivan, Mark; Strotjohann, Nora Linn; Arcavi, Iair; Ben-Ami, Sagi; Bianco, Federica; Bloom, Joshua S.; De, Kishalay; Fraser, Morgan; Fremling, Christoffer U.; Horesh, Assaf; Johansson, Joel; Kelly, Patrick L.; Knežević, Nikola; Knežević, Sladjana; Maguire, Kate; Nyholm, Anders; Papadogiannakis, Seméli; Petrushevska, Tanja; Rubin, Adam; Yan, Lin; Yang, Yi; Adams, Scott M.; Bufano, Filomena; Clubb, Kelsey I.; Foley, Ryan J.; Green, Yoav; Harmanen, Jussi; Ho, Anna Y. Q.; Hook, Isobel M.; Hosseinzadeh, Griffin; Howell, D. Andrew; Kong, Albert K. H.; Kotak, Rubina; Matheson, Thomas; McCully, Curtis; Milisavljevic, Dan; Pan, Yen-Chen; Poznanski, Dovi; Shivvers, Isaac; van Velzen, Sjoert; Verbeek, Kars K.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 255, Issue 2, id.29, 35 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJS..255...29S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJS..255...24V</TD>
<TD>A Deep-learning Approach for Live Anomaly Detection of Extragalactic Transients</TD>
<TD>Villar, V. Ashley; Cranmer, Miles; Berger, Edo; Contardo, Gabriella; Ho, Shirley; Hosseinzadeh, Griffin; Lin, Joshua Yao-Yu</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 255, Issue 2, id.24, 11 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJS..255...24V</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...917L...2F</TD>
<TD>SNIascore: Deep-learning Classification of Low-resolution Supernova Spectra</TD>
<TD>Fremling, Christoffer; Hall, Xander J.; Coughlin, Michael W.; Dahiwale, Aishwarya S.; Duev, Dmitry A.; Graham, Matthew J.; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Kool, Erik C.; Mahabal, Ashish A.; Miller, Adam A.; Neill, James D.; Perley, Daniel A.; Rigault, Mickael; Rosnet, Philippe; Rusholme, Ben; Sharma, Yashvi; Shin, Kyung Min; Shupe, David L.; Sollerman, Jesper; Walters, Richard S.; Kulkarni, S. R.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 917, Issue 1, id.L2, 10 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...917L...2F</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...917...63A</TD>
<TD>The Blue Supergiant Progenitor of the Supernova Imposter AT 2019krl</TD>
<TD>Andrews, Jennifer E.; Jencson, Jacob E.; Van Dyk, Schuyler D.; Smith, Nathan; Neustadt, Jack M. M.; Sand, David J.; Kreckel, K.; Kochanek, C. S.; Valenti, S.; Strader, Jay; Bersten, M. C.; Blanc, Guillermo A.; Bostroem, K. Azalee; Brink, Thomas G.; Emsellem, Eric; Filippenko, Alexei V.; Folatelli, Gastón; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Masci, Frank J.; McElroy, Rebecca; Milisavljevic, Dan; Santoro, Francesco; Szalai, Tamás</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 917, Issue 2, id.63, 16 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...917...63A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...917...41V</TD>
<TD>Recurring Planetary Debris Transits and Circumstellar Gas around White Dwarf ZTF J0328-1219</TD>
<TD>Vanderbosch, Zachary P.; Rappaport, Saul; Guidry, Joseph A.; Gary, Bruce L.; Blouin, Simon; Kaye, Thomas G.; Weinberger, Alycia J.; Melis, Carl; Klein, Beth L.; Zuckerman, B.; Vanderburg, Andrew; Hermes, J. J.; Hegedus, Ryan J.; Burleigh, Matthew. R.; Sefako, Ramotholo; Worters, Hannah L.; Heintz, Tyler M.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 917, Issue 1, id.41, 18 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...917...41V</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...917...36K</TD>
<TD>Illuminating Black Hole Subsystems in Young Star Clusters</TD>
<TD>Kaaz, Nicholas; Kremer, Kyle; Auchettl, Katie; Ramirez-Ruiz, Enrico</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 917, Issue 1, id.36, 12 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...917...36K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...917...24Z</TD>
<TD>Kilonova Emission from Black Hole-Neutron Star Mergers. II. Luminosity Function and Implications for Target-of-opportunity Observations of Gravitational-wave Triggers and Blind Searches</TD>
<TD>Zhu, Jin-Ping; Wu, Shichao; Yang, Yuan-Pei; Zhang, Bing; Gao, He; Yu, Yun-Wei; Li, Zhuo; Cao, Zhoujian; Liu, Liang-Duan; Huang, Yan; Zhang, Xing-Han</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 917, Issue 1, id.24, 25 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...917...24Z</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...917....9H</TD>
<TD>Discovery of a Fast Iron Low-ionization Outflow in the Early Evolution of the Nearby Tidal Disruption Event AT 2019qiz</TD>
<TD>Hung, Tiara; Foley, Ryan J.; Veilleux, S.; Cenko, S. B.; Dai, Jane L.; Auchettl, Katie; Brink, Thomas G.; Dimitriadis, Georgios; Filippenko, Alexei V.; Gezari, S.; Holoien, Thomas W. -S.; Kilpatrick, Charles D.; Mockler, Brenna; Piro, Anthony L.; Ramirez-Ruiz, Enrico; Rojas-Bravo, César; Siebert, Matthew R.; van Velzen, Sjoert; Zheng, WeiKang</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 917, Issue 1, id.9, 22 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...917....9H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...916L..17W</TD>
<TD>Accretion-modified Stars in Accretion Disks of Active Galactic Nuclei: Gravitational-wave Bursts and Electromagnetic Counterparts from Merging Stellar Black Hole Binaries</TD>
<TD>Wang, Jian-Min; Liu, Jun-Rong; Ho, Luis C.; Li, Yan-Rong; Du, Pu</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 916, Issue 2, id.L17, 11 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...916L..17W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...916..119S</TD>
<TD>Cooling Models for the Most Massive White Dwarfs</TD>
<TD>Schwab, Josiah</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 916, Issue 2, id.119, 6 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...916..119S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021AJ....162...63N</TD>
<TD>Zwicky Transient Facility and Globular Clusters: the Period-Luminosity and Period-Luminosity-Color Relations for Late-type Contact Binaries</TD>
<TD>Ngeow, Chow-Choong; Liao, Szu-Han; Bellm, Eric C.; Duev, Dmitry A.; Graham, Matthew J.; Mahabal, Ashish A.; Masci, Frank J.; Medford, Michael S.; Riddle, Reed; Rusholme, Ben</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 162, Issue 2, id.63, 21 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021AJ....162...63N</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021A&amp;A...652A.136K</TD>
<TD>SN 2020bqj: A Type Ibn supernova with a long-lasting peak plateau</TD>
<TD>Kool, E. C.; Karamehmetoglu, E.; Sollerman, J.; Schulze, S.; Lunnan, R.; Reynolds, T. M.; Barbarino, C.; Bellm, E. C.; De, K.; Duev, D. A.; Fremling, C.; Golkhou, V. Z.; Graham, M. L.; Green, D. A.; Horesh, A.; Kaye, S.; Kim, Y. -L.; Laher, R. R.; Masci, F. J.; Nordin, J.; Perley, D. A.; Phinney, E. S.; Porter, M.; Reiley, D.; Rodriguez, H.; van Roestel, J.; Rusholme, B.; Sharma, Y.; Sfaradi, I.; Soumagnac, M. T.; Taggart, K.; Tartaglia, L.; Williams, D. R. A.; Yan, L.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 652, id.A136, 21 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021A&amp;A...652A.136K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021A&amp;A...652A..76H</TD>
<TD>Gaia Early Data Release 3. Gaia photometric science alerts</TD>
<TD>Hodgkin, S. T.; Harrison, D. L.; Breedt, E.; Wevers, T.; Rixon, G.; Delgado, A.; Yoldas, A.; Kostrzewa-Rutkowska, Z.; Wyrzykowski, Ł.; van Leeuwen, M.; Blagorodnova, N.; Campbell, H.; Eappachen, D.; Fraser, M.; Ihanec, N.; Koposov, S. E.; Kruszyńska, K.; Marton, G.; Rybicki, K. A.; Brown, A. G. A.; Burgess, P. W.; Busso, G.; Cowell, S.; De Angeli, F.; Diener, C.; Evans, D. W.; Gilmore, G.; Holland, G.; Jonker, P. G.; van Leeuwen, F.; Mignard, F.; Osborne, P. J.; Portell, J.; Prusti, T.; Richards, P. J.; Riello, M.; Seabroke, G. M.; Walton, N. A.; Ábrahám, P.; Altavilla, G.; Baker, S. G.; Bastian, U.; O'Brien, P.; de Bruijne, J.; Butterley, T.; Carrasco, J. M.; Castañeda, J.; Clark, J. S.; Clementini, G.; Copperwheat, C. M.; Cropper, M.; Damljanovic, G.; Davidson, M.; Davis, C. J.; Dennefeld, M.; Dhillon, V. S.; Dolding, C.; Dominik, M.; Esquej, P.; Eyer, L.; Fabricius, C.; Fridman, M.; Froebrich, D.; Garralda, N.; Gomboc, A.; González-Vidal, J. J.; Guerra, R.; Hambly, N. C.; Hardy, L. K.; Holl, B.; Hourihane, A.; Japelj, J.; Kann, D. A.; Kiss, C.; Knigge, C.; Kolb, U.; Komossa, S.; Kóspál, Á.; Kovács, G.; Kun, M.; Leto, G.; Lewis, F.; Littlefair, S. P.; Mahabal, A. A.; Mundell, C. G.; Nagy, Z.; Padeletti, D.; Palaversa, L.; Pigulski, A.; Pretorius, M. L.; van Reeven, W.; Ribeiro, V. A. R. M.; Roelens, M.; Rowell, N.; Schartel, N.; Scholz, A.; Schwope, A.; Sipőcz, B. M.; Smartt, S. J.; Smith, M. D.; Serraller, I.; Steeghs, D.; Sullivan, M.; Szabados, L.; Szegedi-Elek, E.; Tisserand, P.; Tomasella, L.; van Velzen, S.; Whitelock, P. A.; Wilson, R. W.; Young, D. R.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 652, id.A76, 25 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021A&amp;A...652A..76H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021A&amp;A...652A...3R</TD>
<TD>The NAROO digitization center. Overview and scientific program</TD>
<TD>Robert, V.; Desmars, J.; Lainey, V.; Arlot, J. -E.; Perlbarg, A. -C.; Horville, D.; Aboudarham, J.; Etienne, C.; Guérard, J.; Ilovaisky, S.; Khovritchev, M. Y.; Le Poncin-Lafitte, C.; Le Van Suu, A.; Neiner, C.; Pascu, D.; Poirier, L.; Schneider, J.; Tanga, P.; Valls-Gabaud, D.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 652, id.A3, 16 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021A&amp;A...652A...3R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021A&amp;A...652A...1M</TD>
<TD>The potential role of binary neutron star merger afterglows in multimessenger cosmology</TD>
<TD>Mastrogiovanni, S.; Duque, R.; Chassande-Mottin, E.; Daigne, F.; Mochkovitch, R.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 652, id.A1, 13 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021A&amp;A...652A...1M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021NatAs...5..917A</TD>
<TD>Discovery and confirmation of the shortest gamma-ray burst from a collapsar</TD>
<TD>Ahumada, Tomás; Singer, Leo P.; Anand, Shreya; Coughlin, Michael W.; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Ryan, Geoffrey; Andreoni, Igor; Cenko, S. Bradley; Fremling, Christoffer; Kumar, Harsh; Pang, Peter T. H.; Burns, Eric; Cunningham, Virginia; Dichiara, Simone; Dietrich, Tim; Svinkin, Dmitry S.; Almualla, Mouza; Castro-Tirado, Alberto J.; De, Kishalay; Dunwoody, Rachel; Gatkine, Pradip; Hammerstein, Erica; Iyyani, Shabnam; Mangan, Joseph; Perley, Dan; Purkayastha, Sonalika; Bellm, Eric; Bhalerao, Varun; Bolin, Bryce; Bulla, Mattia; Cannella, Christopher; Chandra, Poonam; Duev, Dmitry A.; Frederiks, Dmitry; Gal-Yam, Avishay; Graham, Matthew; Ho, Anna Y. Q.; Hurley, Kevin; Karambelkar, Viraj; Kool, Erik C.; Kulkarni, S. R.; Mahabal, Ashish; Masci, Frank; McBreen, Sheila; Pandey, Shashi B.; Reusch, Simeon; Ridnaia, Anna; Rosnet, Philippe; Rusholme, Benjamin; Carracedo, Ana Sagués; Smith, Roger; Soumagnac, Maayane; Stein, Robert; Troja, Eleonora; Tsvetkova, Anastasia; Walters, Richard; Valeev, Azamat F.</TD>
<TD>Nature Astronomy, Volume 5, p. 917-927</TD>
<TD>2021-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021NatAs...5..917A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021NatAs...5..911Z</TD>
<TD>A peculiarly short-duration gamma-ray burst from massive star core collapse</TD>
<TD>Zhang, B. -B.; Liu, Z. -K.; Peng, Z. -K.; Li, Y.; Lü, H. -J.; Yang, J.; Yang, Y. -S.; Yang, Y. -H.; Meng, Y. -Z.; Zou, J. -H.; Ye, H. -Y.; Wang, X. -G.; Mao, J. -R.; Zhao, X. -H.; Bai, J. -M.; Castro-Tirado, A. J.; Hu, Y. -D.; Dai, Z. -G.; Liang, E. -W.; Zhang, B.</TD>
<TD>Nature Astronomy, Volume 5, p. 911-916</TD>
<TD>2021-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021NatAs...5..911Z</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021NatAs...5..749G</TD>
<TD>Hierarchical mergers of stellar-mass black holes and their gravitational-wave signatures</TD>
<TD>Gerosa, Davide; Fishbach, Maya</TD>
<TD>Nature Astronomy, Volume 5, p. 749-760</TD>
<TD>2021-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021NatAs...5..749G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.505.1316H</TD>
<TD>The observable supernova rate in galaxy-galaxy lensing systems with the TESS satellite</TD>
<TD>Holwerda, B. W.; Knabel, S.; Steele, R. C.; Strolger, L.; Kielkopf, J.; Jacques, A.; Roemer, W.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 505, Issue 1, pp.1316-1323</TD>
<TD>2021-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.505.1316H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.505.1254K</TD>
<TD>Year 1 of the ZTF high-cadence Galactic plane survey: strategy, goals, and early results on new single-mode hot subdwarf B-star pulsators</TD>
<TD>Kupfer, Thomas; Prince, Thomas A.; van Roestel, Jan; Bellm, Eric C.; Bildsten, Lars; Coughlin, Michael W.; Drake, Andrew J.; Graham, Matthew J.; Klein, Courtney; Kulkarni, Shrinivas R.; Masci, Frank J.; Walters, Richard; Andreoni, Igor; Biswas, Rahul; Bradshaw, Corey; Duev, Dmitry A.; Dekany, Richard; Guidry, Joseph A.; Hermes, J. J.; Laher, Russ R.; Riddle, Reed</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 505, Issue 1, pp.1254-1267</TD>
<TD>2021-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.505.1254K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.505.1105E</TD>
<TD>A novel bivariate autoregressive model for predicting and forecasting irregularly observed time series</TD>
<TD>Elorrieta, Felipe; Eyheramendy, Susana; Palma, Wilfredo; Ojeda, Cesar</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 505, Issue 1, pp.1105-1116</TD>
<TD>2021-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.505.1105E</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.505..215R</TD>
<TD>The outburst of a 60 min AM CVn reveals peculiar colour evolution: implications for outbursts in long-period double white dwarfs</TD>
<TD>Rivera Sandoval, L. E.; Maccarone, T. J.; Cavecchi, Y.; Britt, C.; Zurek, D.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 505, Issue 1, pp.215-222</TD>
<TD>2021-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.505..215R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.504.5975A</TD>
<TD>Correlated time variability of multicomponent high-velocity outflows in J162122.54+075808.4</TD>
<TD>Aromal, P.; Srianand, R.; Petitjean, P.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 504, Issue 4, pp.5975-5991</TD>
<TD>2021-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.504.5975A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.504.5967S</TD>
<TD>Double common envelope jets supernovae (CEJSNe) by triple-star systems</TD>
<TD>Soker, Noam</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 504, Issue 4, pp.5967-5974</TD>
<TD>2021-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.504.5967S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.504.5907G</TD>
<TD>Search for dormant black holes in ellipsoidal variables - III. The OGLE BULGE short-period sample</TD>
<TD>Gomel, Roy; Faigler, Simchon; Mazeh, Tsevi; Pawlak, Michał</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 504, Issue 4, pp.5907-5918</TD>
<TD>2021-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.504.5907G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.504.4907G</TD>
<TD>The double-peaked Type Ic supernova 2019cad: another SN 2005bf-like object</TD>
<TD>Gutiérrez, C. P.; Bersten, M. C.; Orellana, M.; Pastorello, A.; Ertini, K.; Folatelli, G.; Pignata, G.; Anderson, J. P.; Smartt, S.; Sullivan, M.; Pursiainen, M.; Inserra, C.; Elias-Rosa, N.; Fraser, M.; Kankare, E.; Moran, S.; Reguitti, A.; Reynolds, T. M.; Stritzinger, M.; Burke, J.; Frohmaier, C.; Galbany, L.; Hiramatsu, D.; Howell, D. A.; Kuncarayakti, H.; Mattila, S.; Müller-Bravo, T.; Pellegrino, C.; Smith, M.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 504, Issue 4, pp.4907-4922</TD>
<TD>2021-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.504.4907G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.504.4768Z</TD>
<TD>Galactic open cluster Cepheids - a census based on Gaia EDR3</TD>
<TD>Zhou, Xiaoyue; Chen, Xiaodian</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 504, Issue 4, pp.4768-4784</TD>
<TD>2021-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.504.4768Z</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.504.3561H</TD>
<TD>PyTorchDIA: a flexible, GPU-accelerated numerical approach to Difference Image Analysis</TD>
<TD>Hitchcock, James A.; Hundertmark, Markus; Foreman-Mackey, Daniel; Bachelet, Etienne; Dominik, Martin; Street, Rachel; Tsapras, Yiannis</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 504, Issue 3, pp.3561-3579</TD>
<TD>2021-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.504.3561H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.504.3375S</TD>
<TD>On the role of resonances in polluting white dwarfs by asteroids</TD>
<TD>Smallwood, Jeremy L.; Martin, Rebecca G.; Livio, Mario; Veras, Dimitri</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 504, Issue 3, pp.3375-3386</TD>
<TD>2021-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.504.3375S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021CQGra..38o3001D</TD>
<TD>In the realm of the Hubble tension-a review of solutions</TD>
<TD>Di Valentino, Eleonora; Mena, Olga; Pan, Supriya; Visinelli, Luca; Yang, Weiqiang; Melchiorri, Alessandro; Mota, David F.; Riess, Adam G.; Silk, Joseph</TD>
<TD>Classical and Quantum Gravity, Volume 38, Issue 15, id.153001, 110 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021CQGra..38o3001D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...915L..11A</TD>
<TD>On the Binary Neutron Star Post-merger Magnetar Origin of XRT 210423</TD>
<TD>Ai, Shunke; Zhang, Bing</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 915, Issue 1, id.L11, 6 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...915L..11A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...915..121P</TD>
<TD>The Exotic Type Ic Broad-lined Supernova SN 2018gep: Blurring the Line between Supernovae and Fast Optical Transients</TD>
<TD>Pritchard, T. A.; Bensch, Katarzyna; Modjaz, Maryam; Williamson, Marc; Thöne, Christina C.; Vinkó, J.; Bianco, Federica B.; Bostroem, K. Azalee; Burke, Jamison; García-Benito, Rubén; Galbany, L.; Hiramatsu, Daichi; Howell, D. Andrew; Izzo, Luca; Kann, D. Alexander; McCully, Curtis; Pellegrino, Craig; de Ugarte Postigo, Antonio; Valenti, Stefano; Wang, Xiaofeng; Wheeler, J. C.; Xiang, Danfeng; Sárneczky, K.; Bódi, A.; Cseh, B.; Tarczay-Nehéz, D.; Kriskovics, L.; Ordasi, A.; Pál, A.; Szakáts, R.; Vida, K.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 915, Issue 2, id.121, 16 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...915..121P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...915...80L</TD>
<TD>Fast Blue Optical Transients Due to Circumstellar Interaction and the Mysterious Supernova SN 2018gep</TD>
<TD>Leung, Shing-Chi; Fuller, Jim; Nomoto, Ken'ichi</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 915, Issue 2, id.80, 17 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...915...80L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021A&amp;C....3600481L</TD>
<TD>ASTRONOMALY: Personalised active anomaly detection in astronomical data</TD>
<TD>Lochner, M.; Bassett, B. A.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy and Computing, Volume 36, article id. 100481.</TD>
<TD>2021-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021A&amp;C....3600481L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021A&amp;C....3600472G</TD>
<TD>Fast period searches using the Lomb-Scargle algorithm on Graphics Processing Units for large datasets and real-time applications</TD>
<TD>Gowanlock, M.; Kramer, D.; Trilling, D. E.; Butler, N. R.; Donnelly, B.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy and Computing, Volume 36, article id. 100472.</TD>
<TD>2021-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021A&amp;C....3600472G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021A&amp;C....3600463N</TD>
<TD>HiSS-Cube: A scalable framework for Hierarchical Semi-Sparse Cubes preserving uncertainties</TD>
<TD>Nádvorník, J.; Škoda, P.; Tvrdík, P.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy and Computing, Volume 36, article id. 100463.</TD>
<TD>2021-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021A&amp;C....3600463N</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021A&amp;A...651L..12M</TD>
<TD>A CHEOPS white dwarf transit search</TD>
<TD>Morris, Brett M.; Heng, Kevin; Brandeker, Alexis; Swan, Andrew; Lendl, Monika</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 651, id.L12, 9 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021A&amp;A...651L..12M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021A&amp;A...651A.104P</TD>
<TD>Galactic spiral structure revealed by Gaia EDR3</TD>
<TD>Poggio, E.; Drimmel, R.; Cantat-Gaudin, T.; Ramos, P.; Ripepi, V.; Zari, E.; Andrae, R.; Blomme, R.; Chemin, L.; Clementini, G.; Figueras, F.; Fouesneau, M.; Frémat, Y.; Lobel, A.; Marshall, D. J.; Muraveva, T.; Romero-Gómez, M.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 651, id.A104, 10 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021A&amp;A...651A.104P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021A&amp;A...651A..83M</TD>
<TD>Prospects for kilonova signals in the gravitational-wave era</TD>
<TD>Mochkovitch, R.; Daigne, F.; Duque, R.; Zitouni, H.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 651, id.A83, 9 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021A&amp;A...651A..83M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021A&amp;A...651A..81B</TD>
<TD>Type Ic supernovae from the (intermediate) Palomar Transient Factory</TD>
<TD>Barbarino, C.; Sollerman, J.; Taddia, F.; Fremling, C.; Karamehmetoglu, E.; Arcavi, I.; Gal-Yam, A.; Laher, R.; Schulze, S.; Wozniak, P.; Yan, Lin</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 651, id.A81, 22 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021A&amp;A...651A..81B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021PASP..133f4503M</TD>
<TD>Removing Atmospheric Fringes from Zwicky Transient Facility i-band Images using Principal Component Analysis</TD>
<TD>Medford, Michael S.; Nugent, Peter; Goldstein, Danny; Masci, Frank J.; Andreoni, Igor; Beck, Ron; Coughlin, Michael W.; Duev, Dmitry A.; Mahabal, Ashish A.; Riddle, Reed L.</TD>
<TD>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 133, Issue 1024, id.064503, 14 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021PASP..133f4503M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021PASJ...73..753T</TD>
<TD>Spectroscopic and photometric observations of dwarf nova superoutbursts by the 3.8 m telescope Seimei and the Variable Star Network</TD>
<TD>Tampo, Yusuke; Isogai, Keisuke; Kojiguchi, Naoto; Maehara, Hiroyuki; Taguchi, Kenta; Kato, Taichi; Kimura, Mariko; Wakamatsu, Yasuyuki; Shibata, Masaaki; Nogami, Daisaku; Kawabata, Miho; Maeda, Keiichi; Namekata, Kosuke; Okamoto, Soshi; Otsuka, Masaaki; Burgaz, Umut; Nagoshi, Shumpei; Itoh, Hiroshi; Vanmunster, Tonny; Tordai, Tamás; Stone, Geoffrey; Matsumoto, Katsura; Fujii, Daiti; Matsumura, Ryota; Nakagawa, Momoka; Takeuchi, Nodoka; Zenkou, Yuki; Pavlenko, Elena P.; Antonyuk, Kirill A.; Pit, Nikolaj V.; Antonyuk, Oksana I.; Babina, Julia V.; Baklanov, Aleksei V.; Sosnovskij, Aleksei A.; Shugarov, Sergey Yu; Katysheva, Nataly; Chochol, Drahomír; Dvorak, Shawn; Dubovsky, Pavol A.; Medulka, Tomáš; Kudzej, Igor; Kiyota, Seiichiro; Zubareva, Alexandra M.; Belinski, Alexandr A.; Ikonnikova, Natalia P.; Burlak, Marina A.; Sano, Yasuo; Mizutani, Masanori; Ruiz, Javier; Pickard, Roger D.; Hambsch, Franz-Josef; Dufoer, Sjoerd; Brincat, Stephen M.; Galdies, Charles; Menzies, Kenneth; Moriyama, Masayuki; Hiraga, Mitsutaka; Maeda, Yutaka; Hirosawa, Kenji; Funada, Masao; Yamamoto, Minoru</TD>
<TD>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Volume 73, Issue 3, pp.753-771</TD>
<TD>2021-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021PASJ...73..753T</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021PASA...38...25M</TD>
<TD>Processing GOTO survey data with the Rubin Observatory LSST Science Pipelines II: Forced Photometry and lightcurves</TD>
<TD>Makrygianni, L.; Mullaney, J.; Dhillon, V.; Littlefair, S.; Ackley, K.; Dyer, M. J.; Lyman, J.; Ulaczyk, K.; Cutter, R.; Mong, Y. -L.; Steeghs, D.; Galloway, D. K.; O'Brien, P.; Ramsay, G.; Poshyachinda, S.; Kotak, R.; Nuttall, L.; Pallé, E.; Pollacco, D.; Thrane, E.; Aukkaravittayapun, S.; Awiphan, S.; Breton, R. P.; Burhanudin, U.; Chote, P.; Chrimes, A.; Daw, E.; Duffy, C.; Eyles-Ferris, R.; Gompertz, B.; Heikkilä, T.; Irawati, P.; Kennedy, M.; Killestein, T.; Levan, A.; Marsh, T.; Mata-Sanchez, D.; Mattila, S.; Maund, J.; McCormac, J.; Mkrtichian, D.; Rol, E.; Sawangwit, U.; Stanway, E.; Starling, R.; Strøm, P. A.; Tooke, S.; Wiersema, K.</TD>
<TD>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Australia, Volume 38, article id. e025</TD>
<TD>2021-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021PASA...38...25M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021Obs...141..138.</TD>
<TD>Book reviews</TD>
<TD />
<TD>The Observatory, Vol. 141, pp. 138-158</TD>
<TD>2021-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021Obs...141..138.</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021NewAR..9201614C</TD>
<TD>Gamma-ray burst jets in supernovae</TD>
<TD>Corsi, Alessandra; Lazzati, Davide</TD>
<TD>New Astronomy Reviews, Volume 92, article id. 101614.</TD>
<TD>2021-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021NewAR..9201614C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021Natur.595...39C</TD>
<TD>A highly magnetized and rapidly rotating white dwarf as small as the Moon</TD>
<TD>Caiazzo, Ilaria; Burdge, Kevin B.; Fuller, James; Heyl, Jeremy; Kulkarni, S. R.; Prince, Thomas A.; Richer, Harvey B.; Schwab, Josiah; Andreoni, Igor; Bellm, Eric C.; Drake, Andrew; Duev, Dmitry A.; Graham, Matthew J.; Helou, George; Mahabal, Ashish A.; Masci, Frank J.; Smith, Roger; Soumagnac, Maayane T.</TD>
<TD>Nature, Volume 595, Issue 7865, p.39-42</TD>
<TD>2021-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021Natur.595...39C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021NatAs...5..544T</TD>
<TD>Infrared spectropolarimetric detection of intrinsic polarization from a core-collapse supernova</TD>
<TD>Tinyanont, Samaporn; Millar-Blanchaer, Maxwell; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Mawet, Dimitri; Leonard, Douglas C.; Bulla, Mattia; De, Kishalay; Jovanovic, Nemanja; Hankins, Matthew; Vasisht, Gautam; Serabyn, Eugene</TD>
<TD>Nature Astronomy, Volume 5, p. 544-551</TD>
<TD>2021-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021NatAs...5..544T</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.504.2822A</TD>
<TD>Optimizing serendipitous detections of kilonovae: cadence and filter selection</TD>
<TD>Almualla, Mouza; Anand, Shreya; Coughlin, Michael W.; Dietrich, Tim; Guessoum, Nidhal; Sagués Carracedo, Ana; Ahumada, Tomás; Andreoni, Igor; Antier, Sarah; Bellm, Eric C.; Bulla, Mattia; Singer, Leo P.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 504, Issue 2, pp.2822-2831</TD>
<TD>2021-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.504.2822A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.504.2535I</TD>
<TD>The first Hubble diagram and cosmological constraints using superluminous supernovae</TD>
<TD>Inserra, C.; Sullivan, M.; Angus, C. R.; Macaulay, E.; Nichol, R. C.; Smith, M.; Frohmaier, C.; Gutiérrez, C. P.; Vicenzi, M.; Möller, A.; Brout, D.; Brown, P. J.; Davis, T. M.; D'Andrea, C. B.; Galbany, L.; Kessler, R.; Kim, A. G.; Pan, Y. -C.; Pursiainen, M.; Scolnic, D.; Thomas, B. P.; Wiseman, P.; Abbott, T. M. C.; Annis, J.; Avila, S.; Bertin, E.; Brooks, D.; Burke, D. L.; Carnero Rosell, A.; Carrasco Kind, M.; Carretero, J.; Castander, F. J.; Cawthon, R.; Desai, S.; Diehl, H. T.; Eifler, T. F.; Finley, D. A.; Flaugher, B.; Fosalba, P.; Frieman, J.; Garcia-Bellido, J.; Gaztanaga, E.; Gerdes, D. W.; Giannantonio, T.; Gruen, D.; Gruendl, R. A.; Gschwend, J.; Gutierrez, G.; Hollowood, D. L.; Honscheid, K.; James, D. J.; Krause, E.; Kuehn, K.; Kuropatkin, N.; Li, T. S.; Lidman, C.; Lima, M.; Maia, M. A. G.; Marshall, J. L.; Martini, P.; Menanteau, F.; Miquel, R.; Plazas Malagón, A. A.; Romer, A. K.; Roodman, A.; Sako, M.; Sanchez, E.; Scarpine, V.; Schubnell, M.; Serrano, S.; Sevilla-Noarbe, I.; Soares-Santos, M.; Sobreira, F.; Suchyta, E.; Swanson, M. E. C.; Tarle, G.; Thomas, D.; Tucker, D. L.; Vikram, V.; Walker, A. R.; Zhang, Y.; Asorey, J.; Calcino, J.; Carollo, D.; Glazebrook, K.; Hinton, S. R.; Hoormann, J. K.; Lewis, G. F.; Sharp, R.; Swann, E.; Tucker, B. E.; DES Collaboration</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 504, Issue 2, pp.2535-2549</TD>
<TD>2021-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.504.2535I</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.504.2420I</TD>
<TD>Towards a volumetric census of close white dwarf binaries - I. Reference samples</TD>
<TD>Inight, K.; Gänsicke, Boris T.; Breedt, E.; Marsh, T. R.; Pala, A. F.; Raddi, R.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 504, Issue 2, pp.2420-2442</TD>
<TD>2021-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.504.2420I</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.504.2073K</TD>
<TD>A cool and inflated progenitor candidate for the Type Ib supernova 2019yvr at 2.6 yr before explosion</TD>
<TD>Kilpatrick, Charles D.; Drout, Maria R.; Auchettl, Katie; Dimitriadis, Georgios; Foley, Ryan J.; Jones, David O.; DeMarchi, Lindsay; French, K. Decker; Gall, Christa; Hjorth, Jens; Jacobson-Galán, Wynn V.; Margutti, Raffaella; Piro, Anthony L.; Ramirez-Ruiz, Enrico; Rest, Armin; Rojas-Bravo, César</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 504, Issue 2, pp.2073-2093</TD>
<TD>2021-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.504.2073K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.504.1294S</TD>
<TD>Detectability of kilonovae in optical surveys: post-mortem examination of the LVC O3 run follow-up</TD>
<TD>Sagués Carracedo, A.; Bulla, M.; Feindt, U.; Goobar, A.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 504, Issue 1, pp.1294-1303</TD>
<TD>2021-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.504.1294S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.504..792C</TD>
<TD>Accretion disc cooling and narrow absorption lines in the tidal disruption event AT 2019dsg</TD>
<TD>Cannizzaro, G.; Wevers, T.; Jonker, P. G.; Pérez-Torres, M. A.; Moldon, J.; Mata-Sánchez, D.; Leloudas, G.; Pasham, D. R.; Mattila, S.; Arcavi, I.; Decker French, K.; Onori, F.; Inserra, C.; Nicholl, M.; Gromadzki, M.; Chen, T. -W.; Müller-Bravo, T. E.; Short, P.; Anderson, J. P.; Young, D. R.; Gendreau, K. C.; Arzoumanian, Z.; Löwenstein, M.; Remillard, R.; Roy, R.; Hiramatsu, D.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 504, Issue 1, pp.792-815</TD>
<TD>2021-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.504..792C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.504..543B</TD>
<TD>On the AGN nature of broad balmer emission in four low-redshift metal-poor galaxies</TD>
<TD>Burke, Colin J.; Liu, Xin; Chen, Yu-Ching; Shen, Yue; Guo, Hengxiao</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 504, Issue 1, pp.543-550</TD>
<TD>2021-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.504..543B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.504..185N</TD>
<TD>Dipper-like variability of the Gaia alerted young star V555 Ori</TD>
<TD>Nagy, Zsófia; Szegedi-Elek, Elza; Ábrahám, Péter; Kóspál, Ágnes; Bódi, Attila; Bouvier, Jérôme; Kun, Mária; Moór, Attila; Cseh, Borbála; Farkas-Takács, Anikó; Hanyecz, Ottó; Hodgkin, Simon; Ignácz, Bernadett; Kiss, Csaba; Könyves-Tóth, Réka; Kriskovics, Levente; Marton, Gábor; Mészáros, László; Ordasi, András; Pál, András; Sarkis, Paula; Sárneczky, Krisztián; Sódor, Ádám; Szabados, László; Szabó, Zsófia Marianna; Szakáts, Róbert; Tarczay-Nehéz, Dóra; Vida, Krisztián; Zsidi, Gabriella</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 504, Issue 1, pp.185-198</TD>
<TD>2021-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.504..185N</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.503.5997P</TD>
<TD>No velocity-kicks are required to explain large-distance offsets of Ca-rich supernovae and short-GRBs</TD>
<TD>Perets, Hagai B.; Beniamini, Paz</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 503, Issue 4, pp.5997-6004</TD>
<TD>2021-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.503.5997P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.503.4734P</TD>
<TD>Thermonuclear explosion of a massive hybrid HeCO white dwarf triggered by a He detonation on a companion</TD>
<TD>Pakmor, R.; Zenati, Y.; Perets, H. B.; Toonen, S.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 503, Issue 4, pp.4734-4747</TD>
<TD>2021-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.503.4734P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021JPhG...48f0501A</TD>
<TD>IceCube-Gen2: the window to the extreme Universe</TD>
<TD>Aartsen, M. G.; Abbasi, R.; Ackermann, M.; Adams, J.; Aguilar, J. A.; Ahlers, M.; Ahrens, M.; Alispach, C.; Allison, P.; Amin, N. M.; Andeen, K.; Anderson, T.; Ansseau, I.; Anton, G.; Argüelles, C.; Arlen, T. C.; Auffenberg, J.; Axani, S.; Bagherpour, H.; Bai, X.; Balagopal V, A.; Barbano, A.; Bartos, I.; Bastian, B.; Basu, V.; Baum, V.; Baur, S.; Bay, R.; Beatty, J. J.; Becker, K. -H.; Tjus, J. Becker; BenZvi, S.; Berley, D.; Bernardini, E.; Besson, D. Z.; Binder, G.; Bindig, D.; Blaufuss, E.; Blot, S.; Bohm, C.; Bohmer, M.; Böser, S.; Botner, O.; Böttcher, J.; Bourbeau, E.; Bourbeau, J.; Bradascio, F.; Braun, J.; Bron, S.; Brostean-Kaiser, J.; Burgman, A.; Burley, R. T.; Buscher, J.; Busse, R. S.; Bustamante, M.; Campana, M. A.; Carnie-Bronca, E. G.; Carver, T.; Chen, C.; Chen, P.; Cheung, E.; Chirkin, D.; Choi, S.; Clark, B. A.; Clark, K.; Classen, L.; Coleman, A.; Collin, G. H.; Connolly, A.; Conrad, J. M.; Coppin, P.; Correa, P.; Cowen, D. F.; Cross, R.; Dave, P.; Deaconu, C.; De Clercq, C.; DeLaunay, J. J.; De Kockere, S.; Dembinski, H.; Deoskar, K.; De Ridder, S.; Desai, A.; Desiati, P.; de Vries, K. D.; de Wasseige, G.; de With, M.; DeYoung, T.; Dharani, S.; Diaz, A.; Díaz-Vélez, J. C.; Dujmovic, H.; Dunkman, M.; DuVernois, M. A.; Dvorak, E.; Ehrhardt, T.; Eller, P.; Engel, R.; Evans, J. J.; Evenson, P. A.; Fahey, S.; Farrag, K.; Fazely, A. R.; Felde, J.; Fienberg, A. T.; Filimonov, K.; Finley, C.; Fischer, L.; Fox, D.; Franckowiak, A.; Friedman, E.; Fritz, A.; Gaisser, T. K.; Gallagher, J.; Ganster, E.; Garcia-Fernandez, D.; Garrappa, S.; Gartner, A.; Gerhard, L.; Gernhaeuser, R.; Ghadimi, A.; Glaser, C.; Glauch, T.; Glüsenkamp, T.; Goldschmidt, A.; Gonzalez, J. G.; Goswami, S.; Grant, D.; Grégoire, T.; Griffith, Z.; Griswold, S.; Gündüz, M.; Haack, C.; Hallgren, A.; Halliday, R.; Halve, L.; Halzen, F.; Hanson, J. C.; Hanson, K.; Hardin, J.; Haugen, J.; Haungs, A.; Hauser, S.; Hebecker, D.; Heinen, D.; Heix, P.; Helbing, K.; Hellauer, R.; Henningsen, F.; Hickford, S.; Hignight, J.; Hill, C.; Hill, G. C.; Hoffman, K. D.; Hoffmann, B.; Hoffmann, R.; Hoinka, T.; Hokanson-Fasig, B.; Holzapfel, K.; Hoshina, K.; Huang, F.; Huber, M.; Huber, T.; Huege, T.; Hughes, K.; Hultqvist, K.; Hünnefeld, M.; Hussain, R.; In, S.; Iovine, N.; Ishihara, A.; Jansson, M.; Japaridze, G. S.; Jeong, M.; Jones, B. J. P.; Jonske, F.; Joppe, R.; Kalekin, O.; Kang, D.; Kang, W.; Kang, X.; Kappes, A.; Kappesser, D.; Karg, T.; Karl, M.; Karle, A.; Katori, T.; Katz, U.; Kauer, M.; Keivani, A.; Kellermann, M.; Kelley, J. L.; Kheirandish, A.; Kim, J.; Kin, K.; Kintscher, T.; Kiryluk, J.; Kittler, T.; Kleifges, M.; Klein, S. R.; Koirala, R.; Kolanoski, H.; Köpke, L.; Kopper, C.; Kopper, S.; Koskinen, D. J.; Koundal, P.; Kovacevich, M.; Kowalski, M.; Krauss, C. B.; Krings, K.; Krückl, G.; Kulacz, N.; Kurahashi, N.; Gualda, C. Lagunas; Lahmann, R.; Lanfranchi, J. L.; Larson, M. J.; Latif, U.; Lauber, F.; Lazar, J. P.; Leonard, K.; Leszczyńska, A.; Li, Y.; Liu, Q. R.; Lohfink, E.; LoSecco, J.; Mariscal, C. J. Lozano; Lu, L.; Lucarelli, F.; Ludwig, A.; Lünemann, J.; Luszczak, W.; Lyu, Y.; Ma, W. Y.; Madsen, J.; Maggi, G.; Mahn, K. B. M.; Makino, Y.; Mallik, P.; Mancina, S.; Mandalia, S.; Mariş, I. C.; Marka, S.; Marka, Z.; Maruyama, R.; Mase, K.; Maunu, R.; McNally, F.; Meagher, K.; Medina, A.; Meier, M.; Meighen-Berger, S.; Merz, J.; Meyers, Z. S.; Micallef, J.; Mockler, D.; Momenté, G.; Montaruli, T.; Moore, R. W.; Morse, R.; Moulai, M.; Muth, P.; Naab, R.; Nagai, R.; Nam, J.; Nauman, U.; Necker, J.; Neer, G.; Nelles, A.; Nguyễn, L. V.; Niederhausen, H.; Nisa, M. U.; Nowicki, S. C.; Nygren, D. R.; Oberla, E.; Pollmann, A. Obertacke; Oehler, M.; Olivas, A.; O'Sullivan, E.; Pan, Y.; Pandya, H.; Pankova, D. V.; Papp, L.; Park, N.; Parker, G. K.; Paudel, E. N.; Peiffer, P.; Pérez de los Heros, C.; Petersen, T. C.; Philippen, S.; Pieloth, D.; Pieper, S.; Pinfold, J. L.; Pizzuto, A.; Plaisier, I.; Plum, M.; Popovych, Y.; Porcelli, A.; Rodriguez, M. Prado; Price, P. B.; Przybylski, G. T.; Raab, C.; Raissi, A.; Rameez, M.; Rauch, L.; Rawlins, K.; Rea, I. C.; Rehman, A.; Reimann, R.; Renschler, M.; Renzi, G.; Resconi, E.; Reusch, S.; Rhode, W.; Richman, M.; Riedel, B.; Riegel, M.; Roberts, E. J.; Robertson, S.; Roellinghoff, G.; Rongen, M.; Rott, C.; Ruhe, T.; Ryckbosch, D.; Cantu, D. Rysewyk; Safa, I.; Herrera, S. E. Sanchez; Sandrock, A.; Sandroos, J.; Sandstrom, P.; Santander, M.; Sarkar, S.; Sarkar, S.; Satalecka, K.; Scharf, M.; Schaufel, M.; Schieler, H.; Schlunder, P.; Schmidt, T.; Schneider, A.; Schneider, J.; Schröder, F. G.; Schumacher, L.; Sclafani, S.; Seckel, D.; Seunarine, S.; Shaevitz, M. H.; Sharma, A.; Shefali, S.; Silva, M.; Smith, D.; Smithers, B.; Snihur, R.; Soedingrekso, J.; Soldin, D.; Söldner-Rembold, S.; Song, M.; Southall, D.; Spiczak, G. M.; Spiering, C.; Stachurska, J.; Stamatikos, M.; Stanev, T.; Stein, R.; Stettner, J.; Steuer, A.; Stezelberger, T.; Stokstad, R. G.; Strotjohann, N. L.; Stürwald, T.; Stuttard, T.; Sullivan, G. W.; Taboada, I.; Taketa, A.; Tanaka, H. K. M.; Tenholt, F.; Ter-Antonyan, S.; Terliuk, A.; Tilav, S.; Tollefson, K.; Tomankova, L.; Tönnis, C.; Torres, J.; Toscano, S.; Tosi, D.; Trettin, A.; Tselengidou, M.; Tung, C. F.; Turcati, A.; Turcotte, R.; Turley, C. F.; Twagirayezu, J. P.; Ty, B.; Unger, E.; Elorrieta, M. A. Unland; Vandenbroucke, J.; van Eijk, D.; van Eijndhoven, N.; Vannerom, D.; van Santen, J.; Veberic, D.; Verpoest, S.; Vieregg, A.; Vraeghe, M.; Walck, C.; Watson, T. B.; Weaver, C.; Weindl, A.; Weinstock, L.; Weiss, M. J.; Weldert, J.; Welling, C.; Wendt, C.; Werthebach, J.; Whitehorn, N.; Wiebe, K.; Wiebusch, C. H.; Williams, D. R.; Wissel, S. A.; Wolf, M.; Wood, T. R.; Woschnagg, K.; Wrede, G.; Wren, S.; Wulff, J.; Xu, X. W.; Xu, Y.; Yanez, J. P.; Yoshida, S.; Yuan, T.; Zhang, Z.; Zierke, S.; Zöcklein, M.</TD>
<TD>Journal of Physics G: Nuclear and Particle Physics, Volume 48, Issue 6, id.060501, 72 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021JPhG...48f0501A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ExA...tmp...61H</TD>
<TD>MeerCRAB: MeerLICHT classification of real and bogus transients using deep learning</TD>
<TD>Hosenie, Zafiirah; Bloemen, Steven; Groot, Paul; Lyon, Robert; Scheers, Bart; Stappers, Benjamin; Stoppa, Fiorenzo; Vreeswijk, Paul; De Wet, Simon; Wolt, Marc Klein; Körding, Elmar; McBride, Vanessa; Le Poole, Rudolf; Paterson, Kerry; Pieterse, Daniëlle L. A.; Woudt, Patrick</TD>
<TD>Experimental Astronomy, Online First</TD>
<TD>2021-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ExA...tmp...61H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021CoSka..51..138P</TD>
<TD>MASTER OT J172758.09+380021.5: a peculiar ER UMa-type dwarf nova, probably a missed nova in the recent past</TD>
<TD>Pavlenko, E.; Kato, T.; Antonyuk, K.; Pit, N.; Keir, L.; Udovichenko, S.; Dubovský, P.; Sosnovskij, A.; Antonyuk, O.; Shimansky, V.; Gabdeev, M.; Rakhmatullaeva, F.; Kokhirova, G.; Belan, S.; Simon, A.; Baklanov, A.; Kojiguchi, N.; Godunova, V.</TD>
<TD>Contributions of the Astronomical Observatory Skalnaté Pleso, vol. 51, no. 2, p. 138-162.</TD>
<TD>2021-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021CoSka..51..138P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021CoSka..51..132A</TD>
<TD>New SU UMa-type star ZTF18abdlzhd in the Zwicky Transient Facility data</TD>
<TD>Antipin, S. V.; Zubareva, A. M.; Belinski, A. A.; Burlak, M. A.; Ikonnikova, N. P.; Malanchev, K. L.; Kornilov, M. V.; Mishin, E. O.</TD>
<TD>Contributions of the Astronomical Observatory Skalnaté Pleso, vol. 51, no. 2, p. 132-137.</TD>
<TD>2021-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021CoSka..51..132A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJS..254...33K</TD>
<TD>SPICY: The Spitzer/IRAC Candidate YSO Catalog for the Inner Galactic Midplane</TD>
<TD>Kuhn, Michael A.; de Souza, Rafael S.; Krone-Martins, Alberto; Castro-Ginard, Alfred; Ishida, Emille E. O.; Povich, Matthew S.; Hillenbrand, Lynne A.; COIN Collaboration</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 254, Issue 2, id.33, 31 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJS..254...33K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...914L..34P</TD>
<TD>Do LIGO/Virgo Black Hole Mergers Produce AGN Flares? The Case of GW190521 and Prospects for Reaching a Confident Association</TD>
<TD>Palmese, A.; Fishbach, M.; Burke, C. J.; Annis, J.; Liu, X.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 914, Issue 2, id.L34, 10 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...914L..34P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...914L..19Z</TD>
<TD>Thermonuclear Explosions and Accretion-induced Collapses of White Dwarfs in Active Galactic Nucleus Accretion Disks</TD>
<TD>Zhu, Jin-Ping; Yang, Yuan-Pei; Zhang, Bing; Liu, Liang-Duan; Yu, Yun-Wei; Gao, He</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 914, Issue 1, id.L19, 9 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...914L..19Z</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...914..127I</TD>
<TD>The Gaia-ASAS-SN Classical Cepheid Sample. I. Sample Selection</TD>
<TD>Inno, Laura; Rix, Hans-Walter; Stanek, K. Z.; Jayasinghe, T.; Poggio, E.; Drimmel, R.; Rotundi, A.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 914, Issue 2, id.127, 16 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...914..127I</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...914...69C</TD>
<TD>Light Curves of Partial Tidal Disruption Events</TD>
<TD>Chen, Jin-Hong; Shen, Rong-Feng</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 914, Issue 1, id.69, 12 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...914...69C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...914...50T</TD>
<TD>SN 2019yvq Does Not Conform to SN Ia Explosion Models</TD>
<TD>Tucker, M. A.; Ashall, C.; Shappee, B. J.; Vallely, P. J.; Kochanek, C. S.; Huber, M. E.; Anand, G. S.; Keane, J. V.; Hsiao, E. Y.; Holoien, T. W. -S.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 914, Issue 1, id.50, 14 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...914...50T</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...913..143G</TD>
<TD>The Luminous and Double-peaked Type Ic Supernova 2019stc: Evidence for Multiple Energy Sources</TD>
<TD>Gomez, Sebastian; Berger, Edo; Hosseinzadeh, Griffin; Blanchard, Peter K.; Nicholl, Matt; Villar, V. Ashley</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 913, Issue 2, id.143, 14 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...913..143G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...913..118R</TD>
<TD>Minimum Orbital Periods of H-rich Bodies</TD>
<TD>Rappaport, S.; Vanderburg, A.; Schwab, J.; Nelson, L.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 913, Issue 2, id.118, 7 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...913..118R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...913..102W</TD>
<TD>AGNs on the Move: A Search for Off-nuclear AGNs from Recoiling Supermassive Black Holes and Ongoing Galaxy Mergers with the Zwicky Transient Facility</TD>
<TD>Ward, Charlotte; Gezari, Suvi; Frederick, Sara; Hammerstein, Erica; Nugent, Peter; van Velzen, Sjoert; Drake, Andrew; García-Pérez, Abigail; Oyoo, Immaculate; Bellm, Eric C.; Duev, Dmitry A.; Graham, Matthew J.; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Kaye, Stephen; Mahabal, Ashish A.; Masci, Frank J.; Rusholme, Ben; Soumagnac, Maayane T.; Yan, Lin</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 913, Issue 2, id.102, 25 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...913..102W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021AJ....161..267V</TD>
<TD>The ZTF Source Classification Project. I. Methods and Infrastructure</TD>
<TD>van Roestel, Jan; Duev, Dmitry A.; Mahabal, Ashish A.; Coughlin, Michael W.; Mróz, Przemek; Burdge, Kevin; Drake, Andrew; Graham, Matthew J.; Hillenbrand, Lynne; Bellm, Eric C.; Kupfer, Thomas; Delacroix, Alexandre; Fremling, C.; Golkhou, V. Zach; Hale, David; Laher, Russ R.; Masci, Frank J.; Riddle, Reed; Rosnet, Philippe; Rusholme, Ben; Smith, Roger; Soumagnac, Maayane T.; Walters, Richard; Prince, Thomas A.; Kulkarni, S. R.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 161, Issue 6, id.267, 17 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021AJ....161..267V</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021A&amp;A...650A.174T</TD>
<TD>SN 2018ijp: the explosion of a stripped-envelope star within a dense H-rich shell?</TD>
<TD>Tartaglia, L.; Sollerman, J.; Barbarino, C.; Taddia, F.; Mason, E.; Berton, M.; Taggart, K.; Bellm, E. C.; De, K.; Frederick, S.; Fremling, C.; Gal-Yam, A.; Golkhou, V. Z.; Graham, M.; Ho, A. Y. Q.; Hung, T.; Kaye, S.; Kim, Y. -L.; Laher, R. R.; Masci, F. J.; Perley, D. A.; Porter, M. D.; Reiley, D. J.; Riddle, R.; Rusholme, B.; Soumagnac, M. T.; Walters, R.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 650, id.A174, 11 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021A&amp;A...650A.174T</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021A&amp;A...650A.146M</TD>
<TD>A search for distant, pulsating red giants in the southern halo</TD>
<TD>Mauron, N.; Gigoyan, K. S.; Kendall, T. R.; Hambleton, K. M.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 650, id.A146, 8 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021A&amp;A...650A.146M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021PhRvD.103j3529B</TD>
<TD>Spectral separation of the stochastic gravitational-wave background for LISA: Observing both cosmological and astrophysical backgrounds</TD>
<TD>Boileau, Guillaume; Christensen, Nelson; Meyer, Renate; Cornish, Neil J.</TD>
<TD>Physical Review D, Volume 103, Issue 10, article id.103529</TD>
<TD>2021-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021PhRvD.103j3529B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021PTEP.2021eA104S</TD>
<TD>J-GEM optical and near-infrared follow-up of gravitational wave events during LIGO's and Virgo's third observing run</TD>
<TD>Sasada, Mahito; Utsumi, Yousuke; Itoh, Ryosuke; Tominaga, Nozomu; Tanaka, Masaomi; Morokuma, Tomoki; Yanagisawa, Kenshi; Kawabata, Koji S.; Ohgami, Takayuki; Yoshida, Michitoshi; Abe, Fumio; Adachi, Ryo; Akitaya, Hiroshi; Chong, Yang; Daikuhara, Kazuki; Hamasaki, Ryo; Honda, Satoshi; Hosokawa, Ryohei; Iida, Kota; Imazato, Fumiya; Ishioka, Chihiro; Iwasaki, Takumi; Jian, Mingjie; Kamei, Yuhei; Kanai, Takahiro; Kaneda, Hidehiro; Kaneko, Ayane; Katoh, Noriyuki; Kawai, Nobuyuki; Kubota, Keiichiro; Kubota, Yuma; Mamiya, Hideo; Matsubayashi, Kazuya; Morihana, Kumiko; Murata, Katsuhiro L.; Nagayama, Takahiro; Nakamura, Noriatsu; Nakaoka, Tatsuya; Niino, Yuu; Nishinaka, Yuki; Niwano, Masafumi; Nogami, Daisaku; Oasa, Yumiko; Oeda, Miki; Ogawa, Futa; Ohsawa, Ryou; Ohta, Kouji; Oide, Kohei; Onozato, Hiroki; Sako, Shigeyuki; Saito, Tomoki; Sekiguchi, Yuichiro; Shigeyama, Toshikazu; Shigeyoshi, Takumi; Shikauchi, Minori; Shiraishi, Kazuki; Suzuki, Daisuke; Takagi, Kengo; Takahashi, Jun; Takarada, Takuya; Takayama, Masaki; Takeuchi, Himeka; Tamura, Yasuki; Tanaka, Ryoya; Toma, Sayaka; Tozuka, Miyako; Uchida, Nagomi; Uzawa, Yoshinori; Yamanaka, Masayuki; Yasuda, Moeno; Yatsu, Yoichi</TD>
<TD>Progress of Theoretical and Experimental Physics, Volume 2021, Issue 5, id.05A104, 23 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021PTEP.2021eA104S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021PASP..133e4502M</TD>
<TD>A Morphological Classification Model to Identify Unresolved PanSTARRS1 Sources. II. Update to the PS1 Point Source Catalog</TD>
<TD>Miller, A. A.; Hall, X. J.</TD>
<TD>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 133, Issue 1023, id.054502, 10 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021PASP..133e4502M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021PASA...38...24C</TD>
<TD>SkyMapper optical follow-up of gravitational wave triggers: Alert science data pipeline and LIGO/Virgo O3 run</TD>
<TD>Chang, Seo-Won; Onken, Christopher A.; Wolf, Christian; Luvaul, Lance; Möller, Anais; Scalzo, Richard; Schmidt, Brian P.; Scott, Susan M.; Sura, Nikunj; Yuan, Fang</TD>
<TD>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Australia, Volume 38, article id. e024</TD>
<TD>2021-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021PASA...38...24C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021OptMa.11511028A</TD>
<TD>Optical and electrical correlation effects in ZnO nanostructures: Role of pulsed laser annealing</TD>
<TD>Al-Asedy, Hayder J.; Al-khafaji, Shuruq A.; Ghoshal, S. K.</TD>
<TD>Optical Materials, Volume 115, article id. 111028.</TD>
<TD>2021-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021OptMa.11511028A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021OEJV..216....1N</TD>
<TD>Search for period changes in Mira stars</TD>
<TD>Nesci, R.; Rocchi, G.</TD>
<TD>Open European Journal on Variable stars, Vol. 216, p. 1-12.</TD>
<TD>2021-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021OEJV..216....1N</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021NatAs...5..472W</TD>
<TD>A concordance scenario for the observed neutrino from a tidal disruption event</TD>
<TD>Winter, Walter; Lunardini, Cecilia</TD>
<TD>Nature Astronomy, Volume 5, p. 472-477</TD>
<TD>2021-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021NatAs...5..472W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.503.4838K</TD>
<TD>Transient-optimized real-bogus classification with Bayesian convolutional neural networks - sifting the GOTO candidate stream</TD>
<TD>Killestein, T. L.; Lyman, J.; Steeghs, D.; Ackley, K.; Dyer, M. J.; Ulaczyk, K.; Cutter, R.; Mong, Y. -L.; Galloway, D. K.; Dhillon, V.; O'Brien, P.; Ramsay, G.; Poshyachinda, S.; Kotak, R.; Breton, R. P.; Nuttall, L. K.; Pallé, E.; Pollacco, D.; Thrane, E.; Aukkaravittayapun, S.; Awiphan, S.; Burhanudin, U.; Chote, P.; Chrimes, A.; Daw, E.; Duffy, C.; Eyles-Ferris, R.; Gompertz, B.; Heikkilä, T.; Irawati, P.; Kennedy, M. R.; Levan, A.; Littlefair, S.; Makrygianni, L.; Mata Sánchez, D.; Mattila, S.; Maund, J.; McCormac, J.; Mkrtichian, D.; Mullaney, J.; Rol, E.; Sawangwit, U.; Stanway, E.; Starling, R.; Strøm, P. A.; Tooke, S.; Wiersema, K.; Williams, S. C.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 503, Issue 4, pp.4838-4854</TD>
<TD>2021-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.503.4838K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.503.3975P</TD>
<TD>Variability, periodicity, and contact binaries in WISE</TD>
<TD>Petrosky, Evan; Hwang, Hsiang-Chih; Zakamska, Nadia L.; Chandra, Vedant; Hill, Matthew J.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 503, Issue 3, pp.3975-3991</TD>
<TD>2021-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.503.3975P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.503.3931T</TD>
<TD>Core-collapse, superluminous, and gamma-ray burst supernova host galaxy populations at low redshift: the importance of dwarf and starbursting galaxies</TD>
<TD>Taggart, K.; Perley, D. A.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 503, Issue 3, pp.3931-3952</TD>
<TD>2021-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.503.3931T</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.503.2966R</TD>
<TD>An early peak in the radio light curve of short-duration gamma-ray burst 200826A</TD>
<TD>Rhodes, Lauren; Fender, Rob; Williams, David R. A.; Mooley, Kunal</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 503, Issue 2, pp.2966-2972</TD>
<TD>2021-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.503.2966R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.503.2665K</TD>
<TD>GPU-accelerated periodic source identification in large-scale surveys: measuring P and P</TD>
<TD>Katz, Michael L.; Cooper, Olivia R.; Coughlin, Michael W.; Burdge, Kevin B.; Breivik, Katelyn; Larson, Shane L.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 503, Issue 2, pp.2665-2675</TD>
<TD>2021-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.503.2665K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.503.1703I</TD>
<TD>A self-lensing binary massive black hole interpretation of quasi-periodic eruptions</TD>
<TD>Ingram, Adam; Motta, Sara E.; Aigrain, Suzanne; Karastergiou, Aris</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 503, Issue 2, pp.1703-1716</TD>
<TD>2021-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.503.1703I</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.503.1646C</TD>
<TD>Horizontal spreading of planetary debris accreted by white dwarfs</TD>
<TD>Cunningham, Tim; Tremblay, Pier-Emmanuel; Bauer, Evan B.; Toloza, Odette; Cukanovaite, Elena; Koester, Detlev; Farihi, Jay; Freytag, Bernd; Gänsicke, Boris T.; Ludwig, Hans-Günter; Veras, Dimitri</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 503, Issue 2, pp.1646-1667</TD>
<TD>2021-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.503.1646C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.503..830S</TD>
<TD>Observational insights on the origin of giant low surface brightness galaxies</TD>
<TD>Saburova, Anna S.; Chilingarian, Igor V.; Kasparova, Anastasia V.; Sil'chenko, Olga K.; Grishin, Kirill A.; Katkov, Ivan Yu; Uklein, Roman I.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 503, Issue 1, pp.830-849</TD>
<TD>2021-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.503..830S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.503..312M</TD>
<TD>RINGO3 polarimetry of very young ZTF supernovae</TD>
<TD>Maund, J. R.; Yang, Y.; Steele, I. A.; Baade, D.; Jermak, H.; Schulze, S.; Bruch, R.; Gal-Yam, A.; Höflich, P. A.; Ofek, E.; Wang, X.; Amenouche, M.; Dekany, R.; Masci, F. J.; Riddle, R.; Soumagnac, M. T.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 503, Issue 1, pp.312-323</TD>
<TD>2021-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.503..312M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.503..200J</TD>
<TD>The ASAS-SN catalogue of variable stars IX: The spectroscopic properties of Galactic variable stars</TD>
<TD>Jayasinghe, T.; Kochanek, C. S.; Stanek, K. Z.; Shappee, B. J.; Holoien, T. W. -S.; Thompson, Todd A.; Prieto, J. L.; Dong, Subo; Pawlak, M.; Pejcha, O.; Pojmanski, G.; Otero, S.; Hurst, N.; Will, D.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 503, Issue 1, pp.200-235</TD>
<TD>2021-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.503..200J</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021JKPS...78..864R</TD>
<TD>Progress in neutrino astronomy</TD>
<TD>Rott, Carsten</TD>
<TD>Journal of the Korean Physical Society, Volume 78, Issue 10, p.864-872</TD>
<TD>2021-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021JKPS...78..864R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...913L...6N</TD>
<TD>Precovery Observations Confirm the Capture Time of Asteroid 2020 CD3 as Earth's Minimoon</TD>
<TD>Naidu, Shantanu P.; Micheli, Marco; Farnocchia, Davide; Roa, Javier; Fedorets, Grigori; Christensen, Eric; Weryk, Robert</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 913, Issue 1, id.L6, 5 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...913L...6N</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...912..128P</TD>
<TD>Searches after Gravitational Waves Using ARizona Observatories (SAGUARO): Observations and Analysis from Advanced LIGO/Virgo's Third Observing Run</TD>
<TD>Paterson, K.; Lundquist, M. J.; Rastinejad, J. C.; Fong, W.; Sand, D. J.; Andrews, J. E.; Amaro, R. C.; Eskandari, O.; Wyatt, S.; Daly, P. N.; Bradley, H.; Zhou-Wright, S.; Valenti, S.; Yang, S.; Christensen, E.; Gibbs, A. R.; Shelly, F.; Bilinski, C.; Chomiuk, L.; Corsi, A.; Drout, M. R.; Foley, R. J.; Gabor, P.; Garnavich, P.; Grier, C. J.; Hamden, E.; Krantz, H.; Olszewski, E.; Paschalidis, V.; Reichart, D.; Rest, A.; Smith, N.; Strader, J.; Trilling, D.; Veillet, C.; Wagner, R. M.; Weiner, B.; Zabludoff, A.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 912, Issue 2, id.128, 20 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...912..128P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...912..125G</TD>
<TD>I Spy Transits and Pulsations: Empirical Variability in White Dwarfs Using Gaia and the Zwicky Transient Facility</TD>
<TD>Guidry, Joseph A.; Vanderbosch, Zachary P.; Hermes, J. J.; Barlow, Brad N.; Lopez, Isaac D.; Boudreaux, Thomas M.; Corcoran, Kyle A.; Bell, Keaton J.; Montgomery, M. H.; Heintz, Tyler M.; Castanheira, Barbara G.; Reding, Joshua S.; Dunlap, Bart H.; Winget, D. E.; Winget, Karen I.; Kuehne, J. W.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 912, Issue 2, id.125, 24 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...912..125G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...912...46B</TD>
<TD>A Large Fraction of Hydrogen-rich Supernova Progenitors Experience Elevated Mass Loss Shortly Prior to Explosion</TD>
<TD>Bruch, Rachel J.; Gal-Yam, Avishay; Schulze, Steve; Yaron, Ofer; Yang, Yi; Soumagnac, Maayane; Rigault, Mickael; Strotjohann, Nora L.; Ofek, Eran; Sollerman, Jesper; Masci, Frank J.; Barbarino, Cristina; Ho, Anna Y. Q.; Fremling, Christoffer; Perley, Daniel; Nordin, Jakob; Cenko, S. Bradley; Adams, S.; Adreoni, Igor; Bellm, Eric C.; Blagorodnova, Nadia; Bulla, Mattia; Burdge, Kevin; De, Kishalay; Dhawan, Suhail; Drake, Andrew J.; Duev, Dmitry A.; Dugas, Alison; Graham, Matthew; Graham, Melissa L.; Irani, Ido; Jencson, Jacob; Karamehmetoglu, Emir; Kasliwal, Mansi; Kim, Young-Lo; Kulkarni, Shrinivas; Kupfer, Thomas; Liang, Jingyi; Mahabal, Ashish; Miller, A. A.; Prince, Thomas A.; Riddle, Reed; Sharma, Y.; Smith, Roger; Taddia, Francesco; Taggart, Kirsty; Walters, Richard; Yan, Lin</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 912, Issue 1, id.46, 20 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...912...46B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...912...21E</TD>
<TD>Late-time Radio and Millimeter Observations of Superluminous Supernovae and Long Gamma-Ray Bursts: Implications for Central Engines, Fast Radio Bursts, and Obscured Star Formation</TD>
<TD>Eftekhari, T.; Margalit, B.; Omand, C. M. B.; Berger, E.; Blanchard, P. K.; Demorest, P.; Metzger, B. D.; Murase, K.; Nicholl, M.; Villar, V. A.; Williams, P. K. G.; Alexander, K. D.; Chatterjee, S.; Coppejans, D. L.; Cordes, J. M.; Gomez, S.; Hosseinzadeh, G.; Hsu, B.; Kashiyama, K.; Margutti, R.; Yin, Y.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 912, Issue 1, id.21, 23 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...912...21E</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...912...20J</TD>
<TD>Probing the Disk-Corona Systems and Broad-line Regions of Changing-look Quasars with X-Ray and Optical Observations</TD>
<TD>Jin, Xiangyu; Ruan, John J.; Haggard, Daryl; Gingras, Marie-Joëlle; Hountalas, Joseph; MacLeod, Chelsea L.; Anderson, Scott F.; Doan, Anh; Eracleous, Michael; Green, Paul J.; Runnoe, Jessie C.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 912, Issue 1, id.20, 27 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...912...20J</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...912...19D</TD>
<TD>A Population of Heavily Reddened, Optically Missed Novae from Palomar Gattini-IR: Constraints on the Galactic Nova Rate</TD>
<TD>De, Kishalay; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Hankins, Matthew J.; Sokoloski, Jennifer L.; Adams, Scott M.; Ashley, Michael C. B.; Babul, Aliya-Nur; Bagdasaryan, Ashot; Delacroix, Alexandre; Dekany, Richard; Greffe, Timothée; Hale, David; Jencson, Jacob E.; Karambelkar, Viraj R.; Lau, Ryan M.; Mahabal, Ashish; McKenna, Daniel; Moore, Anna M.; Ofek, Eran O.; Sharma, Manasi; Smith, Roger M.; Soon, Jamie; Soria, Roberto; Srinivasaragavan, Gokul; Tinyanont, Samaporn; Travouillon, Tony; Tzanidakis, Anastasios; Yao, Yuhan</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 912, Issue 1, id.19, 20 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...912...19D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...912...14Y</TD>
<TD>Detectability of "Merger-nova" Emission from a Long-lived Magnetar in Short Gamma-Ray Bursts</TD>
<TD>Yuan, Yong; Lü, Hou-Jun; Yuan, Hao-Yu; Ma, Shuai-Bing; Lei, Wei-Hua; Liang, En-Wei</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 912, Issue 1, id.14, 10 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...912...14Y</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021AJ....161..242F</TD>
<TD>The Automatic Learning for the Rapid Classification of Events (ALeRCE) Alert Broker</TD>
<TD>Förster, F.; Cabrera-Vives, G.; Castillo-Navarrete, E.; Estévez, P. A.; Sánchez-Sáez, P.; Arredondo, J.; Bauer, F. E.; Carrasco-Davis, R.; Catelan, M.; Elorrieta, F.; Eyheramendy, S.; Huijse, P.; Pignata, G.; Reyes, E.; Reyes, I.; Rodríguez-Mancini, D.; Ruz-Mieres, D.; Valenzuela, C.; Álvarez-Maldonado, I.; Astorga, N.; Borissova, J.; Clocchiatti, A.; De Cicco, D.; Donoso-Oliva, C.; Hernández-García, L.; Graham, M. J.; Jordán, A.; Kurtev, R.; Mahabal, A.; Maureira, J. C.; Muñoz-Arancibia, A.; Molina-Ferreiro, R.; Moya, A.; Palma, W.; Pérez-Carrasco, M.; Protopapas, P.; Romero, M.; Sabatini-Gacitua, L.; Sánchez, A.; San Martín, J.; Sepúlveda-Cobo, C.; Vera, E.; Vergara, J. R.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 161, Issue 5, id.242, 28 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021AJ....161..242F</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021AJ....161..220H</TD>
<TD>Outbursting Young Stellar Object PGIR 20dci in the Perseus Arm</TD>
<TD>Hillenbrand, Lynne A.; De, Kishalay; Hankins, Matthew; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Rebull, Luisa M.; Lau, Ryan M.; Cutri, Roc M.; Ashley, Michael C. B.; Karambelkar, Viraj R.; Moore, Anna M.; Travouillon, T.; Mainzer, A. K.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 161, Issue 5, id.220, 11 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021AJ....161..220H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021AJ....161..218D</TD>
<TD>Tails: Chasing Comets with the Zwicky Transient Facility and Deep Learning</TD>
<TD>Duev, Dmitry A.; Bolin, Bryce T.; Graham, Matthew J.; Kelley, Michael S. P.; Mahabal, Ashish; Bellm, Eric C.; Coughlin, Michael W.; Dekany, Richard; Helou, George; Kulkarni, Shrinivas R.; Masci, Frank J.; Prince, Thomas A.; Riddle, Reed; Soumagnac, Maayane T.; van der Walt, Stéfan J.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 161, Issue 5, id.218, 8 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021AJ....161..218D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021A&amp;A...649A.163K</TD>
<TD>The luminous and rapidly evolving SN 2018bcc. Clues toward the origin of Type Ibn SNe from the Zwicky Transient Facility</TD>
<TD>Karamehmetoglu, E.; Fransson, C.; Sollerman, J.; Tartaglia, L.; Taddia, F.; De, K.; Fremling, C.; Bagdasaryan, A.; Barbarino, C.; Bellm, E. C.; Dekany, R.; Dugas, A. M.; Giomi, M.; Goobar, A.; Graham, M.; Ho, A.; Laher, R. R.; Masci, F. J.; Neill, J. D.; Perley, D.; Riddle, R.; Rusholme, B.; Soumagnac, M. T.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 649, id.A163, 22 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021A&amp;A...649A.163K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021A&amp;A...649A.134K</TD>
<TD>Core-collapse supernova subtypes in luminous infrared galaxies</TD>
<TD>Kankare, E.; Efstathiou, A.; Kotak, R.; Kool, E. C.; Kangas, T.; O'Neill, D.; Mattila, S.; Väisänen, P.; Ramphul, R.; Mogotsi, M.; Ryder, S. D.; Parker, S.; Reynolds, T.; Fraser, M.; Pastorello, A.; Cappellaro, E.; Mazzali, P. A.; Ochner, P.; Tomasella, L.; Turatto, M.; Kotilainen, J.; Kuncarayakti, H.; Pérez-Torres, M. A.; Randriamanakoto, Z.; Romero-Cañizales, C.; Berton, M.; Cartier, R.; Chen, T. -W.; Galbany, L.; Gromadzki, M.; Inserra, C.; Maguire, K.; Moran, S.; Müller-Bravo, T. E.; Nicholl, M.; Reguitti, A.; Young, D. R.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 649, id.A134, 25 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021A&amp;A...649A.134K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021A&amp;A...649A.131A</TD>
<TD>A transmission spectrum of the planet candidate WD 1856+534 b and a lower limit to its mass</TD>
<TD>Alonso, R.; Rodríguez-Gil, P.; Izquierdo, P.; Deeg, H. J.; Lodieu, N.; Cabrera-Lavers, A.; Hollands, M. A.; Pérez-Toledo, F. M.; Castro-Rodríguez, N.; Reverte Payá, D.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 649, id.A131, 12 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021A&amp;A...649A.131A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021A&amp;A...649A..74N</TD>
<TD>Redshift evolution of the underlying type Ia supernova stretch distribution</TD>
<TD>Nicolas, N.; Rigault, M.; Copin, Y.; Graziani, R.; Aldering, G.; Briday, M.; Kim, Y. -L.; Nordin, J.; Perlmutter, S.; Smith, M.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 649, id.A74, 10 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021A&amp;A...649A..74N</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021PhRvD.103h1501C</TD>
<TD>Gravitational tuning forks and hierarchical triple systems</TD>
<TD>Cardoso, Vitor; Duque, Francisco; Khanna, Gaurav</TD>
<TD>Physical Review D, Volume 103, Issue 8, article id.L081501</TD>
<TD>2021-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021PhRvD.103h1501C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021PSJ.....2...48K</TD>
<TD>Contemporaneous Multiwavelength and Precovery Observations of the Active Centaur P/2019 LD2 (ATLAS)</TD>
<TD>Kareta, Theodore; Woodney, Laura M.; Schambeau, Charles; Fernandez, Yanga; Pinto, Olga Harrington; Wierzchos, Kacper; Womack, M.; Bus, S. J.; Steckloff, Jordan; Sarid, Gal; Volk, Kathryn; Harris, Walter M.; Reddy, Vishnu</TD>
<TD>The Planetary Science Journal, Volume 2, Issue 2, id.48, 14 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021PSJ.....2...48K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021PASP..133d4002B</TD>
<TD>Low-redshift Type Ia Supernova from the LSQ/LCO Collaboration</TD>
<TD>Baltay, C.; Grossman, L.; Howard, R.; Rabinowitz, D.; Arcavi, I.; Barbour, N.; Burke, J.; Contreras, C.; Dilday, B.; Graham, M.; Hiramatsu, D.; Hossenzadeh, G.; Howell, D. A.; McCully, C.; McKinnon, R.; Ment, K.; Montesi, R.; Pellegrino, C.; Valenti, S.</TD>
<TD>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 133, Issue 1022, id.044002, 15 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021PASP..133d4002B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021Obs...141...63L</TD>
<TD>Is 1RXS J012750.5+380830 a superhumping intermediate polar?</TD>
<TD>Lloyd, C.; Tordai, T.; Vanmunster, T., Rickard, R.</TD>
<TD>The Observatory, Vol. 141, pp. 63-73</TD>
<TD>2021-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021Obs...141...63L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021Natur.592..704A</TD>
<TD>X-ray quasi-periodic eruptions from two previously quiescent galaxies</TD>
<TD>Arcodia, R.; Merloni, A.; Nandra, K.; Buchner, J.; Salvato, M.; Pasham, D.; Remillard, R.; Comparat, J.; Lamer, G.; Ponti, G.; Malyali, A.; Wolf, J.; Arzoumanian, Z.; Bogensberger, D.; Buckley, D. A. H.; Gendreau, K.; Gromadzki, M.; Kara, E.; Krumpe, M.; Markwardt, C.; Ramos-Ceja, M. E.; Rau, A.; Schramm, M.; Schwope, A.</TD>
<TD>Nature, Volume 592, Issue 7856, p.704-707</TD>
<TD>2021-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021Natur.592..704A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.502.5147M</TD>
<TD>Anomaly detection in the Zwicky Transient Facility DR3</TD>
<TD>Malanchev, K. L.; Pruzhinskaya, M. V.; Korolev, V. S.; Aleo, P. D.; Kornilov, M. V.; Ishida, E. E. O.; Krushinsky, V. V.; Mondon, F.; Sreejith, S.; Volnova, A. A.; Belinski, A. A.; Dodin, A. V.; Tatarnikov, A. M.; Zheltoukhov, S. G.; (The SNAD Team)</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 502, Issue 4, pp.5147-5175</TD>
<TD>2021-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.502.5147M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.502.4972K</TD>
<TD>Hidden in plain sight: a double-lined white dwarf binary 26 pc away and a distant cousin</TD>
<TD>Kilic, Mukremin; Bédard, A.; Bergeron, P.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 502, Issue 4, pp.4972-4980</TD>
<TD>2021-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.502.4972K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.502.4953D</TD>
<TD>Evidence that short-period AM CVn systems are diverse in outburst behaviour</TD>
<TD>Duffy, C.; Ramsay, G.; Steeghs, D.; Dhillon, V.; Kennedy, M. R.; Mata Sánchez, D.; Ackley, K.; Dyer, M.; Lyman, J.; Ulaczyk, K.; Galloway, D. K.; O'Brien, P.; Noysena, K.; Nuttall, L.; Pollacco, D.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 502, Issue 4, pp.4953-4962</TD>
<TD>2021-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.502.4953D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.502.4305P</TD>
<TD>Magnetic white dwarfs in post-common-envelope binaries</TD>
<TD>Parsons, S. G.; Gänsicke, B. T.; Schreiber, M. R.; Marsh, T. R.; Ashley, R. P.; Breedt, E.; Littlefair, S. P.; Meusinger, H.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 502, Issue 3, pp.4305-4327</TD>
<TD>2021-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.502.4305P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.502.3533M</TD>
<TD>Exploring the diversity of double-detonation explosions for Type Ia supernovae: effects of the post-explosion helium shell composition</TD>
<TD>Magee, M. R.; Maguire, K.; Kotak, R.; Sim, S. A.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 502, Issue 3, pp.3533-3553</TD>
<TD>2021-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.502.3533M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.502.3385M</TD>
<TD>Limits on mass outflow from optical tidal disruption events</TD>
<TD>Matsumoto, Tatsuya; Piran, Tsvi</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 502, Issue 3, pp.3385-3393</TD>
<TD>2021-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.502.3385M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.502.2912S</TD>
<TD>Discovering strongly lensed QSOs from unresolved light curves</TD>
<TD>Shu, Yiping; Belokurov, Vasily; Evans, N. Wyn</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 502, Issue 2, pp.2912-2921</TD>
<TD>2021-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.502.2912S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.502.2087T</TD>
<TD>Improving estimates of the growth rate using galaxy-velocity correlations: a simulation study</TD>
<TD>Turner, Ryan J.; Blake, Chris; Ruggeri, Rossana</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 502, Issue 2, pp.2087-2096</TD>
<TD>2021-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.502.2087T</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.502.1678K</TD>
<TD>SN 2020ank: a bright and fast-evolving H-deficient superluminous supernova</TD>
<TD>Kumar, Amit; Kumar, Brajesh; Pandey, S. B.; Sahu, D. K.; Singh, Avinash; Anupama, G. C.; Aryan, Amar; Gupta, Rahul; Dutta, Anirban; Misra, Kuntal</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 502, Issue 2, pp.1678-1693</TD>
<TD>2021-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.502.1678K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.502.1612S</TD>
<TD>Improved early warning of compact binary mergers using higher modes of gravitational radiation: a population study</TD>
<TD>Singh, Mukesh Kumar; Kapadia, Shasvath J.; Shaikh, Md Arif; Chatterjee, Deep; Ajith, Parameswaran</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 502, Issue 2, pp.1612-1622</TD>
<TD>2021-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.502.1612S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021JKAS...54...37K</TD>
<TD>Simulations of Torus Reverberation Mapping Experiments with SPHEREx</TD>
<TD>Kim, Minjin; Jeong, Woong-Seob; Yang, Yujin; Son, Jiwon; Ho, Luis C.; Woo, Jong-Hak; Im, Myungshin; Byun, Woowon</TD>
<TD>Journal of the Korean Astronomical Society, vol. 54, pp. 37-47 (2021)</TD>
<TD>2021-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021JKAS...54...37K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021AstL...47..252B</TD>
<TD>Changes in the Period of SU Sct, a Population II Cepheid</TD>
<TD>Berdnikov, L. N.; Pastukhova, E. N.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy Letters, Volume 47, Issue 4, p.252-261</TD>
<TD>2021-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021AstL...47..252B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJS..253...51L</TD>
<TD>Chromospheric Activity of Periodic Variable Stars Based on the LAMOST Low- and Medium-resolution Spectral Survey</TD>
<TD>Long, Liu; Zhang, Li-yun; Bi, Shao-Lan; Shi, Jianrong; Lu, Hong-Peng; Han, Xianming L.; Wang, Haifeng; Prabhakar, Misra</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 253, Issue 2, id.51, 21 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJS..253...51L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...911L..35P</TD>
<TD>Time-series and Phase-curve Photometry of the Episodically Active Asteroid (6478) Gault in a Quiescent State Using APO, GROWTH, P200, and ZTF</TD>
<TD>Purdum, Josiah N.; Lin, Zhong-Yi; Bolin, Bryce T.; Sharma, Kritti; Choi, Philip I.; Bhalerao, Varun; Hanuš, Josef; Kumar, Harsh; Quimby, Robert; van Roestel, Joannes C.; Zhai, Chengxing; Fernandez, Yanga R.; Lisse, Carey M.; Bodewits, Dennis; Fremling, Christoffer; Ryan Golovich, Nathan; Hsu, Chen-Yen; Ip, Wing-Huen; Ngeow, Chow-Choong; Saini, Navtej S.; Shao, Michael; Yao, Yuhan; Ahumada, Tomás; Anand, Shreya; Andreoni, Igor; Burdge, Kevin B.; Burruss, Rick; Chang, Chan-Kao; Copperwheat, Chris M.; Coughlin, Michael; De, Kishalay; Dekany, Richard; Delacroix, Alexandre; Drake, Andrew; Duev, Dmitry; Graham, Matthew; Hale, David; Kool, Erik C.; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Kostadinova, Iva S.; Kulkarni, Shrinivas R.; Laher, Russ R.; Mahabal, Ashish; Masci, Frank J.; Mróz, Przemyslaw J.; Neill, James D.; Riddle, Reed; Rodriguez, Hector; Smith, Roger M.; Walters, Richard; Yan, Lin; Zolkower, Jeffry</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 911, Issue 2, id.L35, 16 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...911L..35P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...911L..20R</TD>
<TD>Gaia EDR3 Parallax Zero-point Offset Based on W Ursae Majoris-type Eclipsing Binaries</TD>
<TD>Ren, Fangzhou; Chen, Xiaodian; Zhang, Huawei; de Grijs, Richard; Deng, Licai; Huang, Yang</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 911, Issue 2, id.L20, 6 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...911L..20R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...911L..14W</TD>
<TD>Accretion-modified Stars in Accretion Disks of Active Galactic Nuclei: Slowly Transient Appearance</TD>
<TD>Wang, Jian-Min; Liu, Jun-Rong; Ho, Luis C.; Du, Pu</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 911, Issue 1, id.L14, 8 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...911L..14W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...911..142L</TD>
<TD>Magnetar-driven Shock Breakout Revisited and Implications for Double-peaked Type I Superluminous Supernovae</TD>
<TD>Liu, Liang-Duan; Gao, He; Wang, Xiao-Feng; Yang, Sheng</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 911, Issue 2, id.142, 8 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...911..142L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...911..104K</TD>
<TD>Fast Optical Transients from Stellar-mass Black Hole Tidal Disruption Events in Young Star Clusters</TD>
<TD>Kremer, Kyle; Lu, Wenbin; Piro, Anthony L.; Chatterjee, Sourav; Rasio, Frederic A.; Ye, Claire S.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 911, Issue 2, id.104, 13 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...911..104K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...911...51L</TD>
<TD>HO Puppis: Not a Be Star, but a Newly Confirmed IW And-type Star</TD>
<TD>Lee, Chien-De; Ou, Jia-Yu; Yu, Po-Chieh; Ngeow, Chow-Choong; Huang, Po-Chieh; Ip, Wing-Huen; Hambsch, Franz-Josef; Sung, Hyun-il; van Roestel, Jan; Dekany, Richard; Drake, Andrew J.; Graham, Matthew J.; Duev, Dmitry A.; Kaye, Stephen; Kupfer, Thomas; Laher, Russ R.; Masci, Frank J.; Mróz, Przemek; Neill, James D.; Riddle, Reed; Rusholme, Ben; Walters, Richard</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 911, Issue 1, id.51, 18 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...911...51L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...911...43S</TD>
<TD>GRB 191016A: A Long Gamma-Ray Burst Detected by TESS</TD>
<TD>Smith, Krista Lynne; Ridden-Harper, Ryan; Fausnaugh, Michael; Daylan, Tansu; Omodei, Nicola; Racusin, Judith; Weaver, Zachary; Barclay, Thomas; Veres, Péter; Kann, D. Alexander; Arimoto, Makoto</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 911, Issue 1, id.43, 9 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...911...43S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...911...31J</TD>
<TD>Infrared Echoes of Optical Tidal Disruption Events: ∼1% Dust-covering Factor or Less at Subparsec Scale</TD>
<TD>Jiang, Ning; Wang, Tinggui; Hu, Xueyang; Sun, Luming; Dou, Liming; Xiao, Lin</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 911, Issue 1, id.31, 10 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...911...31J</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...910..132K</TD>
<TD>Census of R Coronae Borealis Stars. I. Infrared Light Curves from Palomar Gattini IR</TD>
<TD>Karambelkar, Viraj R.; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Tisserand, Patrick; De, Kishalay; Anand, Shreya; Ashley, Michael C. B.; Delacroix, Alex; Hankins, Matthew; Jencson, Jacob E.; Lau, Ryan M.; McKenna, Dan; Moore, Anna; Ofek, Eran O.; Smith, Roger M.; Soria, Roberto; Soon, Jamie; Tinyanont, Samaporn; Travouillon, Tony; Yao, Yuhan</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 910, Issue 2, id.132, 17 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...910..132K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...910...93R</TD>
<TD>Forward Modeling Populations of Flares from Tidal Disruptions of Stars by Supermassive Black Holes</TD>
<TD>Roth, Nathaniel; van Velzen, Sjoert; Cenko, S. Bradley; Mushotzky, R. F.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 910, Issue 2, id.93, 27 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...910...93R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...910...83H</TD>
<TD>A Swift Fix for Nuclear Outbursts</TD>
<TD>Hinkle, Jason T.; Holoien, Thomas W. -S.; Shappee, Benjamin. J.; Auchettl, Katie</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 910, Issue 2, id.83, 10 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...910...83H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021AJ....161..192N</TD>
<TD>Second Data Release of the All-sky NOIRLab Source Catalog</TD>
<TD>Nidever, David L.; Dey, Arjun; Fasbender, Katie; Juneau, Stéphanie; Meisner, Aaron M.; Wishart, Joseph; Scott, Adam; Matt, Kyle; Nikutta, Robert; Pucha, Ragadeepika</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 161, Issue 4, id.192, 16 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021AJ....161..192N</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021AJ....161..168E</TD>
<TD>On the Classification and Feature Relevance of Multiband Light Curves</TD>
<TD>Edes-Huyal, Fatma Kuzey; Cataltepe, Zehra; Kahya, Emre O.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 161, Issue 4, id.168, 18 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021AJ....161..168E</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021A&amp;C....3500451D</TD>
<TD>Photometric data-driven classification of Type Ia supernovae in the open Supernova Catalog</TD>
<TD>Dobryakov, S.; Malanchev, K.; Derkach, D.; Hushchyn, M.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy and Computing, Volume 35, article id. 100451.</TD>
<TD>2021-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021A&amp;C....3500451D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021A&amp;A...648A.122V</TD>
<TD>Machine learning technique for morphological classification of galaxies from the SDSS. I. Photometry-based approach</TD>
<TD>Vavilova, I. B.; Dobrycheva, D. V.; Vasylenko, M. Yu.; Elyiv, A. A.; Melnyk, O. V.; Khramtsov, V.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 648, id.A122, 14 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021A&amp;A...648A.122V</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021A&amp;A...648A..44M</TD>
<TD>Large-amplitude variables in Gaia Data Release 2. Multi-band variability characterization</TD>
<TD>Mowlavi, N.; Rimoldini, L.; Evans, D. W.; Riello, M.; De Angeli, F.; Palaversa, L.; Audard, M.; Eyer, L.; Garcia-Lario, P.; Gavras, P.; Holl, B.; Jevardat de Fombelle, G.; Lecœur-Taïbi, I.; Nienartowicz, K.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 648, id.A44, 30 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021A&amp;A...648A..44M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021Univ....7...76N</TD>
<TD>Multiwavelength Observations of Fast Radio Bursts</TD>
<TD>Nicastro, Luciano; Guidorzi, Cristiano; Palazzi, Eliana; Zampieri, Luca; Turatto, Massimo; Gardini, Angela</TD>
<TD>Universe, vol. 7, issue 3, p. 76</TD>
<TD>2021-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021Univ....7...76N</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021SoSyR..55..124B</TD>
<TD>Discovery of the First Interstellar Comet and the Spatial Density of Interstellar Objects in the Solar Neighborhood</TD>
<TD>Borisov, G. V.; Shustov, B. M.</TD>
<TD>Solar System Research, Volume 55, Issue 2, p.124-131</TD>
<TD>2021-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021SoSyR..55..124B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021PhRvL.126j1105T</TD>
<TD>Detectable Environmental Effects in GW190521-like Black-Hole Binaries with LISA</TD>
<TD>Toubiana, Alexandre; Sberna, Laura; Caputo, Andrea; Cusin, Giulia; Marsat, Sylvain; Jani, Karan; Babak, Stanislav; Barausse, Enrico; Caprini, Chiara; Pani, Paolo; Sesana, Alberto; Tamanini, Nicola</TD>
<TD>Physical Review Letters, Volume 126, Issue 10, article id.101105</TD>
<TD>2021-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021PhRvL.126j1105T</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021NJPh...23c1201A</TD>
<TD>SNEWS 2.0: a next-generation supernova early warning system for multi-messenger astronomy</TD>
<TD>Al Kharusi, S.; BenZvi, S. Y.; Bobowski, J. S.; Bonivento, W.; Brdar, V.; Brunner, T.; Caden, E.; Clark, M.; Coleiro, A.; Colomer-Molla, M.; Crespo-Anadón, J. I.; Depoian, A.; Dornic, D.; Fischer, V.; Franco, D.; Fulgione, W.; Gallo Rosso, A.; Geske, M.; Griswold, S.; Gromov, M.; Haggard, D.; Habig, A.; Halim, O.; Higuera, A.; Hill, R.; Horiuchi, S.; Ishidoshiro, K.; Kato, C.; Katsavounidis, E.; Khaitan, D.; Kneller, J. P.; Kopec, A.; Kulikovskiy, V.; Lai, M.; Lamoureux, M.; Lang, R. F.; Li, H. L.; Lincetto, M.; Lunardini, C.; Migenda, J.; Milisavljevic, D.; McCarthy, M. E.; O Connor, E.; O Sullivan, E.; Pagliaroli, G.; Patel, D.; Peres, R.; Pointon, B. W.; Qin, J.; Raj, N.; Renshaw, A.; Roeth, A.; Rumleskie, J.; Scholberg, K.; Sheshukov, A.; Sonley, T.; Strait, M.; Takhistov, V.; Tamborra, I.; Tseng, J.; Tunnell, C. D.; Vasel, J.; Vigorito, C. F.; Viren, B.; Virtue, C. J.; Wang, J. S.; Wen, L. J.; Winslow, L.; Wolfs, F. L. H.; Xu, X. J.; Xu, Y.</TD>
<TD>New Journal of Physics, Volume 23, Issue 3, id.031201, 34 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021NJPh...23c1201A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.502.1299T</TD>
<TD>SuperWASP variable stars: classifying light curves using citizen science</TD>
<TD>Thiemann, Heidi B.; Norton, Andrew J.; Dickinson, Hugh J.; McMaster, Adam; Kolb, Ulrich C.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 502, Issue 1, pp.1299-1311</TD>
<TD>2021-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.502.1299T</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.502.1136M</TD>
<TD>Testing the general theory of relativity using gravitational wave propagation from dark standard sirens</TD>
<TD>Mukherjee, Suvodip; Wandelt, Benjamin D.; Silk, Joseph</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 502, Issue 1, pp.1136-1144</TD>
<TD>2021-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.502.1136M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.502..510J</TD>
<TD>Spectroscopy of the first resolved strongly lensed Type Ia supernova iPTF16geu</TD>
<TD>Johansson, J.; Goobar, A.; Price, S. H.; Sagués Carracedo, A.; Della Bruna, L.; Nugent, P. E.; Dhawan, S.; Mörtsell, E.; Papadogiannakis, S.; Amanullah, R.; Goldstein, D.; Cenko, S. B.; De, K.; Dugas, A.; Kasliwal, M. M.; Kulkarni, S. R.; Lunnan, R.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 502, Issue 1, pp.510-520</TD>
<TD>2021-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.502..510J</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.501.4123F</TD>
<TD>New insights into time-series analysis IV: panchromatic and flux-independent period finding methods</TD>
<TD>Ferreira Lopes, C. E.; Cross, N. J. G.; Jablonski, F.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 501, Issue 3, pp.4123-4135</TD>
<TD>2021-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.501.4123F</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.501.3272M</TD>
<TD>FINK, a new generation of broker for the LSST community</TD>
<TD>Möller, Anais; Peloton, Julien; Ishida, Emille E. O.; Arnault, Chris; Bachelet, Etienne; Blaineau, Tristan; Boutigny, Dominique; Chauhan, Abhishek; Gangler, Emmanuel; Hernandez, Fabio; Hrivnac, Julius; Leoni, Marco; Leroy, Nicolas; Moniez, Marc; Pateyron, Sacha; Ramparison, Adrien; Turpin, Damien; Ansari, Réza; Allam, Tarek, Jr.; Bajat, Armelle; Biswas, Biswajit; Boucaud, Alexandre; Bregeon, Johan; Campagne, Jean-Eric; Cohen-Tanugi, Johann; Coleiro, Alexis; Dornic, Damien; Fouchez, Dominique; Godet, Olivier; Gris, Philippe; Karpov, Sergey; Nebot Gomez-Moran, Ada; Neveu, Jérémy; Plaszczynski, Stephane; Savchenko, Volodymyr; Webb, Natalie</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 501, Issue 3, pp.3272-3288</TD>
<TD>2021-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.501.3272M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021JInst..16P3025A</TD>
<TD>Design and sensitivity of the Radio Neutrino Observatory in Greenland (RNO-G)</TD>
<TD>Aguilar, J. A.; Allison, P.; Beatty, J. J.; Bernhoff, H.; Besson, D.; Bingefors, N.; Botner, O.; Buitink, S.; Carter, K.; Clark, B. A.; Connolly, A.; Dasgupta, P.; de Kockere, S.; de Vries, K. D.; Deaconu, C.; DuVernois, M. A.; Feigl, N.; García-Fernández, D.; Glaser, C.; Hallgren, A.; Hallmann, S.; Hanson, J. C.; Hendricks, B.; Hokanson-Fasig, B.; Hornhuber, C.; Hughes, K.; Karle, A.; Kelley, J. L.; Klein, S. R.; Krebs, R.; Lahmann, R.; Magnuson, M.; Meures, T.; Meyers, Z. S.; Nelles, A.; Novikov, A.; Oberla, E.; Oeyen, B.; Pandya, H.; Plaisier, I.; Pyras, L.; Ryckbosch, D.; Scholten, O.; Seckel, D.; Smith, D.; Southall, D.; Torres, J.; Toscano, S.; Van Den Broeck, D. J.; van Eijndhoven, N.; Vieregg, A. G.; Welling, C.; Wissel, S.; Young, R.; Zink, A.</TD>
<TD>Journal of Instrumentation, Volume 16, Issue 03, id.P03025, 55 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021JInst..16P3025A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021JCAP...03..045A</TD>
<TD>The H.E.S.S. gravitational wave rapid follow-up program</TD>
<TD>Ashkar, Halim; Brun, Francois; Füßling, Matthias; Hoischen, Clemens; Ohm, Stefan; Prokoph, Heike; Reichherzer, Patrick; Schüssler, Fabian; Seglar-Arroyo, Monica</TD>
<TD>Journal of Cosmology and Astroparticle Physics, Volume 2021, Issue 03, id.045, 28 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021JCAP...03..045A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJS..253...20H</TD>
<TD>Supermassive Black Holes with High Accretion Rates in Active Galactic Nuclei. XII. Reverberation Mapping Results for 15 PG Quasars from a Long-duration High-cadence Campaign</TD>
<TD>Hu, Chen; Li, Sha-Sha; Yang, Sen; Yang, Zi-Xu; Guo, Wei-Jian; Bao, Dong-Wei; Jiang, Bo-Wei; Du, Pu; Li, Yan-Rong; Xiao, Ming; Songsheng, Yu-Yang; Yu, Zhe; Bai, Jin-Ming; Ho, Luis C.; Brotherton, Michael S.; Aceituno, Jesús; Winkler, Hartmut; Wang, Jian-Min; Seambh Collaboration</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 253, Issue 1, id.20, 18 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJS..253...20H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...910...65B</TD>
<TD>Be It Unresolved: Measuring Time Delays from Lensed Supernovae</TD>
<TD>Bag, Satadru; Kim, Alex G.; Linder, Eric V.; Shafieloo, Arman</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 910, Issue 1, id.65, 13 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...910...65B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...910....1H</TD>
<TD>Lunar Gravitational-wave Antenna</TD>
<TD>Harms, Jan; Ambrosino, Filippo; Angelini, Lorella; Braito, Valentina; Branchesi, Marica; Brocato, Enzo; Cappellaro, Enrico; Coccia, Eugenio; Coughlin, Michael; Della Ceca, Roberto; Della Valle, Massimo; Dionisio, Cesare; Federico, Costanzo; Formisano, Michelangelo; Frigeri, Alessandro; Grado, Aniello; Izzo, Luca; Marcelli, Augusto; Maselli, Andrea; Olivieri, Marco; Pernechele, Claudio; Possenti, Andrea; Ronchini, Samuele; Serafinelli, Roberto; Severgnini, Paola; Agostini, Maila; Badaracco, Francesca; Bertolini, Alessandro; Betti, Lorenzo; Civitani, Marta Maria; Collette, Christophe; Covino, Stefano; Dall'Osso, Simone; D'Avanzo, Paolo; DeSalvo, Riccardo; Di Giovanni, Matteo; Focardi, Mauro; Giunchi, Carlo; van Heijningen, Joris; Khetan, Nandita; Melini, Daniele; Mitri, Giuseppe; Mow-Lowry, Conor; Naponiello, Luca; Noce, Vladimiro; Oganesyan, Gor; Pace, Emanuele; Paik, Ho Jung; Pajewski, Alessandro; Palazzi, Eliana; Pallavicini, Marco; Pareschi, Giovanni; Pozzobon, Riccardo; Sharma, Ashish; Spada, Giorgio; Stanga, Ruggero; Tagliaferri, Gianpiero; Votta, Raffaele</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 910, Issue 1, id.1, 22 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...910....1H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...909..126K</TD>
<TD>Swift Follow-up Observations of Gravitational-wave and High-energy Neutrino Coincident Signals</TD>
<TD>Keivani, Azadeh; Kennea, Jamie A.; Evans, Phil A.; Tohuvavohu, Aaron; Rapisura, Riki; Oates, Samantha R.; Countryman, Stefan; Bartos, Imre; Márka, Zsuzsa; Veske, Doğa; Márka, Szabolcs; Fox, Derek B.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 909, Issue 2, id.126, 9 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...909..126K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...909..102B</TD>
<TD>A Luminous X-Ray Transient in SDSS J143359.16+400636.0: A Likely Tidal Disruption Event</TD>
<TD>Brightman, Murray; Ward, Charlotte; Stern, Daniel; Mooley, Kunal; De, Kishalay; Gezari, Suvi; Van Velzen, Sjoert; Andreoni, Igor; Graham, Matthew; Masci, Frank J.; Riddle, Reed; Zolkower, Jeffry</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 909, Issue 2, id.102, 15 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...909..102B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...909...64R</TD>
<TD>Detection of Tidal Disruption Events around Direct-collapse Black Holes at High Redshifts with the James Webb Space Telescope</TD>
<TD>Regős, Enikő; Vinkó, József; Stermeczky, Zsófia V.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 909, Issue 1, id.64, 11 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...909...64R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...909...48N</TD>
<TD>Correction to the Photometric Colors of the Gaia Data Release 2 with the Stellar Color Regression Method</TD>
<TD>Niu, Zexi; Yuan, Haibo; Liu, Jifeng</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 909, Issue 1, id.48, 11 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...909...48N</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...909...25D</TD>
<TD>Possible Evidence of Hydrogen Emission in the First-overtone and Multimode RR Lyrae Variables</TD>
<TD>Duan, Xiao-Wei; Chen, Xiao-Dian; Deng, Li-Cai; Yang, Fan; Liu, Chao; Bhardwaj, Anupam; Zhang, Hua-Wei</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 909, Issue 1, id.25, 11 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...909...25D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021AcA....71...55B</TD>
<TD>Photometric and Spectroscopic Investigations of the Galactic Field RRc Candidates V764 Mon and HY Com</TD>
<TD>Benkő, J. M.; Sódor, Á.; Pál, A.</TD>
<TD>Acta Astronomica, vol 71, no 1, p. 55-71</TD>
<TD>2021-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021AcA....71...55B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021AJ....161..141S</TD>
<TD>Alert Classification for the ALeRCE Broker System: The Light Curve Classifier</TD>
<TD>Sánchez-Sáez, P.; Reyes, I.; Valenzuela, C.; Förster, F.; Eyheramendy, S.; Elorrieta, F.; Bauer, F. E.; Cabrera-Vives, G.; Estévez, P. A.; Catelan, M.; Pignata, G.; Huijse, P.; De Cicco, D.; Arévalo, P.; Carrasco-Davis, R.; Abril, J.; Kurtev, R.; Borissova, J.; Arredondo, J.; Castillo-Navarrete, E.; Rodriguez, D.; Ruz-Mieres, D.; Moya, A.; Sabatini-Gacitúa, L.; Sepúlveda-Cobo, C.; Camacho-Iñiguez, E.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 161, Issue 3, id.141, 31 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021AJ....161..141S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021AJ....161..116B</TD>
<TD>Initial Characterization of Active Transitioning Centaur, P/2019 LD&lt;SUB&gt;2&lt;/SUB&gt; (ATLAS), Using Hubble, Spitzer, ZTF, Keck, Apache Point Observatory, and GROWTH Visible and Infrared Imaging and Spectroscopy</TD>
<TD>Bolin, Bryce T.; Fernandez, Yanga R.; Lisse, Carey M.; Holt, Timothy R.; Lin, Zhong-Yi; Purdum, Josiah N.; Deshmukh, Kunal P.; Bauer, James M.; Bellm, Eric C.; Bodewits, Dennis; Burdge, Kevin B.; Carey, Sean J.; Copperwheat, Chris M.; Helou, George; Ho, Anna Y. Q.; Horner, Jonathan; van Roestel, Jan; Bhalerao, Varun; Chang, Chan-Kao; Chen, Christine; Hsu, Chen-Yen; Ip, Wing-Huen; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Masci, Frank J.; Ngeow, Chow-Choong; Quimby, Robert; Burruss, Rick; Coughlin, Michael; Dekany, Richard; Delacroix, Alexandre; Drake, Andrew; Duev, Dmitry A.; Graham, Matthew; Hale, David; Kupfer, Thomas; Laher, Russ R.; Mahabal, Ashish; Mróz, Przemyslaw J.; Neill, James D.; Riddle, Reed; Rodriguez, Hector; Smith, Roger M.; Soumagnac, Maayane T.; Walters, Richard; Yan, Lin; Zolkower, Jeffry</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 161, Issue 3, id.116, 15 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021AJ....161..116B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021AJ....161..107M</TD>
<TD>The ANTARES Astronomical Time-domain Event Broker</TD>
<TD>Matheson, Thomas; Stubens, Carl; Wolf, Nicholas; Lee, Chien-Hsiu; Narayan, Gautham; Saha, Abhijit; Scott, Adam; Soraisam, Monika; Bolton, Adam S.; Hauger, Benjamin; Silva, David R.; Kececioglu, John; Scheidegger, Carlos; Snodgrass, Richard; Aleo, Patrick D.; Evans-Jacquez, Eric; Singh, Navdeep; Wang, Zhe; Yang, Shuo; Zhao, Zhenge</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 161, Issue 3, id.107, 16 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021AJ....161..107M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021A&amp;A...647A.184R</TD>
<TD>Mysterious, variable, and extremely hot: White dwarfs showing ultra-high excitation lines. I. Photometric variability</TD>
<TD>Reindl, Nicole; Schaffenroth, Veronika; Filiz, Semih; Geier, Stephan; Pelisoli, Ingrid; Kepler, Souza Oliveira</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 647, id.A184, 22 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021A&amp;A...647A.184R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021A&amp;A...647A..93P</TD>
<TD>Forbidden hugs in pandemic times. II. The luminous red nova variety: AT 2020hat and AT 2020kog</TD>
<TD>Pastorello, A.; Valerin, G.; Fraser, M.; Elias-Rosa, N.; Valenti, S.; Reguitti, A.; Mazzali, P. A.; Amaro, R. C.; Andrews, J. E.; Dong, Y.; Jencson, J.; Lundquist, M.; Reichart, D. E.; Sand, D. J.; Wyatt, S.; Smartt, S. J.; Smith, K. W.; Srivastav, S.; Cai, Y. -Z.; Cappellaro, E.; Holmbo, S.; Fiore, A.; Jones, D.; Kankare, E.; Karamehmetoglu, E.; Lundqvist, P.; Morales-Garoffolo, A.; Reynolds, T. M.; Stritzinger, M. D.; Williams, S. C.; Chambers, K. C.; de Boer, T. J. L.; Huber, M. E.; Rest, A.; Wainscoat, R.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 647, id.A93, 13 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021A&amp;A...647A..93P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021A&amp;A...647A...9M</TD>
<TD>AT 2019avd: a novel addition to the diverse population of nuclear transients</TD>
<TD>Malyali, A.; Rau, A.; Merloni, A.; Nandra, K.; Buchner, J.; Liu, Z.; Gezari, S.; Sollerman, J.; Shappee, B.; Trakhtenbrot, B.; Arcavi, I.; Ricci, C.; van Velzen, S.; Goobar, A.; Frederick, S.; Kawka, A.; Tartaglia, L.; Burke, J.; Hiramatsu, D.; Schramm, M.; van der Boom, D.; Anderson, G.; Miller-Jones, J. C. A.; Bellm, E.; Drake, A.; Duev, D.; Fremling, C.; Graham, M.; Masci, F.; Rusholme, B.; Soumagnac, M.; Walters, R.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 647, id.A9, 17 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021A&amp;A...647A...9M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021PSJ.....2...40S</TD>
<TD>Zwicky Transient Facility Observations of Trojan Asteroids: A Thousand Colors, Rotation Amplitudes, and Phase Functions</TD>
<TD>Schemel, Madeline; Brown, Michael E.</TD>
<TD>The Planetary Science Journal, Volume 2, Issue 1, id.40, 8 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021PSJ.....2...40S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021PASJ...73...25M</TD>
<TD>Follow-up observations for IceCube-170922A: Detection of rapid near-infrared variability and intensive monitoring of TXS 0506+056</TD>
<TD>Morokuma, Tomoki; Utsumi, Yousuke; Ohta, Kouji; Yamanaka, Masayuki; Kawabata, Koji S.; Inoue, Yoshiyuki; Tanaka, Masaomi; Yoshida, Michitoshi; Itoh, Ryosuke; Sasada, Mahito; Tominaga, Nozomu; Mori, Hiroki; Kawabata, Miho; Nakaoka, Tatsuya; Chogi, Maiko; Abe, Taisei; Huang, Ruochen; Kawahara, Naoki; Kimura, Hiroki; Nagashima, Hiroki; Takagi, Kengo; Yamazaki, Yuina; Liu, Wei; Ohsawa, Ryou; Sako, Shigeyuki; Murata, Katsuhiro L.; Morihana, Kumiko; Gilligan, Christina K.; Isogai, Keisuke; Kimura, Mariko; Wakamatsu, Yasuyuki; Ohnishi, Ryuhei; Takayama, Masaki; Honda, Satoshi; Matsuoka, Yoshiki; Yamashita, Takuji; Nagataki, Shigehiro; Tanaka, Yasuyuki T.</TD>
<TD>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Volume 73, Issue 1, pp.25-43</TD>
<TD>2021-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021PASJ...73...25M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021PASJ...73...14N</TD>
<TD>A GPU-accelerated image reduction pipeline</TD>
<TD>Niwano, Masafumi; Murata, Katsuhiro L.; Adachi, Ryo; Wang, Sili; Tachibana, Yutaro; Yatsu, Yoichi; Kawai, Nobuyuki; Shimokawabe, Takashi; Itoh, Ryosuke</TD>
<TD>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Volume 73, Issue 1, pp.14-24</TD>
<TD>2021-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021PASJ...73...14N</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021NatAs...5..510S</TD>
<TD>A tidal disruption event coincident with a high-energy neutrino</TD>
<TD>Stein, Robert; van Velzen, Sjoert; Kowalski, Marek; Franckowiak, Anna; Gezari, Suvi; Miller-Jones, James C. A.; Frederick, Sara; Sfaradi, Itai; Bietenholz, Michael F.; Horesh, Assaf; Fender, Rob; Garrappa, Simone; Ahumada, Tomás; Andreoni, Igor; Belicki, Justin; Bellm, Eric C.; Böttcher, Markus; Brinnel, Valery; Burruss, Rick; Cenko, S. Bradley; Coughlin, Michael W.; Cunningham, Virginia; Drake, Andrew; Farrar, Glennys R.; Feeney, Michael; Foley, Ryan J.; Gal-Yam, Avishay; Golkhou, V. Zach; Goobar, Ariel; Graham, Matthew J.; Hammerstein, Erica; Helou, George; Hung, Tiara; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Kilpatrick, Charles D.; Kong, Albert K. H.; Kupfer, Thomas; Laher, Russ R.; Mahabal, Ashish A.; Masci, Frank J.; Necker, Jannis; Nordin, Jakob; Perley, Daniel A.; Rigault, Mickael; Reusch, Simeon; Rodriguez, Hector; Rojas-Bravo, César; Rusholme, Ben; Shupe, David L.; Singer, Leo P.; Sollerman, Jesper; Soumagnac, Maayane T.; Stern, Daniel; Taggart, Kirsty; van Santen, Jakob; Ward, Charlotte; Woudt, Patrick; Yao, Yuhan</TD>
<TD>Nature Astronomy, Volume 5, p. 510-518</TD>
<TD>2021-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021NatAs...5..510S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.501.1836Y</TD>
<TD>Tidally excited oscillations in hot white dwarfs</TD>
<TD>Yu, Hang; Fuller, Jim; Burdge, Kevin B.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 501, Issue 2, pp.1836-1851</TD>
<TD>2021-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.501.1836Y</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.501.1059R</TD>
<TD>Low-luminosity Type II supernovae - III. SN 2018hwm, a faint event with an unusually long plateau</TD>
<TD>Reguitti, A.; Pumo, M. L.; Mazzali, P. A.; Pastorello, A.; Pignata, G.; Elias-Rosa, N.; Prentice, S. J.; Reynolds, T.; Benetti, S.; Rodrìguez, O.; Mattila, S.; Kuncarayakti, H.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 501, Issue 1, pp.1059-1071</TD>
<TD>2021-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.501.1059R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.500.5639V</TD>
<TD>High-cadence, early-time observations of core-collapse supernovae from the TESS prime mission</TD>
<TD>Vallely, P. J.; Kochanek, C. S.; Stanek, K. Z.; Fausnaugh, M.; Shappee, B. J.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 500, Issue 4, pp.5639-5656</TD>
<TD>2021-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.500.5639V</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.500.5098K</TD>
<TD>Multiband light-curve analysis of the 40.5-min period eclipsing double-degenerate binary SDSS J082239.54+304857.19</TD>
<TD>Kosakowski, Alekzander; Kilic, Mukremin; Brown, Warren</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 500, Issue 4, pp.5098-5105</TD>
<TD>2021-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.500.5098K</TD>
</TR>

</TABLEDATA>
</DATA>
</TABLE>
</RESOURCE>
</VOTABLE>