<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf8'?>
<!DOCTYPE VOTABLE SYSTEM "http://cdsweb.u-strasbg.fr/xml/VOTable.dtd" >
<VOTABLE version="1.1">
<DESCRIPTION>
   Results generated from the NASA Astrophysics Data System: https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu
   For more information and support please contact ads@cfa.harvard.edu
</DESCRIPTION>
<RESOURCE type="results">
<TABLE>
<DESCRIPTION>
   ADS Search Results.
   Selected and retrieved 500 records.
</DESCRIPTION>
<FIELD ID="bibcode" datatype="char" arraysize="19">
<DESCRIPTION>The bibcode identifier for the record</DESCRIPTION>
</FIELD>
<FIELD ID="title" datatype="char" arraysize="*">
<DESCRIPTION>Title of the paper</DESCRIPTION>
</FIELD>
<FIELD ID="creator" datatype="char" arraysize="*">
<DESCRIPTION>List of authors</DESCRIPTION>
</FIELD>
<FIELD ID="source" datatype="char" arraysize="*">
<DESCRIPTION>Publication infromation</DESCRIPTION>
</FIELD>
<FIELD ID="date" datatype="char" arraysize="10">
<DESCRIPTION>Publication Date</DESCRIPTION>
</FIELD>
<FIELD ID="url" datatype="char" arraysize="*">
<DESCRIPTION>Resource URL</DESCRIPTION>
</FIELD>
<DATA>
<TABLEDATA>
<TR>
<TD>2023LRR....26....2A</TD>
<TD>Astrophysics with the Laser Interferometer Space Antenna</TD>
<TD>Amaro-Seoane, Pau; Andrews, Jeff; Arca Sedda, Manuel; Askar, Abbas; Baghi, Quentin; Balasov, Razvan; Bartos, Imre; Bavera, Simone S.; Bellovary, Jillian; Berry, Christopher P. L.; Berti, Emanuele; Bianchi, Stefano; Blecha, Laura; Blondin, Stéphane; Bogdanović, Tamara; Boissier, Samuel; Bonetti, Matteo; Bonoli, Silvia; Bortolas, Elisa; Breivik, Katelyn; Capelo, Pedro R.; Caramete, Laurentiu; Cattorini, Federico; Charisi, Maria; Chaty, Sylvain; Chen, Xian; Chruślińska, Martyna; Chua, Alvin J. K.; Church, Ross; Colpi, Monica; D'Orazio, Daniel; Danielski, Camilla; Davies, Melvyn B.; Dayal, Pratika; De Rosa, Alessandra; Derdzinski, Andrea; Destounis, Kyriakos; Dotti, Massimo; DuÅ£an, Ioana; Dvorkin, Irina; Fabj, Gaia; Foglizzo, Thierry; Ford, Saavik; Fouvry, Jean-Baptiste; Franchini, Alessia; Fragos, Tassos; Fryer, Chris; Gaspari, Massimo; Gerosa, Davide; Graziani, Luca; Groot, Paul; Habouzit, Melanie; Haggard, Daryl; Haiman, Zoltan; Han, Wen-Biao; Istrate, Alina; Johansson, Peter H.; Khan, Fazeel Mahmood; Kimpson, Tomas; Kokkotas, Kostas; Kong, Albert; Korol, Valeriya; Kremer, Kyle; Kupfer, Thomas; Lamberts, Astrid; Larson, Shane; Lau, Mike; Liu, Dongliang; Lloyd-Ronning, Nicole; Lodato, Giuseppe; Lupi, Alessandro; Ma, Chung-Pei; Maccarone, Tomas; Mandel, Ilya; Mangiagli, Alberto; Mapelli, Michela; Mathis, Stéphane; Mayer, Lucio; McGee, Sean; McKernan, Barry; Miller, M. Coleman; Mota, David F.; Mumpower, Matthew; Nasim, Syeda S.; Nelemans, Gijs; Noble, Scott; Pacucci, Fabio; Panessa, Francesca; Paschalidis, Vasileios; Pfister, Hugo; Porquet, Delphine; Quenby, John; Ricarte, Angelo; Röpke, Friedrich K.; Regan, John; Rosswog, Stephan; Ruiter, Ashley; Ruiz, Milton; Runnoe, Jessie; Schneider, Raffaella; Schnittman, Jeremy; Secunda, Amy; Sesana, Alberto; Seto, Naoki; Shao, Lijing; Shapiro, Stuart; Sopuerta, Carlos; Stone, Nicholas C.; Suvorov, Arthur; Tamanini, Nicola; Tamfal, Tomas; Tauris, Thomas; Temmink, Karel; Tomsick, John; Toonen, Silvia; Torres-Orjuela, Alejandro; Toscani, Martina; Tsokaros, Antonios; Unal, Caner; Vázquez-Aceves, Verónica; Valiante, Rosa; van Putten, Maurice; van Roestel, Jan; Vignali, Christian; Volonteri, Marta; Wu, Kinwah; Younsi, Ziri; Yu, Shenghua; Zane, Silvia; Zwick, Lorenz; Antonini, Fabio; Baibhav, Vishal; Barausse, Enrico; Bonilla Rivera, Alexander; Branchesi, Marica; Branduardi-Raymont, Graziella; Burdge, Kevin; Chakraborty, Srija; Cuadra, Jorge; Dage, Kristen; Davis, Benjamin; de Mink, Selma E.; Decarli, Roberto; Doneva, Daniela; Escoffier, Stephanie; Gandhi, Poshak; Haardt, Francesco; Lousto, Carlos O.; Nissanke, Samaya; Nordhaus, Jason; O'Shaughnessy, Richard; Portegies Zwart, Simon; Pound, Adam; Schussler, Fabian; Sergijenko, Olga; Spallicci, Alessandro; Vernieri, Daniele; Vigna-Gómez, Alejandro</TD>
<TD>Living Reviews in Relativity, Volume 26, Issue 1, article id.2</TD>
<TD>2023-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023LRR....26....2A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023Icar..39715520O</TD>
<TD>Spins and shapes of basaltic asteroids and the missing mantle problem</TD>
<TD>Oszkiewicz, Dagmara; Troianskyi, Volodymyr; Galád, Adrián; Hanuš, Josef; Ďurech, Josef; Wilawer, Emil; Marciniak, Anna; Kwiatkowski, Tomasz; Koleńczuk, Paweł; Skiff, Brian A.; Polakis, Tom; Moskovitz, Nicholas A.; Geier, Stefan; Föhring, Dóra; Hung, Denise; Gajdoš, Štefan; Világi, Jozef; Polčic, L. 'udovít; Kashuba, Volodymyr; Udovichenko, Sergei; Keir, Leonid; Benishek, Vladimir; Pray, Donald P.; Shevchenko, Vasilij; Krugly, Yurij; Kankiewicz, Paweł; Hasegawa, Sunao; Behrend, Raoul; Bernasconi, Laurent; Leroy, Arnaud; Roy, René; Ivanova, Oleksandra; Husárik, Marek; Simon, Andrii</TD>
<TD>Icarus, Volume 397, article id. 115520.</TD>
<TD>2023-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023Icar..39715520O</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.521.3127C</TD>
<TD>The Calar Alto CAFOS direct imaging first data release</TD>
<TD>Cortés-Contreras, M.; Solano, E.; Alonso-Hernández, J.; Cardiel, N.; Cruz, P.; Rodrigo, C.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 521, Issue 2, pp.3127-3149</TD>
<TD>2023-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.521.3127C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.521.1941A</TD>
<TD>Repeating periodic eruptions of the supernova impostor SN 2000ch</TD>
<TD>Aghakhanloo, Mojgan; Smith, Nathan; Milne, Peter; Andrews, Jennifer E.; Filippenko, Alexei V.; Jencson, Jacob E.; Sand, David J.; Van Dyk, Schuyler D.; Wyatt, Samuel; Zheng, WeiKang</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 521, Issue 2, pp.1941-1957</TD>
<TD>2023-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.521.1941A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.521.1880B</TD>
<TD>Photometric follow-up of 43 new eclipsing white dwarf plus main-sequence binaries from the ZTF survey</TD>
<TD>Brown, Alex J.; Parsons, Steven G.; van Roestel, Jan; Rebassa-Mansergas, Alberto; Breedt, Elmé; Dhillon, Vik S.; Dyer, Martin J.; Green, Matthew J.; Kerry, Paul; Littlefair, Stuart P.; Marsh, Thomas R.; Munday, James; Pelisoli, Ingrid; Sahman, David I.; Wild, James F.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 521, Issue 2, pp.1880-1896</TD>
<TD>2023-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.521.1880B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.521.1162D</TD>
<TD>SN 2021zny: an early flux excess combined with late-time oxygen emission suggests a double white dwarf merger event</TD>
<TD>Dimitriadis, Georgios; Maguire, Kate; Karambelkar, Viraj R.; Lebron, Ryan J.; Liu (刘 畅), Chang; Kozyreva, Alexandra; Miller, Adam A.; Ridden-Harper, Ryan; Anderson, Joseph P.; Chen, Ting-Wan; Coughlin, Michael; Valle, Massimo Della; Drake, Andrew; Galbany, Lluís; Gromadzki, Mariusz; Groom, Steven L.; Gutiérrez, Claudia P.; Ihanec, Nada; Inserra, Cosimo; Johansson, Joel; Müller-Bravo, Tomás E.; Nicholl, Matt; Polin, Abigail; Rusholme, Ben; Schulze, Steve; Sollerman, Jesper; Srivastav, Shubham; Taggart, Kirsty; Wang, Qinan; Yang (杨 轶), Yi; Young, David R.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 521, Issue 1, pp.1162-1183</TD>
<TD>2023-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.521.1162D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.521..389R</TD>
<TD>Day-time-scale variability in the radio light curve of the Tidal Disruption Event AT2022cmc: confirmation of a highly relativistic outflow</TD>
<TD>Rhodes, L.; Bright, J. S.; Fender, R.; Sfaradi, I.; Green, D. A.; Horesh, A.; Mooley, K.; Pasham, D.; Smartt, S.; Titterington, D. J.; van der Horst, A. J.; Williams, D. R. A.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 521, Issue 1, pp.389-395</TD>
<TD>2023-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.521..389R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.521...99W</TD>
<TD>Dwarf AGNs from variability for the origins of seeds (DAVOS): optical variability of broad-line dwarf AGNs from the zwicky transient facility</TD>
<TD>Wang, Z. Franklin; Burke, Colin J.; Liu, Xin; Shen, Yue</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 521, Issue 1, pp.99-113</TD>
<TD>2023-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.521...99W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.520.5635Y</TD>
<TD>Data release of the AST3-2 automatic survey from Dome A, Antarctica</TD>
<TD>Yang, Xu; Hu, Yi; Shang, Zhaohui; Ma, Bin; Ashley, Michael C. B.; Cui, Xiangqun; Du, Fujia; Fu, Jianning; Gong, Xuefei; Gu, Bozhong; Jiang, Peng; Li, Xiaoyan; Li, Zhengyang; Tao, Charling; Wang, Lifan; Xu, Lingzhe; Yang, Shi-hai; Yu, Ce; Yuan, Xiangyan; Zhou, Ji-lin; Zhu, Zhenxi</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 520, Issue 4, pp.5635-5650</TD>
<TD>2023-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.520.5635Y</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.520.5573F</TD>
<TD>Linking the interiors and surfaces of magnetic stars</TD>
<TD>Fuller, Jim; Mathis, Stéphane</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 520, Issue 4, pp.5573-5585</TD>
<TD>2023-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.520.5573F</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.520.5413F</TD>
<TD>A survey for variable young stars with small telescopes: VI - Analysis of the outbursting Be stars NSW 284, gaia 19eyy, and VES 263</TD>
<TD>Froebrich, Dirk; Hillenbrand, Lynne A.; Herbert, Carys; De, Kishalay; Eislöffel, Jochen; Campbell-White, Justyn; Kahar, Ruhee; Hambsch, Franz-Josef; Urtly, Thomas; Popowicz, Adam; Bernacki, Krzysztof; Malcher, Andrzej; Lasota, Slawomir; Fiolka, Jerzy; Jozwik-Wabik, Piotr; Dubois, Franky; Logie, Ludwig; Rau, Steve; Phillips, Mark; Fleming, George; Farfán, Rafael Gonzalez; Alfaro, Francisco C. Soldán; Nelson, Tim; Futcher, Stephen R. L.; Rolfe, Samantha M.; Campbell, David A.; Vale, Tony; Devine, Pat; Moździerski, Dawid; Mikołajczyk, Przemysław J.; Eggenstein, Heinz-Bernd; Rodriguez, Diego; Walton, Ivan L.; Vanaverbeke, Siegfried; Merrikin, Barry; Öğmen, Yenal; Perez, Alex Escartin; Aimar, Mario Morales; Piehler, Georg; Dover, Lord; Patel, Aashini L.; Miller, Niall; Finch, Jack; Hankins, Matt; Moore, Anna M.; Travouillon, Tony; Szczepanski, Marek</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 520, Issue 4, pp.5413-5432</TD>
<TD>2023-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.520.5413F</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.520.5283G</TD>
<TD>The TIME Table: rotation and ages of cool exoplanet host stars</TD>
<TD>Gaidos, Eric; Claytor, Zachary; Dungee, Ryan; Ali, Aleezah; Feiden, Gregory A.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 520, Issue 4, pp.5283-5304</TD>
<TD>2023-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.520.5283G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.520.4356N</TD>
<TD>The ASAS-SN bright supernova catalogue - V. 2018-2020</TD>
<TD>Neumann, K. D.; Holoien, T. W. -S.; Kochanek, C. S.; Stanek, K. Z.; Vallely, P. J.; Shappee, B. J.; Prieto, J. L.; Pessi, T.; Jayasinghe, T.; Brimacombe, J.; Bersier, D.; Aydi, E.; Basinger, C.; Beacom, J. F.; Bose, S.; Brown, J. S.; Chen, P.; Clocchiatti, A.; Desai, D. D.; Dong, Subo; Falco, E.; Holmbo, S.; Morrell, N.; Shields, J. V.; Sokolovsky, K. V.; Strader, J.; Stritzinger, M. D.; Swihart, S.; Thompson, T. A.; Way, Z.; Aslan, L.; Bishop, D. W.; Bock, G.; Bradshaw, J.; Cacella, P.; Castro-Morales, N.; Conseil, E.; Cornect, R.; Cruz, I.; Farfan, R. G.; Fernandez, J. M.; Gabuya, A.; Gonzalez-Carballo, J. -L.; Kendurkar, M. R.; Kiyota, S.; Koff, R. A.; Krannich, G.; Marples, P.; Masi, G.; Monard, L. A. G.; Muñoz, J. A.; Nicholls, B.; Post, R. S.; Pujic, Z.; Stone, G.; Tomasella, L.; Trappett, D. L.; Wiethoff, W. S.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 520, Issue 3, pp.4356-4369</TD>
<TD>2023-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.520.4356N</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.520.4209M</TD>
<TD>eRASSt J074426.3 + 291606: prompt accretion disc formation in a 'faint and slow' tidal disruption event</TD>
<TD>Malyali, A.; Liu, Z.; Merloni, A.; Rau, A.; Buchner, J.; Ciroi, S.; Di Mille, F.; Grotova, I.; Dwelly, T.; Nandra, K.; Salvato, M.; Homan, D.; Krumpe, M.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 520, Issue 3, pp.4209-4225</TD>
<TD>2023-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.520.4209M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.520.3355S</TD>
<TD>Tilted discs in six poorly studied cataclysmic variables</TD>
<TD>Stefanov, Stefan Y.; Stefanov, Atanas K.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 520, Issue 3, pp.3355-3367</TD>
<TD>2023-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.520.3355S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.520.2965X</TD>
<TD>SN 2018hna: Adding a piece to the puzzles of the explosion of blue supergiants</TD>
<TD>Xiang, Danfeng; Wang, Xiaofeng; Zhang, Xinghan; Sai, Hanna; Zhang, Jujia; Brink, Thomas G.; Filippenko, Alexei V.; Mo, Jun; Zhang, Tianmeng; Chen, Zhihao; Dessart, Luc; Li, Zhitong; Yan, Shengyu; Blinnikov, Sergei I.; Rui, Liming; Baron, E.; DerKacy, J. M.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 520, Issue 2, pp.2965-2982</TD>
<TD>2023-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.520.2965X</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.520.2887L</TD>
<TD>The simulated catalogue of optical transients and correlated hosts (SCOTCH)</TD>
<TD>Lokken, Martine; Gagliano, Alexander; Narayan, Gautham; Hložek, Renée; Kessler, Richard; Crenshaw, John Franklin; Salo, Laura; Alves, Catarina S.; Chatterjee, Deep; Vincenzi, Maria; Malz, Alex I.; LSST Dark Energy Science Collaboration</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 520, Issue 2, pp.2887-2912</TD>
<TD>2023-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.520.2887L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.520.2547R</TD>
<TD>Enabling discovery of gravitationally lensed explosive transients: a new method to build an all-sky watch list of groups and clusters of galaxies</TD>
<TD>Ryczanowski, Dan; Smith, Graham P.; Bianconi, Matteo; McGee, Sean; Robertson, Andrew; Massey, Richard; Jauzac, Mathilde</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 520, Issue 2, pp.2547-2557</TD>
<TD>2023-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.520.2547R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.520.2417W</TD>
<TD>The radio detection and accretion properties of the peculiar nuclear transient AT 2019avd</TD>
<TD>Wang, Yanan; Baldi, Ranieri D.; del Palacio, Santiago; Guolo, Muryel; Yang, Xiaolong; Zhang, Yangkang; Done, Chris; Castro Segura, Noel; Pasham, Dheeraj R.; Middleton, Matthew; Altamirano, Diego; Gandhi, Poshak; Qiao, Erlin; Jiang, Ning; Yan, Hongliang; Giroletti, Marcello; Migliori, Giulia; McHardy, Ian; Panessa, Francesca; Jin, Chichuan; Shen, Rongfeng; Dai, Lixin</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 520, Issue 2, pp.2417-2435</TD>
<TD>2023-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.520.2417W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.520.2386R</TD>
<TD>The value-added catalogue of ASAS-SN eclipsing binaries - II. Properties of extra-physics systems</TD>
<TD>Rowan, D. M.; Jayasinghe, T.; Stanek, K. Z.; Kochanek, C. S.; Thompson, Todd A.; Shappee, B. J.; Holoien, T. W. -S.; Prieto, J. L.; Giles, W.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 520, Issue 2, pp.2386-2404</TD>
<TD>2023-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.520.2386R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.520.1807C</TD>
<TD>Broad-line region in NGC 4151 monitored by two decades of reverberation mapping campaigns - I. Evolution of structure and kinematics</TD>
<TD>Chen, Yong-Jie; Bao, Dong-Wei; Zhai, Shuo; Fang, Feng-Na; Hu, Chen; Du, Pu; Yang, Sen; Yao, Zhu-Heng; Li, Yan-Rong; Brotherton, Michael S.; McLane, Jacob N.; Zastrocky, T. E.; Olson, Kianna A.; Bon, Edi; Bai, Hua-Rui; Fu, Yi-Xin; Liu, Jun-Rong; Wang, Yi-Lin; Maithil, Jaya; Kobulnicky, H. A.; Dale, D. A.; Adelman, C.; Caradonna, M. J.; Carter, Z.; Favro, J.; Ferguson, A. J.; Gonzalez, I. M.; Hadding, L. M.; Hagler, H. D.; Murphree, G.; Oeur, M.; Rogers, C. J.; Roth, T.; Schonsberg, S.; Stack, T. R.; Wang, Jian-Min</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 520, Issue 2, pp.1807-1831</TD>
<TD>2023-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.520.1807C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023Icar..39415481.</TD>
<TD>Ed. Board</TD>
<TD />
<TD>Icarus, Volume 394, article id. 115481.</TD>
<TD>2023-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023Icar..39415481.</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023Icar..39415442B</TD>
<TD>Preliminary estimates of the Zwicky Transient Facility 'Ayló'chaxnim asteroid population completeness</TD>
<TD>Bolin, B. T.; Ahumada, T.; Dokkum, P. van; Fremling, C.; Hardegree-Ullman, K. K.; Purdum, J. N.; Serabyn, E.; Southworth, J.</TD>
<TD>Icarus, Volume 394, article id. 115442.</TD>
<TD>2023-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023Icar..39415442B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023AJ....165..150K</TD>
<TD>Comet 108P/Ciffreo: The Blob</TD>
<TD>Kim, Yoonyoung; Jewitt, David; Luu, Jane; Li, Jing; Mutchler, Max</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 165, Issue 4, id.150, 8 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023AJ....165..150K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023AJ....165..148H</TD>
<TD>Spectroscopically Identified Cataclysmic Variables from the LAMOST Survey. II. Period Estimates</TD>
<TD>Hou, Wen; Luo, A. -Li; Dong, Yi-Qiao; Chen, Xiang-Lei; Bai, Zhong-Rui</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 165, Issue 4, id.148, 33 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023AJ....165..148H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023AJ....165..142K</TD>
<TD>Multifilter Time-series Observations of Eleven Blue Short-period ATLAS Variable Stars</TD>
<TD>Koen, C.; Schaffenroth, V.; Kniazev, A.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 165, Issue 4, id.142, 17 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023AJ....165..142K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023AJ....165..141H</TD>
<TD>Localizing Sources of Variability in Crowded TESS Photometry</TD>
<TD>Higgins, Michael E.; Bell, Keaton J.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 165, Issue 4, id.141, 13 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023AJ....165..141H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023AJ....165..138F</TD>
<TD>Detecting Long-period Variability in the SDSS Stripe 82 Standards Catalog</TD>
<TD>Fatović, Marta; Palaversa, Lovro; Tisanić, Krešimir; Thanjavur, Karun; Ivezić, Željko; Kovačević, Andjelka B.; Ilić, Dragana; Č. Popović, Luka</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 165, Issue 4, id.138, 13 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023AJ....165..138F</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023AJ....165..137O</TD>
<TD>A Distance Measurement to M33 Using Optical Photometry of Mira Variables</TD>
<TD>Ou, Jia-Yu; Ngeow, Chow-Choong; Bhardwaj, Anupam; Graham, Matthew J.; Laher, Russ R.; Masci, Frank J.; Riddle, Reed</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 165, Issue 4, id.137, 11 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023AJ....165..137O</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023A&amp;A...672A..69R</TD>
<TD>Identifying and characterising the population of hot sub-luminous stars with multi-colour MeerLICHT data</TD>
<TD>Ranaivomanana, P.; Johnston, C.; Groot, P. J.; Aerts, C.; Lees, R.; IJspeert, L.; Bloemen, S.; Klein-Wolt, M.; Woudt, P.; Körding, E.; Le Poole, R.; Pieterse, D.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 672, id.A69, 24 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023A&amp;A...672A..69R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023Univ....9..161M</TD>
<TD>Yukawa–Casimir Wormholes in f(Q) Gravity</TD>
<TD>Mishra, Ambuj Kumar; Shweta; Sharma, Umesh Kumar</TD>
<TD>Universe, vol. 9, issue 4, p. 161</TD>
<TD>2023-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023Univ....9..161M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023Univ....9..138A</TD>
<TD>Quiescent and Active Galactic Nuclei as Factories of Merging Compact Objects in the Era of Gravitational Wave Astronomy</TD>
<TD>Arca Sedda, Manuel; Naoz, Smadar; Kocsis, Bence</TD>
<TD>Universe, vol. 9, issue 3, p. 138</TD>
<TD>2023-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023Univ....9..138A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023SCPMA..6630411Z</TD>
<TD>Exploring the nature of black hole and gravity with an imminent merging binary of supermassive black holes</TD>
<TD>Zhong, Xingyu; Han, Wen-Biao; Luo, Ziren; Wu, Yueliang</TD>
<TD>Science China Physics, Mechanics &amp;amp; Astronomy, Volume 66, Issue 3, article id.230411</TD>
<TD>2023-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023SCPMA..6630411Z</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023RAA....23c5013L</TD>
<TD>Limiting Magnitudes of the Wide Field Survey Telescope (WFST)</TD>
<TD>Lei, Lei; Zhu, Qing-Feng; Kong, Xu; Wang, Ting-Gui; Zheng, Xian-Zhong; Shi, Dong-Dong; Fan, Lu-Lu; Liu, Wei</TD>
<TD>Research in Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 23, Issue 3, id.035013, 8 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023RAA....23c5013L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023PSJ.....4...47Y</TD>
<TD>Comet P/2021 HS (PANSTARRS) and the Challenge of Detecting Low-activity Comets</TD>
<TD>Ye, Quanzhi; Kelley, Michael S. P.; Bauer, James M.; Farnham, Tony L.; Bodewits, Dennis; Buzzi, Luca; Weryk, Robert; Masci, Frank J.; Medford, Michael S.; Riddle, Reed; Wold, Avery</TD>
<TD>The Planetary Science Journal, Volume 4, Issue 3, id.47, 14 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023PSJ.....4...47Y</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023PSJ.....4...43H</TD>
<TD>Observational Characterization of Main-belt Comet and Candidate Main-belt Comet Nuclei</TD>
<TD>Hsieh, Henry H.; Micheli, Marco; Kelley, Michael S. P.; Knight, Matthew M.; Moskovitz, Nicholas A.; Pittichová, Jana; Sheppard, Scott S.; Thirouin, Audrey; Trujillo, Chadwick A.; Wainscoat, Richard J.; Weryk, Robert J.; Ye, Quanzhi</TD>
<TD>The Planetary Science Journal, Volume 4, Issue 3, id.43, 22 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023PSJ.....4...43H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023PASP..135c4102K</TD>
<TD>Comparison of Different Tidal Disruption Event Light Curve Models with TiDE, a New Modular Open Source Code</TD>
<TD>Kovács-Stermeczky, Zsófia V.; Vinkó, József</TD>
<TD>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 135, Issue 1045, id.034102, 16 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023PASP..135c4102K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023NatAs...7..339Y</TD>
<TD>Magnetar spin-down glitch clearing the way for FRB-like bursts and a pulsed radio episode</TD>
<TD>Younes, G.; Baring, M. G.; Harding, A. K.; Enoto, T.; Wadiasingh, Z.; Pearlman, A. B.; Ho, W. C. G.; Guillot, S.; Arzoumanian, Z.; Borghese, A.; Gendreau, K.; Göǧüş, E.; Güver, T.; van der Horst, A. J.; Hu, C. -P.; Jaisawal, G. K.; Kouveliotou, C.; Lin, L.; Majid, W. A.</TD>
<TD>Nature Astronomy, Volume 7, p. 339-350</TD>
<TD>2023-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023NatAs...7..339Y</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.tmp..880M</TD>
<TD>Shock cooling emission from explosions of red super-giants: I. A numerically calibrated analytic model</TD>
<TD>Morag, Jonathan; Sapir, Nir; Waxman, Eli</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Advance Access</TD>
<TD>2023-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.tmp..880M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.tmp..810U</TD>
<TD>Light-curve modelling for the initial rising phase of rapidly-evolving transients powered by continuous outflow</TD>
<TD>Uno, Kohki; Maeda, Keiichi</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Advance Access</TD>
<TD>2023-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.tmp..810U</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.tmp..753H</TD>
<TD>Multiwavelength monitoring of the nucleus in PBC J2333.9-2343: the giant radio galaxy with a blazar-like core</TD>
<TD>Hernández-García, L.; Panessa, F.; Bruni, G.; Bassani, L.; Arévalo, P.; Patiño-Alvarez, V. M.; Tramacere, A.; Lira, P.; Sánchez-Sáez, P.; Bauer, F. E.; Chavushyan, V.; Carraro, R.; Förster, F.; Arancibia, A. M. Muñoz; Ubertini, P.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Advance Access</TD>
<TD>2023-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.tmp..753H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.tmp..705S</TD>
<TD>The path from the chinese and japanese observations of supernova 1181 AD, to a type iax supernova, to the merger of CO and ONe white dwarfs</TD>
<TD>Schaefer, Bradley E.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Advance Access</TD>
<TD>2023-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.tmp..705S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.520.1044M</TD>
<TD>Investigating the variability of Swift-BAT blazars with NICER</TD>
<TD>Mundo, Sergio A.; Mushotzky, Richard</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 520, Issue 1, pp.1044-1054</TD>
<TD>2023-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.520.1044M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.520..828D</TD>
<TD>Automated classification of eclipsing binary systems in the VVV Survey</TD>
<TD>Daza-Perilla, I. V.; Gramajo, L. V.; Lares, M.; Palma, T.; Ferreira Lopes, C. E.; Minniti, D.; Clariá, J. J.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 520, Issue 1, pp.828-838</TD>
<TD>2023-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.520..828D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.520..684G</TD>
<TD>Core-collapse supernovae in the Dark Energy Survey: luminosity functions and host galaxy demographics</TD>
<TD>Grayling, M.; Gutiérrez, C. P.; Sullivan, M.; Wiseman, P.; Vincenzi, M.; Galbany, L.; Möller, A.; Brout, D.; Davis, T. M.; Frohmaier, C.; Graur, O.; Kelsey, L.; Lidman, C.; Popovic, B.; Smith, M.; Toy, M.; Tucker, B. E.; Zontos, Z.; Abbott, T. M. C.; Aguena, M.; Allam, S.; Andrade-Oliveira, F.; Annis, J.; Asorey, J.; Bacon, D.; Bertin, E.; Bocquet, S.; Brooks, D.; Carnero Rosell, A.; Carollo, D.; Carrasco Kind, M.; Carretero, J.; Costanzi, M.; da Costa, L. N.; Pereira, M. E. S.; De Vicente, J.; Desai, S.; Diehl, H. T.; Doel, P.; Everett, S.; Ferrero, I.; Friedel, D.; Frieman, J.; García-Bellido, J.; Gatti, M.; Gruen, D.; Gschwend, J.; Gutierrez, G.; Hinton, S. R.; Hollowood, D. L.; Honscheid, K.; James, D. J.; Kuehn, K.; Kuropatkin, N.; Lewis, G. F.; Malik, U.; March, M.; Menanteau, F.; Miquel, R.; Morgan, R.; Ogando, R. L. C.; Palmese, A.; Paz-Chinchón, F.; Pieres, A.; Plazas Malagón, A. A.; Rodriguez-Monroy, M.; Romer, A. K.; Roodman, A.; Sanchez, E.; Scarpine, V.; Sevilla-Noarbe, I.; Suchyta, E.; Tarle, G.; To, C.; Tucker, D. L.; Varga, T. N.; DES Collaboration</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 520, Issue 1, pp.684-701</TD>
<TD>2023-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.520..684G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.520..613A</TD>
<TD>GRB 160410A: The first chemical study of the interstellar medium of a short GRB</TD>
<TD>Agüí Fernández, J. F.; Thöne, C. C.; Kann, D. A.; de Ugarte Postigo, A.; Selsing, J.; Schady, P.; Yates, R. M.; Greiner, J.; Oates, S. R.; Malesani, D. B.; Xu, D.; Klotz, A.; Campana, S.; Rossi, A.; Perley, D. A.; Blažek, M.; D'Avanzo, P.; Giunta, A.; Hartmann, D.; Heintz, K. E.; Jakobsson, P.; Kirkpatrick, C. C., IV; Kouveliotou, C.; Melandri, A.; Pugliese, G.; Salvaterra, R.; Starling, R. L. C.; Tanvir, N. R.; Vergani, S. D.; Wiersema, K.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 520, Issue 1, pp.613-636</TD>
<TD>2023-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.520..613A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.520..560H</TD>
<TD>The core normal Type Ia supernova 2019np - an overall spherical explosion with an aspherical surface layer and an aspherical &lt;SUP&gt;56&lt;/SUP&gt;Ni core</TD>
<TD>Hoeflich, Peter; Yang, Yi; Baade, Dietrich; Cikota, Aleksandar; Maund, Justyn R.; Mishra, Divya; Patat, Ferdinando; Patra, Kishore C.; Wang, Lifan; Wheeler, J. Craig; Filippenko, Alexei V.; Gal-Yam, Avishay; Schulze, Steven</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 520, Issue 1, pp.560-582</TD>
<TD>2023-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.520..560H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.519.6349D</TD>
<TD>Optical/γ-ray blazar flare correlations: understanding the high-energy emission process using ASAS-SN and Fermi light curves</TD>
<TD>de Jaeger, T.; Shappee, B. J.; Kochanek, C. S.; Hinkle, J. T.; Garrappa, S.; Liodakis, I.; Franckowiak, A.; Stanek, K. Z.; Beacom, J. F.; Prieto, J. L.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 519, Issue 4, pp.6349-6380</TD>
<TD>2023-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.519.6349D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.519.5787R</TD>
<TD>Close encounters of tight binary stars with stellar-mass black holes</TD>
<TD>Ryu, Taeho; Perna, Rosalba; Pakmor, Ruediger; Ma, Jing-Ze; Farmer, Rob; de Mink, Selma E.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 519, Issue 4, pp.5787-5799</TD>
<TD>2023-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.519.5787R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.519.5760L</TD>
<TD>The study of 11 contact binaries with mass ratios less than 0.1</TD>
<TD>Liu, Xin-Yi; Li, Kai; Michel, Raul; Gao, Xiang; Gao, Xing; Liu, Fei; Yin, Shi-Peng; Wang, Xi; Sun, Guo-You</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 519, Issue 4, pp.5760-5774</TD>
<TD>2023-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.519.5760L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.519.5689M</TD>
<TD>RR Lyrae stars as probes of the outer Galactic halo: chemical and kinematic analysis of a pilot sample</TD>
<TD>Medina, Gustavo E.; Hansen, Camilla J.; Muñoz, Ricardo R.; Grebel, Eva K.; Vivas, A. Katherina; Carlin, Jeffrey L.; Martínez-Vázquez, Clara E.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 519, Issue 4, pp.5689-5722</TD>
<TD>2023-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.519.5689M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.519.5454K</TD>
<TD>Fundamental parameters for double-lined spectroscopic and detached eclipsing binary system J064726.39 + 223431.6</TD>
<TD>Kovalev, Mikhail; Wang, Song; Chen, Xuefei; Han, Zhanwen</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 519, Issue 4, pp.5454-5471</TD>
<TD>2023-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.519.5454K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.519.5271C</TD>
<TD>The ASAS-SN catalogue of variable stars X: discovery of 116 000 new variable stars using G-band photometry</TD>
<TD>Christy, C. T.; Jayasinghe, T.; Stanek, K. Z.; Kochanek, C. S.; Thompson, T. A.; Shappee, B. J.; Holoien, T. W. -S.; Prieto, J. L.; Dong, Subo; Giles, W.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 519, Issue 4, pp.5271-5287</TD>
<TD>2023-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.519.5271C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.519.4841D</TD>
<TD>The quadrupole in the local Hubble parameter: first constraints using Type Ia supernova data and forecasts for future surveys</TD>
<TD>Dhawan, Suhail; Borderies, Antonin; Macpherson, Hayley J.; Heinesen, Asta</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 519, Issue 4, pp.4841-4855</TD>
<TD>2023-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.519.4841D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.519.3923C</TD>
<TD>Pulsar revival in neutron star mergers: multimessenger prospects for the discovery of pre-merger coherent radio emission</TD>
<TD>Cooper, A. J.; Gupta, O.; Wadiasingh, Z.; Wijers, R. A. M. J.; Boersma, O. M.; Andreoni, I.; Rowlinson, A.; Gourdji, K.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 519, Issue 3, pp.3923-3946</TD>
<TD>2023-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.519.3923C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.519.3881G</TD>
<TD>Deep drilling in the time domain with DECam: survey characterization</TD>
<TD>Graham, Melissa L.; Knop, Robert A.; Kennedy, Thomas D.; Nugent, Peter E.; Bellm, Eric; Catelan, Márcio; Patel, Avi; Smotherman, Hayden; Soraisam, Monika; Stetzler, Steven; Aldoroty, Lauren N.; Awbrey, Autumn; Baeza-Villagra, Karina; Bernardinelli, Pedro H.; Bianco, Federica; Brout, Dillon; Clarke, Riley; Clarkson, William I.; Collett, Thomas; Davenport, James R. A.; Fu, Shenming; Gizis, John E.; Heinze, Ari; Hu, Lei; Jha, Saurabh W.; Jurić, Mario; Kalmbach, J. Bryce; Kim, Alex; Lee, Chien-Hsiu; Lidman, Chris; Magee, Mark; Martínez-Vázquez, Clara E.; Matheson, Thomas; Narayan, Gautham; Palmese, Antonella; Phillips, Christopher A.; Rabus, Markus; Rest, Armin; Rodríguez-Segovia, Nicolás; Street, Rachel; Vivas, A. Katherina; Wang, Lifan; Wolf, Nicholas; Yang, Jiawen</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 519, Issue 3, pp.3881-3902</TD>
<TD>2023-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.519.3881G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023JHEAp..37...51S</TD>
<TD>Synchrotron self-compton emission in the two-component jet model for gamma-ray bursts</TD>
<TD>Sato, Yuri; Obayashi, Kaori; Theodre Zhang, B.; Tanaka, Shuta J.; Murase, Kohta; Ohira, Yutaka; Yamazaki, Ryo</TD>
<TD>Journal of High Energy Astrophysics, Volume 37, p. 51-61.</TD>
<TD>2023-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023JHEAp..37...51S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023ApJS..265...27B</TD>
<TD>Young Stellar Objects, Accretion Disks, and Their Variability with Rubin Observatory LSST</TD>
<TD>Bonito, R.; Venuti, L.; Ustamujic, S.; Yoachim, P.; Street, R. A.; Prisinzano, L.; Hartigan, P.; Guarcello, M. G.; Stassun, K. G.; Giannini, T.; Feigelson, E. D.; Caratti o Garatti, A.; Orlando, S.; Clarkson, W. I.; McGehee, P.; Bellm, E. C.; Gizis, J. E.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 265, Issue 1, id.27, 8 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023ApJS..265...27B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023ApJ...946L...3T</TD>
<TD>Observable Signatures of Stellar-mass Black Holes in Active Galactic Nuclei</TD>
<TD>Tagawa, Hiromichi; Kimura, Shigeo S.; Haiman, Zoltán; Perna, Rosalba; Bartos, Imre</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 946, Issue 1, id.L3, 8 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023ApJ...946L...3T</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023ApJ...946...35L</TD>
<TD>A Population Study of the Radio Emission of Fast Blue Optical Transients</TD>
<TD>Liu, Jian-Feng; Liu, Liang-Duan; Yu, Yun-Wei; Zhu, Jin-Ping</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 946, Issue 1, id.35, 7 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023ApJ...946...35L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023ApJ...946...31V</TD>
<TD>Searching for Supernovae in HETDEX Data Release 3</TD>
<TD>Vinkó, József; Thomas, Benjamin P.; Wheeler, J. Craig; Ho, Anna Y. Q.; Cooper, Erin Mentuch; Gebhardt, Karl; Ciardullo, Robin; Farrow, Daniel J.; Hill, Gary J.; Jäger, Zoltán; Kollatschny, Wolfram; Liu, Chenxu; Regős, Enikő; Sárneczky, Krisztián</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 946, Issue 1, id.31, 14 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023ApJ...946...31V</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023ApJ...945L..34M</TD>
<TD>Unusual Hard X-Ray Flares Caught in NICER Monitoring of the Binary Supermassive Black Hole Candidate AT2019cuk/Tick Tock/SDSS J1430+2303</TD>
<TD>Masterson, Megan; Kara, Erin; Pasham, Dheeraj R.; D'Orazio, Daniel J.; Walton, Dominic J.; Fabian, Andrew C.; Lucchini, Matteo; Remillard, Ronald A.; Arzoumanian, Zaven; Burkhonov, Otabek; Choi, Hyeonho; Ehgamberdiev, Shuhrat A.; Ferrara, Elizabeth C.; Guolo, Muryel; Im, Myungshin; Kim, Yonggi; Mirzaqulov, Davron O.; Paek, Gregory S. H.; Sung, Hyun-Il; Yoon, Joh-Na</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 945, Issue 2, id.L34, 18 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023ApJ...945L..34M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023ApJ...945..141R</TD>
<TD>Discovery of Two Polars from a Crossmatch of ZTF and the SRG/eFEDS X-Ray Catalog</TD>
<TD>Rodriguez, Antonio C.; Kulkarni, Shrinivas R.; Prince, Thomas A.; Szkody, Paula; Burdge, Kevin B.; Caiazzo, Ilaria; van Roestel, Jan; Vanderbosch, Zachary P.; El-Badry, Kareem; Bellm, Eric C.; Gänsicke, Boris T.; Graham, Matthew J.; Mahabal, Ashish A.; Masci, Frank J.; Mróz, Przemek; Riddle, Reed; Rusholme, Ben</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 945, Issue 2, id.141, 15 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023ApJ...945..141R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023ApJ...945..104T</TD>
<TD>Precursors of Supernovae from Mass Eruption: Prospects for Early Warning of Nearby Core-collapse Supernovae</TD>
<TD>Tsuna, Daichi; Takei, Yuki; Shigeyama, Toshikazu</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 945, Issue 2, id.104, 11 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023ApJ...945..104T</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023ApJ...945...98V</TD>
<TD>Prospects for Extending the Core-collapse Supernova Detection Horizon Using High-energy Neutrinos</TD>
<TD>Valtonen-Mattila, Nora; O'Sullivan, Erin</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 945, Issue 2, id.98, 6 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023ApJ...945...98V</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023ApJ...945...89S</TD>
<TD>Differential Interferometric Signatures of Close Binaries of Supermassive Black Holes in Active Galactic Nuclei. II. Merged Broad-line Regions</TD>
<TD>Songsheng, Yu-Yang; Wang, Jian-Min</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 945, Issue 2, id.89, 19 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023ApJ...945...89S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023ApJ...945...86L</TD>
<TD>Unstable Mass Transfer from a Main-sequence Star to a Supermassive Black Hole and Quasiperiodic Eruptions</TD>
<TD>Linial, Itai; Sari, Re'em</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 945, Issue 2, id.86, 11 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023ApJ...945...86L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023ApJ...945...83M</TD>
<TD>RR Lyrae Mid-infrared Period-Luminosity-Metallicity and Period-Wesenheit-Metallicity Relations Based on Gaia DR3 Parallaxes</TD>
<TD>Mullen, Joseph P.; Marengo, Massimo; Martínez-Vázquez, Clara E.; Chaboyer, Brian; Bono, Giuseppe; Braga, Vittorio F.; Dall'Ora, Massimo; D'Orazi, Valentina; Fabrizio, Michele; Monelli, Matteo; Thévenin, Frédéric</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 945, Issue 1, id.83, 10 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023ApJ...945...83M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023ApJ...945...46S</TD>
<TD>Inferencing Progenitor and Explosion Properties of Evolving Core-collapse Supernovae from Zwicky Transient Facility Light Curves</TD>
<TD>Subrayan, Bhagya M.; Milisavljevic, Dan; Moriya, Takashi J.; Weil, Kathryn E.; Lentner, Geoffery; Linvill, Mark; Banovetz, John; Garretson, Braden; Reynolds, Jack; Sravan, Niharika; Chornock, Ryan; Margutti, Raffaella</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 945, Issue 1, id.46, 20 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023ApJ...945...46S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023ApJ...945...30A</TD>
<TD>VERITAS and Fermi-LAT Constraints on the Gamma-Ray Emission from Superluminous Supernovae SN2015bn and SN2017egm</TD>
<TD>Acharyya, A.; Adams, C. B.; Bangale, P.; Benbow, W.; Buckley, J. H.; Capasso, M.; Dwarkadas, V. V.; Errando, M.; Falcone, A.; Feng, Q.; Finley, J. P.; Foote, G. M.; Fortson, L.; Furniss, A.; Gallagher, G.; Gent, A.; Hanlon, W. F.; Hervet, O.; Holder, J.; Humensky, T. B.; Jin, W.; Kaaret, P.; Kertzman, M.; Kherlakian, M.; Kieda, D.; Kleiner, T. K.; Kumar, S.; Lang, M. J.; Lundy, M.; Maier, G.; McGrath, C. E.; Millis, J.; Moriarty, P.; Mukherjee, R.; Nievas-Rosillo, M.; O'Brien, S.; Ong, R. A.; Patel, S. R.; Pfrang, K.; Pohl, M.; Pueschel, E.; Quinn, J.; Ragan, K.; Reynolds, P. T.; Ribeiro, D.; Roache, E.; Ryan, J. L.; Sadeh, I.; Santander, M.; Sembroski, G. H.; Shang, R.; Splettstoesser, M.; Tak, D.; Tucci, J. V.; Weinstein, A.; Williams, D. A.; Metzger, B. D.; Nicholl, M.; Vurm, I.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 945, Issue 1, id.30, 14 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023ApJ...945...30A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023AJ....165..120K</TD>
<TD>TOI-5205b: A Short-period Jovian Planet Transiting a Mid-M Dwarf</TD>
<TD>Kanodia, Shubham; Mahadevan, Suvrath; Libby-Roberts, Jessica; Stefansson, Gudmundur; Cañas, Caleb I.; Piette, Anjali A. A.; Boss, Alan; Teske, Johanna; Chambers, John; Zeimann, Greg; Monson, Andrew; Robertson, Paul; Ninan, Joe P.; Lin, Andrea S. J.; Bender, Chad F.; Cochran, William D.; Diddams, Scott A.; Gupta, Arvind F.; Halverson, Samuel; Hawley, Suzanne; Kobulnicky, Henry A.; Metcalf, Andrew J.; Parker, Brock A.; Powers, Luke; Ramsey, Lawrence W.; Roy, Arpita; Schwab, Christian; Swaby, Tera N.; Terrien, Ryan C.; Wisniewski, John</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 165, Issue 3, id.120, 20 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023AJ....165..120K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023AJ....165..119Y</TD>
<TD>ELM of ELM-WD: An Extremely-low-mass Hot Star Discovered in LAMOST Survey</TD>
<TD>Yuan, Hailong; Li, Zhenwei; Bai, Zhongrui; Dong, Yiqiao; Wang, Mengxin; Yu, Sicheng; Chen, Xuefei; Zhao, Yongheng; Chu, Yaoquan; Zhang, Haotong</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 165, Issue 3, id.119, 12 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023AJ....165..119Y</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023AJ....165..118A</TD>
<TD>A Reinforcement Learning-Based Follow-up Framework</TD>
<TD>Astudillo, Javiera; Protopapas, Pavlos; Pichara, Karim; Becker, Ignacio</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 165, Issue 3, id.118, 15 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023AJ....165..118A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023AJ....165..111T</TD>
<TD>The Solar System Notification Alert Processing System (SNAPS): Design, Architecture, and First Data Release (SNAPShot1)</TD>
<TD>Trilling, David E.; Gowanlock, Michael; Kramer, Daniel; McNeill, Andrew; Donnelly, Brian; Butler, Nat; Kececioglu, John</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 165, Issue 3, id.111, 17 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023AJ....165..111T</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023AJ....165...90M</TD>
<TD>Investigating Stellar Variability in the Open Cluster Region NGC 381</TD>
<TD>Maurya, Jayanand; Joshi, Y. C.; Panchal, A.; Gour, A. S.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 165, Issue 3, id.90, 17 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023AJ....165...90M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023AJ....165...80P</TD>
<TD>Three Ultra-short-period Contact Eclipsing Binary Systems Mined from Massive Astronomical Surveys</TD>
<TD>Papageorgiou, Athanasios; Christopoulou, Panagiota-Eleftheria; Ferreira Lopes, C. E.; Lalounta, Eleni; Catelan, Márcio; Drake, Andrew J.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 165, Issue 3, id.80, 12 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023AJ....165...80P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023AJ....165...77Z</TD>
<TD>A Multilevel Scheduling Framework for Distributed Time-domain Large-area Sky Survey Telescope Array</TD>
<TD>Zhang, Yajie; Yu, Ce; Sun, Chao; Shang, Zhaohui; Hu, Yi; Zhi, Huiyu; Yang, Jinmao; Tang, Shanjiang</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 165, Issue 3, id.77, 15 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023AJ....165...77Z</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023A&amp;A...671A.158P</TD>
<TD>Forbidden hugs in pandemic times. IV. Panchromatic evolution of three luminous red novae</TD>
<TD>Pastorello, A.; Valerin, G.; Fraser, M.; Reguitti, A.; Elias-Rosa, N.; Filippenko, A. V.; Rojas-Bravo, C.; Tartaglia, L.; Reynolds, T. M.; Valenti, S.; Andrews, J. E.; Ashall, C.; Bostroem, K. A.; Brink, T. G.; Burke, J.; Cai, Y. -Z.; Cappellaro, E.; Coulter, D. A.; Dastidar, R.; Davis, K. W.; Dimitriadis, G.; Fiore, A.; Foley, R. J.; Fugazza, D.; Galbany, L.; Gangopadhyay, A.; Geier, S.; Gutiérrez, C. P.; Haislip, J.; Hiramatsu, D.; Holmbo, S.; Howell, D. A.; Hsiao, E. Y.; Hung, T.; Jha, S. W.; Kankare, E.; Karamehmetoglu, E.; Kilpatrick, C. D.; Kotak, R.; Kouprianov, V.; Kravtsov, T.; Kumar, S.; Li, Z. -T.; Lundquist, M. J.; Lundqvist, P.; Matilainen, K.; Mazzali, P. A.; McCully, C.; Misra, K.; Morales-Garoffolo, A.; Moran, S.; Morrell, N.; Newsome, M.; Padilla Gonzalez, E.; Pan, Y. -C.; Pellegrino, C.; Phillips, M. M.; Pignata, G.; Piro, A. L.; Reichart, D. E.; Rest, A.; Salmaso, I.; Sand, D. J.; Siebert, M. R.; Smartt, S. J.; Smith, K. W.; Srivastav, S.; Stritzinger, M. D.; Taggart, K.; Tinyanont, S.; Yan, S. -Y.; Wang, L.; Wang, X. -F.; Williams, S. C.; Wyatt, S.; Zhang, T. -M.; de Boer, T.; Chambers, K.; Gao, H.; Magnier, E.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 671, id.A158, 33 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023A&amp;A...671A.158P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023Univ....9...94H</TD>
<TD>Hubble Tension: The Evidence of New Physics</TD>
<TD>Hu, Jian-Ping; Wang, Fa-Yin</TD>
<TD>Universe, vol. 9, issue 2, p. 94</TD>
<TD>2023-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023Univ....9...94H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023Symm...15..383O</TD>
<TD>On the Traversable Yukawa–Casimir Wormholes</TD>
<TD>Oliveira, Pedro Henrique Ferreira de; Alencar, Geová; Jardim, Ivan Carneiro; Landim, Ricardo Renan</TD>
<TD>Symmetry, vol. 15, issue 2, p. 383</TD>
<TD>2023-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023Symm...15..383O</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023SCPMA..6629511L</TD>
<TD>Forecast of cosmological constraints with type Ia supernovae from the Chinese Space Station Telescope</TD>
<TD>Li, Shi-Yu; Li, Yun-Long; Zhang, Tianmeng; Vinkó, József; Regős, Enikő; Wang, Xiaofeng; Xi, Gaobo; Zhan, Hu</TD>
<TD>Science China Physics, Mechanics &amp;amp; Astronomy, Volume 66, Issue 2, article id.229511</TD>
<TD>2023-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023SCPMA..6629511L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023RAA....23b5012L</TD>
<TD>AT2021acak: a Candidate Tidal Disruption Event Found in the Zwicky Transient Facility Survey</TD>
<TD>Li, Jie; Wang, Zhong-Xiang; Zheng, Dong; Zhang, Ju-Jia; Zhu, Li-Tao; Chen, Zhang-Yi</TD>
<TD>Research in Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 23, Issue 2, id.025012, 9 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023RAA....23b5012L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023PASP..135b4503M</TD>
<TD>The SNAD Viewer: Everything You Want to Know about Your Favorite ZTF Object</TD>
<TD>Malanchev, Konstantin; Kornilov, Matwey V.; Pruzhinskaya, Maria V.; Ishida, Emille E. O.; Aleo, Patrick D.; Korolev, Vladimir S.; Lavrukhina, Anastasia; Russeil, Etienne; Sreejith, Sreevarsha; Volnova, Alina A.; Voloshina, Anastasiya; Krone-Martins, Alberto</TD>
<TD>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 135, Issue 1044, id.024503, 18 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023PASP..135b4503M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023PASJ...75..103S</TD>
<TD>Modeling photometric variations due to a global inhomogeneity on an obliquely rotating star: Application to light curves of white dwarfs</TD>
<TD>Suto, Yasushi; Sasaki, Shin; Aizawa, Masataka; Fujisawa, Kotaro; Kashiyama, Kazumi</TD>
<TD>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Volume 75, Issue 1, pp.103-119</TD>
<TD>2023-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023PASJ...75..103S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023NatAs...7..223L</TD>
<TD>An 18.9 min blue large-amplitude pulsator crossing the `Hertzsprung gap' of hot subdwarfs</TD>
<TD>Lin, Jie; Wu, Chengyuan; Wang, Xiaofeng; Németh, Péter; Xiong, Heran; Wu, Tao; Filippenko, Alexei V.; Cai, Yongzhi; Brink, Thomas G.; Yan, Shengyu; Zeng, Xiangyun; Luo, Yangping; Xiang, Danfeng; Zhang, Jujia; Zheng, WeiKang; Yang, Yi; Mo, Jun; Xi, Gaobo; Zhang, Jicheng; Iskandar, Abdusamatjan; Esamdin, Ali; Jiang, Xiaojun; Sai, Hanna; Wei, Zixuan; Chen, Liyang; Guo, Fangzhou; Chen, Zhihao; Li, Wenxiong; Lin, Weili; Lin, Han; Zhang, Xinghan</TD>
<TD>Nature Astronomy, Volume 7, p. 223-233</TD>
<TD>2023-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023NatAs...7..223L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.519.3154H</TD>
<TD>FIRE-3: updated stellar evolution models, yields, and microphysics and fitting functions for applications in galaxy simulations</TD>
<TD>Hopkins, Philip F.; Wetzel, Andrew; Wheeler, Coral; Sanderson, Robyn; Grudić, Michael Y.; Sameie, Omid; Boylan-Kolchin, Michael; Orr, Matthew; Ma, Xiangcheng; Faucher-Giguère, Claude-André; Kereš, Dušan; Quataert, Eliot; Su, Kung-Yi; Moreno, Jorge; Feldmann, Robert; Bullock, James S.; Loebman, Sarah R.; Anglés-Alcázar, Daniel; Stern, Jonathan; Necib, Lina; Choban, Caleb R.; Hayward, Christopher C.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 519, Issue 2, pp.3154-3181</TD>
<TD>2023-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.519.3154H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.519.2995B</TD>
<TD>Relating peak optical luminosity and orbital period of stellar-mass black holes in X-ray binaries</TD>
<TD>Blackmon, Victoria A.; Maccarone, Thomas J.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 519, Issue 2, pp.2995-2999</TD>
<TD>2023-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.519.2995B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.519.2567S</TD>
<TD>New insights into the helium star formation channel of AM CVn systems with explanations of Gaia14aae and ZTFJ1637+49</TD>
<TD>Sarkar, Arnab; Ge, Hongwei; Tout, Christopher A.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 519, Issue 2, pp.2567-2577</TD>
<TD>2023-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.519.2567S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.519.2035H</TD>
<TD>SCAT uncovers ATLAS's first tidal disruption event ATLAS18mlw: a faint and fast TDE in a quiescent Balmer strong Galaxy</TD>
<TD>Hinkle, Jason T.; Tucker, Michael A.; Shappee, Benjamin J.; Holoien, Thomas W. -S.; Vallely, Patrick J.; de Jaeger, Thomas; Auchettl, Katie; Aldering, Greg; Ashall, Chris; Desai, Dhvanil D.; Do, Aaron; Payne, Anna V.; Tonry, John L.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 519, Issue 2, pp.2035-2045</TD>
<TD>2023-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.519.2035H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.519.1618Y</TD>
<TD>The interaction of supernova 2018evt with a substantial amount of circumstellar matter - An SN 1997cy-like event</TD>
<TD>Yang, Yi; Baade, Dietrich; Hoeflich, Peter; Wang, Lifan; Cikota, Aleksandar; Chen, Ting-Wan; Burke, Jamison; Hiramatsu, Daichi; Pellegrino, Craig; Howell, D. Andrew; McCully, Curtis; Valenti, Stefano; Schulze, Steve; Gal-Yam, Avishay; Wang, Lingzhi; Filippenko, Alexei V.; Maeda, Keiichi; Bulla, Mattia; Yao, Yuhan; Maund, Justyn R.; Patat, Ferdinando; Spyromilio, Jason; Wheeler, J. Craig; Rau, Arne; Hu, Lei; Li, Wenxiong; Andrews, Jennifer E.; Galbany, Llúis; Sand, David J.; Shahbandeh, Melissa; Hsiao, Eric Y.; Wang, Xiaofeng</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 519, Issue 2, pp.1618-1647</TD>
<TD>2023-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.519.1618Y</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.519.1381W</TD>
<TD>Two substellar survivor candidates: one found and one missing</TD>
<TD>Walters, N.; Farihi, J.; Marsh, T. R.; Breedt, E.; Cauley, P. W.; von Hippel, T.; Hermes, J. J.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 519, Issue 1, pp.1381-1395</TD>
<TD>2023-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.519.1381W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.519..891S</TD>
<TD>Mechanisms for high spin in black-hole neutron-star binaries and kilonova emission: inheritance and accretion</TD>
<TD>Steinle, Nathan; Gompertz, Benjamin P.; Nicholl, Matt</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 519, Issue 1, pp.891-901</TD>
<TD>2023-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.519..891S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.519..248A</TD>
<TD>Photometric and spectroscopic analysis of the Type II SN 2020jfo with a short plateau</TD>
<TD>Ailawadhi, B.; Dastidar, R.; Misra, K.; Roy, R.; Hiramatsu, D.; Howell, D. A.; Brink, T. G.; Zheng, W.; Galbany, L.; Shahbandeh, M.; Arcavi, I.; Ashall, C.; Bostroem, K. A.; Burke, J.; Chapman, T.; Dimple; Filippenko, A. V.; Gangopadhyay, A.; Ghosh, A.; Hoffman, A. M.; Hosseinzadeh, G.; Jennings, C.; Jha, V. K.; Kumar, A.; Karamehmetoglu, E.; McCully, C.; McGinness, E.; Müller-Bravo, T. E.; Murakami, Y. S.; Pandey, S. B.; Pellegrino, C.; Piscarreta, L.; Rho, J.; Stritzinger, M.; Sunseri, J.; Van Dyk, S. D.; Yadav, L.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 519, Issue 1, pp.248-270</TD>
<TD>2023-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.519..248A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.519..148D</TD>
<TD>Limiting the accretion disc light in two mass transferring hot subdwarf binaries</TD>
<TD>Deshmukh, Kunal; Kupfer, Thomas; Hakala, Pasi; Bauer, Evan B.; Berdyugin, Andrei; Bildsten, Lars; Marsh, Thomas R.; Mereghetti, Sandro; Piirola, Vilppu</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 519, Issue 1, pp.148-156</TD>
<TD>2023-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.519..148D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.518.5279M</TD>
<TD>Novae in M51: a new, much higher rate from multi-epoch HST data</TD>
<TD>Mandel, Shifra; Shara, Michael M.; Zurek, David; Conroy, Charlie; van Dokkum, Pieter</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 518, Issue 4, pp.5279-5297</TD>
<TD>2023-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.518.5279M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023ExA....55....1E</TD>
<TD>The CUBES science case</TD>
<TD>Evans, Chris; Cristiani, Stefano; Opitom, Cyrielle; Cescutti, Gabriele; D'Odorico, Valentina; Alcalá, Juan Manuel; Alencar, Silvia H. P.; Balashev, Sergei; Barbuy, Beatriz; Bastian, Nate; Battino, Umberto; Cambianica, Pamela; Carini, Roberta; Carter, Brad; Cassisi, Santi; Vaz Castilho, Bruno; Christlieb, Norbert; Cooke, Ryan; Covino, Stefano; Cremonese, Gabriele; Cunha, Katia; da Silva, André R.; D'Elia, Valerio; De Cia, Annalisa; De Silva, Gayandhi; Diaz, Marcos; Di Marcantonio, Paolo; Ernandes, Heitor; Fitzsimmons, Alan; Franchini, Mariagrazia; Gänsicke, Boris T.; Genoni, Matteo; Giribaldi, Riano E.; Grazian, Andrea; Hansen, Camilla Juul; La Forgia, Fiorangela; Lazzarin, Monica; Marcolino, Wagner; Marconi, Marcella; Migliorini, Alessandra; Noterdaeme, Pasquier; Pereira, Claudio; Pilecki, Bogumil; Quirrenbach, Andreas; Randich, Sofia; Rossi, Silvia; Smiljanic, Rodolfo; Snodgrass, Colin; Stürmer, Julian; Trost, Andrea; Vanzella, Eros; Ventura, Paolo; Wright, Duncan; Zafar, Tayyaba</TD>
<TD>Experimental Astronomy, Volume 55, Issue 1, p.1-57</TD>
<TD>2023-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023ExA....55....1E</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023CMAME.405k5813N</TD>
<TD>Adaptive sparse interpolation for accelerating nonlinear stochastic reduced-order modeling with time-dependent bases</TD>
<TD>Naderi, Mohammad Hossein; Babaee, Hessam</TD>
<TD>Computer Methods in Applied Mechanics and Engineering, vol. 405, p. 115813</TD>
<TD>2023-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023CMAME.405k5813N</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023ApJS..264...45F</TD>
<TD>POSYDON: A General-purpose Population Synthesis Code with Detailed Binary-evolution Simulations</TD>
<TD>Fragos, Tassos; Andrews, Jeff J.; Bavera, Simone S.; Berry, Christopher P. L.; Coughlin, Scott; Dotter, Aaron; Giri, Prabin; Kalogera, Vicky; Katsaggelos, Aggelos; Kovlakas, Konstantinos; Lalvani, Shamal; Misra, Devina; Srivastava, Philipp M.; Qin, Ying; Rocha, Kyle A.; Román-Garza, Jaime; Serra, Juan Gabriel; Stahle, Petter; Sun, Meng; Teng, Xu; Trajcevski, Goce; Tran, Nam Hai; Xing, Zepei; Zapartas, Emmanouil; Zevin, Michael</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 264, Issue 2, id.45, 46 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023ApJS..264...45F</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023ApJS..264...39R</TD>
<TD>A Systematic Search for Short-period Close White Dwarf Binary Candidates Based on Gaia EDR3 Catalog and Zwicky Transient Facility Data</TD>
<TD>Ren, Liangliang; Li, Chengyuan; Ma, Bo; Cheng, Sihao; Huang, Shun-Jia; Tang, Baitian; Hu, Yi-ming</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 264, Issue 2, id.39, 35 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023ApJS..264...39R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023ApJS..264...28S</TD>
<TD>The Dark Energy Camera Plane Survey 2 (DECaPS2): More Sky, Less Bias, and Better Uncertainties</TD>
<TD>Saydjari, Andrew K.; Schlafly, Edward F.; Lang, Dustin; Meisner, Aaron M.; Green, Gregory M.; Zucker, Catherine; Zelko, Ioana; Speagle, Joshua S.; Daylan, Tansu; Lee, Albert; Valdes, Francisco; Schlegel, David; Finkbeiner, Douglas P.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 264, Issue 2, id.28, 35 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023ApJS..264...28S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023ApJ...944L..49W</TD>
<TD>SN 2019ewu: A Peculiar Supernova with Early Strong Carbon and Weak Oxygen Features from a New Sample of Young SN Ic Spectra</TD>
<TD>Williamson, Marc; Vogl, Christian; Modjaz, Maryam; Kerzendorf, Wolfgang; Singhal, Jaladh; Boland, Teresa; Burke, Jamison; Chen, Zhihao; Hiramatsu, Daichi; Galbany, Lluís; Gonzalez, Estefania Padilla; Howell, D. Andrew; Jha, Saurabh W.; Kwok, Lindsey A.; McCully, Curtis; Newsome, Megan; Pellegrino, Craig; Rho, Jeonghee; Terreran, Giacomo; Wang, Xiaofeng</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 944, Issue 2, id.L49, 12 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023ApJ...944L..49W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023ApJ...944..204U</TD>
<TD>SN 2020uem: a Possible Thermonuclear Explosion within a Dense Circumstellar Medium (II). The Properties of the CSM from Polarimetry and Light-curve Modeling</TD>
<TD>Uno, Kohki; Nagao, Takashi; Maeda, Keiichi; Kuncarayakti, Hanindyo; Tanaka, Masaomi; Kawabata, Koji S.; Nakaoka, Tatsuya; Kawabata, Miho; Yamanaka, Masayuki; Aoki, Kentaro; Isogai, Keisuke; Ogawa, Mao; Tajitsu, Akito; Imazawa, Ryo</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 944, Issue 2, id.204, 13 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023ApJ...944..204U</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023ApJ...944..203U</TD>
<TD>SN 2020uem: a Possible Thermonuclear Explosion within a Dense Circumstellar Medium. I. The Nature of Type IIn/Ia-CSM SNe from Photometry and Spectroscopy</TD>
<TD>Uno, Kohki; Maeda, Keiichi; Nagao, Takashi; Nakaoka, Tatsuya; Motohara, Kentaro; Tajitsu, Akito; Konishi, Masahiro; Koyama, Shuhei; Takahashi, Hidenori; Tanaka, Masaomi; Kuncarayakti, Hanindyo; Kawabata, Miho; Yamanaka, Masayuki; Aoki, Kentaro; Isogai, Keisuke; Taguchi, Kenta; Ogawa, Mao; Kawabata, Koji S.; Yoshii, Yuzuru; Miyata, Takashi; Imazawa, Ryo</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 944, Issue 2, id.203, 17 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023ApJ...944..203U</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023ApJ...944...80A</TD>
<TD>IceCube Search for Neutrinos Coincident with Gravitational Wave Events from LIGO/Virgo Run O3</TD>
<TD>Abbasi, R.; Ackermann, M.; Adams, J.; Aggarwal, N.; Aguilar, J. A.; Ahlers, M.; Ahrens, M.; Alameddine, J. M.; Alves, A. A.; Amin, N. M.; Andeen, K.; Anderson, T.; Anton, G.; Argüelles, C.; Asali, Y.; Ashida, Y.; Athanasiadou, S.; Axani, S.; Bai, X.; Balagopal V., A.; Baricevic, M.; Bartos, I.; Barwick, S. W.; Basu, V.; Bay, R.; Beatty, J. J.; Becker, K. -H.; Becker Tjus, J.; Beise, J.; Bellenghi, C.; Benda, S.; BenZvi, S.; Berley, D.; Bernardini, E.; Besson, D. Z.; Binder, G.; Bindig, D.; Blaufuss, E.; Blot, S.; Bontempo, F.; Book, J. Y.; Borowka, J.; Böser, S.; Botner, O.; Böttcher, J.; Bourbeau, E.; Bradascio, F.; Braun, J.; Brinson, B.; Bron, S.; Brostean-Kaiser, J.; Burley, R. T.; Busse, R. S.; Campana, M. A.; Carnie-Bronca, E. G.; Chen, C.; Chen, Z.; Chirkin, D.; Choi, K.; Clark, B. A.; Classen, L.; Coleman, A.; Collin, G. H.; Connolly, A.; Conrad, J. M.; Coppin, P.; Correa, P.; Countryman, S. T.; Cowen, D. F.; Cross, R.; Dappen, C.; Dave, P.; De Clercq, C.; DeLaunay, J. J.; Delgado López, D.; Dembinski, H.; Deoskar, K.; Desai, A.; Desiati, P.; de Vries, K. D.; de Wasseige, G.; DeYoung, T.; Diaz, A.; Díaz-Vélez, J. C.; Dittmer, M.; Dujmovic, H.; DuVernois, M. A.; Ehrhardt, T.; Eller, P.; Engel, R.; Erpenbeck, H.; Evans, J.; Evenson, P. A.; Fan, K. L.; Fazely, A. R.; Fedynitch, A.; Feigl, N.; Fiedlschuster, S.; Fienberg, A. T.; Finley, C.; Fischer, L.; Fox, D.; Franckowiak, A.; Friedman, E.; Fritz, A.; Fürst, P.; Gaisser, T. K.; Gallagher, J.; Ganster, E.; Garcia, A.; Garrappa, S.; Gerhardt, L.; Ghadimi, A.; Glaser, C.; Glauch, T.; Glüsenkamp, T.; Goehlke, N.; Gonzalez, J. G.; Goswami, S.; Grant, D.; Grégoire, T.; Griswold, S.; Günther, C.; Gutjahr, P.; Haack, C.; Hallgren, A.; Halliday, R.; Halve, L.; Halzen, F.; Hamdaoui, H.; Ha Minh, M.; Hanson, K.; Hardin, J.; Harnisch, A. A.; Hatch, P.; Haungs, A.; Helbing, K.; Hellrung, J.; Henningsen, F.; Heuermann, L.; Hickford, S.; Hill, C.; Hill, G. C.; Hoffman, K. D.; Hoshina, K.; Hou, W.; Huber, T.; Hultqvist, K.; Hünnefeld, M.; Hussain, R.; Hymon, K.; In, S.; Iovine, N.; Ishihara, A.; Jansson, M.; Japaridze, G. S.; Jeong, M.; Jin, M.; Jones, B. J. P.; Kang, D.; Kang, W.; Kang, X.; Kappes, A.; Kappesser, D.; Kardum, L.; Karg, T.; Karl, M.; Karle, A.; Katz, U.; Kauer, M.; Kelley, J. L.; Kheirandish, A.; Kin, K.; Kiryluk, J.; Klein, S. R.; Kochocki, A.; Koirala, R.; Kolanoski, H.; Kontrimas, T.; Köpke, L.; Kopper, C.; Koskinen, D. J.; Koundal, P.; Kovacevich, M.; Kowalski, M.; Kozynets, T.; Krupczak, E.; Kun, E.; Kurahashi, N.; Lad, N.; Lagunas Gualda, C.; Larson, M. J.; Lauber, F.; Lazar, J. P.; Lee, J. W.; Leonard, K.; Leszczyńska, A.; Lincetto, M.; Liu, Q. R.; Liubarska, M.; Lohfink, E.; Love, C.; Mariscal, C. J. Lozano; Lu, L.; Lucarelli, F.; Ludwig, A.; Luszczak, W.; Lyu, Y.; Ma, W. Y.; Madsen, J.; Mahn, K. B. M.; Makino, Y.; Mancina, S.; Sainte, W. Marie; Mariş, I. C.; Márka, S.; Márka, Z.; Marsee, M.; Martinez-Soler, I.; Maruyama, R.; McElroy, T.; McNally, F.; Mead, J. V.; Meagher, K.; Mechbal, S.; Medina, A.; Meier, M.; Meighen-Berger, S.; Merckx, Y.; Micallef, J.; Mockler, D.; Montaruli, T.; Moore, R. W.; Morse, R.; Moulai, M.; Mukherjee, T.; Naab, R.; Nagai, R.; Naumann, U.; Necker, J.; Neumann, M.; Niederhausen, H.; Nisa, M. U.; Nowicki, S. C.; Obertacke Pollmann, A.; Oehler, M.; Oeyen, B.; Olivas, A.; Orsoe, R.; Osborn, J.; O'Sullivan, E.; Pandya, H.; Pankova, D. V.; Park, N.; Parker, G. K.; Paudel, E. N.; Paul, L.; Pérez de los Heros, C.; Peters, L.; Peterson, J.; Philippen, S.; Pieper, S.; Pizzuto, A.; Plum, M.; Popovych, Y.; Porcelli, A.; Prado Rodriguez, M.; Pries, B.; Przybylski, G. T.; Raab, C.; Rack-Helleis, J.; Rameez, M.; Rawlins, K.; Rechav, Z.; Rehman, A.; Reichherzer, P.; Renzi, G.; Resconi, E.; Reusch, S.; Rhode, W.; Richman, M.; Riedel, B.; Roberts, E. J.; Robertson, S.; Rodan, S.; Roellinghoff, G.; Rongen, M.; Rott, C.; Ruhe, T.; Ruohan, L.; Ryckbosch, D.; Rysewyk Cantu, D.; Safa, I.; Saffer, J.; Salazar-Gallegos, D.; Sampathkumar, P.; Sanchez Herrera, S. E.; Sandrock, A.; Santander, M.; Sarkar, S.; Sarkar, S.; Satalecka, K.; Schaufel, M.; Schieler, H.; Schindler, S.; Schlueter, B.; Schmidt, T.; Schneider, J.; Schröder, F. G.; Schumacher, L.; Schwefer, G.; Sclafani, S.; Seckel, D.; Seunarine, S.; Sharma, A.; Shefali, S.; Shimizu, N.; Silva, M.; Silva Oliveira, A. C.; Skrzypek, B.; Smithers, B.; Snihur, R.; Soedingrekso, J.; Sogaard, A.; Soldin, D.; Spannfellner, C.; Spiczak, G. M.; Spiering, C.; Stamatikos, M.; Stanev, T.; Stein, R.; Stezelberger, T.; Stürwald, T.; Stuttard, T.; Sullivan, A. G.; Sullivan, G. W.; Taboada, I.; Ter-Antonyan, S.; Thompson, W. G.; Thwaites, J.; Tilav, S.; Tollefson, K.; Tönnis, C.; Toscano, S.; Tosi, D.; Trettin, A.; Tung, C. F.; Turcotte, R.; Twagirayezu, J. P.; Ty, B.; Unland Elorrieta, M. A.; Upshaw, K.; Valtonen-Mattila, N.; Vandenbroucke, J.; van Eijndhoven, N.; Vannerom, D.; van Santen, J.; Vara, J.; Veitch-Michaelis, J.; Verpoest, S.; Veske, D.; Walck, C.; Wang, W.; Watson, T. B.; Weaver, C.; Weigel, P.; Weindl, A.; Weldert, J.; Wendt, C.; Werthebach, J.; Weyrauch, M.; Whitehorn, N.; Wiebusch, C. H.; Willey, N.; Williams, D. R.; Wolf, M.; Wrede, G.; Wulff, J.; Xu, X. W.; Yanez, J. P.; Yildizci, E.; Yoshida, S.; Yu, S.; Yuan, T.; Zhang, Z.; Zhelnin, P.; IceCube Collaboration</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 944, Issue 1, id.80, 19 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023ApJ...944...80A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023ApJ...944...25T</TD>
<TD>Evolving Morphology of Resolved Stellar Einstein Rings</TD>
<TD>Turyshev, Slava G.; Toth, Viktor T.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 944, Issue 1, id.25, 21 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023ApJ...944...25T</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023ApJ...943L..20S</TD>
<TD>The Luminous Type Ia Supernova 2022ilv and Its Early Excess Emission</TD>
<TD>Srivastav, Shubham; Smartt, S. J.; Huber, M. E.; Dimitriadis, G.; Chambers, K. C.; Fulton, Michael D.; Moore, Thomas; Callan, F. P.; Gillanders, James H.; Maguire, K.; Nicholl, M.; Shingles, Luke J.; Sim, S. A.; Smith, K. W.; Anderson, J. P.; de Boer, Thomas; Chen, Ting-Wan; Gao, Hua; Young, D. R.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 943, Issue 2, id.L20, 9 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023ApJ...943L..20S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023ApJ...943L..18C</TD>
<TD>Linear and Circular Polarimetry of the Optically Bright Relativistic Tidal Disruption Event AT 2022cmc</TD>
<TD>Cikota, Aleksandar; Leloudas, Giorgos; Bulla, Mattia; Dai, Lixin; Maund, Justyn; Andreoni, Igor</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 943, Issue 2, id.L18, 8 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023ApJ...943L..18C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023ApJ...943..103A</TD>
<TD>Multiwavelength Observations of a New Redback Millisecond Pulsar 4FGL J1910.7-5320</TD>
<TD>Au, Ka-Yui; Strader, Jay; Swihart, Samuel J.; Lin, Lupin C. C.; Kong, Albert K. H.; Takata, Jumpei; Hui, Chung-Yue; Panurach, Teresa; Molina, Isabella; Aydi, Elias; Sokolovsky, Kirill; Li, Kwan-Lok</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 943, Issue 2, id.103, 8 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023ApJ...943..103A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023Ap&amp;SS.368....8C</TD>
<TD>Accretion disks, quasars and cosmology: meandering towards understanding</TD>
<TD>Czerny, BoŻena; Cao, Shulei; Jaiswal, Vikram Kumar; Karas, Vladimír; Khadka, Narayan; Martínez-Aldama, Mary Loli; Naddaf, Mohammad Hassan; Panda, Swayamtrupta; Pozo Nuñez, Francisco; Prince, Raj; Ratra, Bharat; Sniegowska, Marzena; Yu, Zhefu; Zajaček, Michal</TD>
<TD>Astrophysics and Space Science, Volume 368, Issue 2, article id.8</TD>
<TD>2023-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023Ap&amp;SS.368....8C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023AJ....165...71H</TD>
<TD>TESS-Gaia Light Curve: A PSF-based TESS FFI Light-curve Product</TD>
<TD>Han, Te; Brandt, Timothy D.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 165, Issue 2, id.71, 18 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023AJ....165...71H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023AJ....165...63F</TD>
<TD>The Colorado Ultraviolet Transit Experiment Mission Overview</TD>
<TD>France, Kevin; Fleming, Brian; Egan, Arika; Desert, Jean-Michel; Fossati, Luca; Koskinen, Tommi T.; Nell, Nicholas; Petit, Pascal; Vidotto, Aline A.; Beasley, Matthew; DeCicco, Nicholas; Sreejith, Aickara Gopinathan; Suresh, Ambily; Baumert, Jared; Cauley, P. Wilson; D'Angelo, Carolina Villarreal; Hoadley, Keri; Kane, Robert; Kohnert, Richard; Lambert, Julian; Ulrich, Stefan</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 165, Issue 2, id.63, 9 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023AJ....165...63F</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023AJ....165...44G</TD>
<TD>TESS Giants Transiting Giants. III. An Eccentric Warm Jupiter Supports a Period-Eccentricity Relation for Giant Planets Transiting Evolved Stars</TD>
<TD>Grunblatt, Samuel K.; Saunders, Nicholas; Chontos, Ashley; Hattori, Soichiro; Veras, Dimitri; Huber, Daniel; Angus, Ruth; Rice, Malena; Breivik, Katelyn; Blunt, Sarah; Giacalone, Steven; Lubin, Jack; Isaacson, Howard; Howard, Andrew W.; Ciardi, David R.; Safonov, Boris S.; Strakhov, Ivan A.; Latham, David W.; Bieryla, Allyson; Ricker, George R.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Tenenbaum, Peter; Shporer, Avi; Morgan, Edward H.; Kostov, Veselin; Osborn, Hugh P.; Dragomir, Diana; Seager, Sara; Vanderspek, Roland K.; Winn, Joshua N.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 165, Issue 2, id.44, 15 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023AJ....165...44G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023AJ....165...43L</TD>
<TD>Kepler K2 and TESS Observations of Two Magnetic Cataclysmic Variables: The New Asynchronous Polar SDSS J084617.11+245344.1 and Paloma</TD>
<TD>Littlefield, Colin; Hoard, D. W.; Garnavich, Peter; Szkody, Paula; Mason, Paul A.; Scaringi, Simone; Ilkiewicz, Krystian; Kennedy, Mark R.; Rappaport, Saul A.; Jayaraman, Rahul</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 165, Issue 2, id.43, 14 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023AJ....165...43L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023AJ....165...30X</TD>
<TD>The Eclipsing Binaries from the LAMOST Medium-resolution Survey. III. A High-precision Empirical Stellar Mass Library</TD>
<TD>Xiong, Jianping; Liu, Chao; Li, Jiao; Li, Jiadong; Zhang, Bo; Chen, Xiaodian; Luo, Changqing; Cao, Zihuang; Zhao, Yongheng</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 165, Issue 2, id.30, 15 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023AJ....165...30X</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023A&amp;A...670A.130M</TD>
<TD>Multi-epoch variability of AT 2000ch (SN 2000ch) in NGC 3432. A radio continuum and optical study</TD>
<TD>Müller, Ancla; Frohn, Vanessa; Dirks, Lukas; Stein, Michael; Adebahr, Björn; Bomans, Dominik J.; Weis, Kerstin; Dettmar, Ralf-Jürgen</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 670, id.A130, 20 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023A&amp;A...670A.130M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023A&amp;A...670A.119B</TD>
<TD>StarDICE. I. Sensor calibration bench and absolute photometric calibration of a Sony IMX411 sensor</TD>
<TD>Betoule, Marc; Antier, Sarah; Bertin, Emmanuel; Blanc, Pierre Éric; Bongard, Sébastien; Cohen Tanugi, Johann; Dagoret-Campagne, Sylvie; Feinstein, Fabrice; Hardin, Delphine; Juramy, Claire; Le Guillou, Laurent; Le Van Suu, Auguste; Moniez, Marc; Neveu, Jérémy; Nuss, Éric; Plez, Bertrand; Regnault, Nicolas; Sepulveda, Eduardo; Sommer, Kélian; Souverin, Thierry; Wang, Xiao Feng</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 670, id.A119, 18 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023A&amp;A...670A.119B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023A&amp;A...670A..48C</TD>
<TD>Cosmic rate of type IIn supernovae and its evolution with redshift</TD>
<TD>Cold, C.; Hjorth, J.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 670, id.A48, 7 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023A&amp;A...670A..48C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023A&amp;A...670A...7W</TD>
<TD>SN 2020qlb: A hydrogen-poor superluminous supernova with well-characterized light curve undulations</TD>
<TD>West, S. L.; Lunnan, R.; Omand, C. M. B.; Kangas, T.; Schulze, S.; Strotjohann, N. L.; Yang, S.; Fransson, C.; Sollerman, J.; Perley, D.; Yan, L.; Chen, T. -W.; Chen, Z. H.; Taggart, K.; Fremling, C.; Bloom, J. S.; Drake, A.; Graham, M. J.; Kasliwal, M. M.; Laher, R.; Medford, M. S.; Neill, J. D.; Riddle, R.; Shupe, D.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 670, id.A7, 21 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023A&amp;A...670A...7W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023Univ....9...52S</TD>
<TD>Polarimetric Reverberation Mapping in Medium-Band Filters</TD>
<TD>Shablovinskaya, Elena; Popović, Luka Č.; Uklein, Roman; Malygin, Eugene; Ilić, Dragana; Ciroi, Stefano; Oparin, Dmitry; Crepaldi, Luca; Slavcheva-Mihova, Lyuba; Mihov, Boyko; Nikolov, Yanko</TD>
<TD>Universe, vol. 9, issue 1, p. 52</TD>
<TD>2023-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023Univ....9...52S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023RAA....23a5003W</TD>
<TD>1SWASP J010313.78+352903.7: A Totally Eclipsing Binary with Components in Poor Thermal Contact</TD>
<TD>Wang, Zhihua; Zhu, Liying; Yuan, Kai</TD>
<TD>Research in Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 23, Issue 1, id.015003, 8 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023RAA....23a5003W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023PSJ.....4...18M</TD>
<TD>Shape Models of Lucy Targets (3548) Eurybates and (21900) Orus from Disk-integrated Photometry</TD>
<TD>Mottola, Stefano; Hellmich, Stephan; Buie, Marc W.; Zangari, Amanda M.; Stephens, Robert D.; Di Martino, Mario; Proffe, Gerrit; Marchi, Simone; Olkin, Catherine B.; Levison, Harold F.</TD>
<TD>The Planetary Science Journal, Volume 4, Issue 1, id.18, 20 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023PSJ.....4...18M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023NewA...9801943P</TD>
<TD>DeGaPe 35: Amateur discovery of a new southern symbiotic star</TD>
<TD>Petit, Thomas; Merc, Jaroslav; Gális, Rudolf; Charbonnel, Stéphane; Demange, Thierry; Galli, Richard; Garde, Olivier; Le Dû, Pascal; Mulato, Lionel</TD>
<TD>New Astronomy, Volume 98, article id. 101943.</TD>
<TD>2023-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023NewA...9801943P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023NewA...9801924Z</TD>
<TD>X-ray and optical observations of two AM Her type cataclysmic variables: V388 Peg and V1189 Her</TD>
<TD>Zengi̇n Çamurdan, Dicle</TD>
<TD>New Astronomy, Volume 98, article id. 101924.</TD>
<TD>2023-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023NewA...9801924Z</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023NewA...9801914X</TD>
<TD>The first photometric and spectroscopic analysis of the neglected totally eclipsing contact binary NSVS 2536063</TD>
<TD>Xia, Qi-Qi; Li, Kai; Gao, Xing; Sun, Guo-You; Wang, Xi; Yin, Shi-Peng; Liu, Fei</TD>
<TD>New Astronomy, Volume 98, article id. 101914.</TD>
<TD>2023-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023NewA...9801914X</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023NatAs...7...88P</TD>
<TD>The Birth of a Relativistic Jet Following the Disruption of a Star by a Cosmological Black Hole</TD>
<TD>Pasham, Dheeraj R.; Lucchini, Matteo; Laskar, Tanmoy; Gompertz, Benjamin P.; Srivastav, Shubham; Nicholl, Matt; Smartt, Stephen J.; Miller-Jones, James C. A.; Alexander, Kate D.; Fender, Rob; Smith, Graham P.; Fulton, M.; Dewangan, Gulab; Gendreau, Keith; Coughlin, Eric R.; Rhodes, Lauren; Horesh, Assaf; van Velzen, Sjoert; Sfaradi, Itai; Guolo, Muryel; Castro Segura, Noel; Aamer, Aysha; Anderson, Joseph P.; Arcavi, Iair; Brennan, Seán J.; Chambers, Kenneth; Charalampopoulos, Panos; Chen, Ting-Wan; Clocchiatti, A.; de Boer, Thomas; Dennefeld, Michel; Ferrara, Elizabeth; Galbany, Lluís; Gao, Hua; Gillanders, James H.; Goodwin, Adelle; Gromadzki, Mariusz; Huber, M.; Jonker, Peter G.; Joshi, Manasvita; Kara, Erin; Killestein, Thomas L.; Kosec, Peter; Kocevski, Daniel; Leloudas, Giorgos; Lin, Chien-Cheng; Margutti, Raffaella; Mattila, Seppo; Moore, Thomas; Müller-Bravo, Tomás; Ngeow, Chow-Choong; Oates, Samantha; Onori, Francesca; Pan, Yen-Chen; Perez-Torres, Miguel; Rani, Priyanka; Remillard, Ronald; Ridley, Evan J.; Schulze, Steve; Sheng, Xinyue; Shingles, Luke; Smith, Ken W.; Steiner, James F.; Wainscoat, Richard; Wevers, Thomas; Yang, Sheng</TD>
<TD>Nature Astronomy, Volume 7, p. 88-104</TD>
<TD>2023-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023NatAs...7...88P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.518L..31M</TD>
<TD>A search for planetary transits on a set of 1.4 million multisector DIAmante light curves</TD>
<TD>Montalto, M.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 518, Issue 1, pp.L31-L35</TD>
<TD>2023-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.518L..31M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.518.4172D</TD>
<TD>Optical follow-up of the tick-tock massive black hole binary candidate</TD>
<TD>Dotti, Massimo; Bonetti, Matteo; Rigamonti, Fabio; Bortolas, Elisa; Fossati, Matteo; Decarli, Roberto; Covino, Stefano; Lupi, Alessandro; Franchini, Alessia; Sesana, Alberto; Calderone, Giorgio</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 518, Issue 3, pp.4172-4179</TD>
<TD>2023-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.518.4172D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.518.3966S</TD>
<TD>White dwarf binaries suggest a common envelope efficiency α   1/3</TD>
<TD>Scherbak, Peter; Fuller, Jim</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 518, Issue 3, pp.3966-3984</TD>
<TD>2023-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.518.3966S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.518.3397W</TD>
<TD>Final stage of merging binaries of supermassive black holes: observational signatures</TD>
<TD>Wang, Jian-Min; Songsheng, Yu-Yang; Li, Yan-Rong; Du, Pu</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 518, Issue 3, pp.3397-3406</TD>
<TD>2023-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.518.3397W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.518.3123C</TD>
<TD>Photometric identification of compact galaxies, stars, and quasars using multiple neural networks</TD>
<TD>Chaini, Siddharth; Bagul, Atharva; Deshpande, Anish; Gondkar, Rishi; Sharma, Kaushal; Vivek, M.; Kembhavi, Ajit</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 518, Issue 2, pp.3123-3136</TD>
<TD>2023-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.518.3123C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.518.2938T</TD>
<TD>BASS XXXIX: Swift-BAT AGN with changing-look optical spectra</TD>
<TD>Temple, Matthew J.; Ricci, Claudio; Koss, Michael J.; Trakhtenbrot, Benny; Bauer, Franz E.; Mushotzky, Richard; Rojas, Alejandra F.; Caglar, Turgay; Harrison, Fiona; Oh, Kyuseok; Padilla Gonzalez, Estefania; Powell, Meredith C.; Ricci, Federica; Riffel, Rogério; Stern, Daniel; Urry, C. Megan</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 518, Issue 2, pp.2938-2953</TD>
<TD>2023-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.518.2938T</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.518.2341K</TD>
<TD>The merger fraction of ultramassive white dwarfs</TD>
<TD>Kilic, Mukremin; Moss, Adam G.; Kosakowski, Alekzander; Bergeron, P.; Conly, Annamarie A.; Brown, Warren R.; Toonen, Silvia; Williams, Kurtis A.; Dufour, P.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 518, Issue 2, pp.2341-2353</TD>
<TD>2023-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.518.2341K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.518.2320D</TD>
<TD>Multiple gas phases in supernova remnant IC 443: mapping shocked H&lt;SUB&gt;2&lt;/SUB&gt; with VLT/KMOS</TD>
<TD>Deng, Yunwei; Zhang, Zhi-Yu; Zhou, Ping; Wang, Junzhi; Fang, Min; Lin, Lingrui; Bian, Fuyan; Chen, Zhiwei; Shi, Yong; Chen, Guoyin; Li, Hui</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 518, Issue 2, pp.2320-2340</TD>
<TD>2023-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.518.2320D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.518.1880B</TD>
<TD>Dwarf AGNs from variability for the origins of seeds (DAVOS): Intermediate-mass black hole demographics from optical synoptic surveys</TD>
<TD>Burke, Colin J.; Shen, Yue; Liu, Xin; Natarajan, Priyamvada; Caplar, Neven; Bellovary, Jillian M.; Wang, Z. Franklin</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 518, Issue 2, pp.1880-1904</TD>
<TD>2023-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.518.1880B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.518.1531L</TD>
<TD>The Type 1 and Type 2 AGN dichotomy according to their ZTF optical variability</TD>
<TD>López-Navas, E.; Arévalo, P.; Bernal, S.; Graham, Matthew J.; Hernández-García, L.; Lira, P.; Sánchez-Sáez, P.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 518, Issue 1, pp.1531-1542</TD>
<TD>2023-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.518.1531L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.518.1057E</TD>
<TD>A Sun-like star orbiting a black hole</TD>
<TD>El-Badry, Kareem; Rix, Hans-Walter; Quataert, Eliot; Howard, Andrew W.; Isaacson, Howard; Fuller, Jim; Hawkins, Keith; Breivik, Katelyn; Wong, Kaze W. K.; Rodriguez, Antonio C.; Conroy, Charlie; Shahaf, Sahar; Mazeh, Tsevi; Arenou, Frédéric; Burdge, Kevin B.; Bashi, Dolev; Faigler, Simchon; Weisz, Daniel R.; Seeburger, Rhys; Almada Monter, Silvia; Wojno, Jennifer</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 518, Issue 1, pp.1057-1085</TD>
<TD>2023-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.518.1057E</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023MNRAS.518..847G</TD>
<TD>Radio observations of the tidal disruption event AT2020opy: a luminous non-relativistic outflow encountering a dense circumnuclear medium</TD>
<TD>Goodwin, A. J.; Miller-Jones, J. C. A.; van Velzen, S.; Bietenholz, M.; Greenland, J.; Cenko, B.; Gezari, S.; Horesh, A.; Sivakoff, G. R.; Yan, L.; Yu, W.; Zhang, X.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 518, Issue 1, pp.847-854</TD>
<TD>2023-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023MNRAS.518..847G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023Galax..11...22R</TD>
<TD>Astro-COLIBRI 2—An Advanced Platform for Real-Time Multi-Messenger Discoveries</TD>
<TD>Reichherzer, Patrick; Schüssler, Fabian; Lefranc, Valentin; Becker Tjus, Julia; Mourier, Jayson; Alkan, Atilla Kaan</TD>
<TD>Galaxies, vol. 11, issue 1, p. 22</TD>
<TD>2023-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023Galax..11...22R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023ApJS..264...20I</TD>
<TD>A Three-dimensional Map of the Milky Way Using 66,000 Mira Variable Stars</TD>
<TD>Iwanek, Patryk; Poleski, Radosław; Kozłowski, Szymon; Soszyński, Igor; Pietrukowicz, Paweł; Ban, Makiko; Skowron, Jan; Mróz, Przemysław; Wrona, Marcin; Udalski, Andrzej; Szymański, Michał K.; Skowron, Dorota M.; Ulaczyk, Krzysztof; Gromadzki, Mariusz; Rybicki, Krzysztof; Ratajczak, Milena</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 264, Issue 1, id.20, 18 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023ApJS..264...20I</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023ApJS..264...18K</TD>
<TD>Light Curves of Trans-Neptunian Objects from the K2 Mission of the Kepler Space Telescope</TD>
<TD>Kecskeméthy, Viktória; Kiss, Csaba; Szakáts, Róbert; Pál, András; Szabó, Gyula M.; Molnár, László; Sárneczky, Krisztián; Vinkó, József; Szabó, Róbert; Marton, Gábor; Farkas-Takács, Anikó; Kalup, Csilla E.; Kiss, László L.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 264, Issue 1, id.18, 20 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023ApJS..264...18K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023ApJ...943...42C</TD>
<TD>The Hydrogen-poor Superluminous Supernovae from the Zwicky Transient Facility Phase I Survey. II. Light-curve Modeling and Characterization of Undulations</TD>
<TD>Chen, Z. H.; Yan, Lin; Kangas, T.; Lunnan, R.; Sollerman, J.; Schulze, S.; Perley, D. A.; Chen, T. -W.; Taggart, K.; Hinds, K. R.; Gal-Yam, A.; Wang, X. F.; De, K.; Bellm, E.; Bloom, J. S.; Dekany, R.; Graham, M.; Kasliwal, M.; Kulkarni, S.; Laher, R.; Neill, D.; Rusholme, B.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 943, Issue 1, id.42, 23 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023ApJ...943...42C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023ApJ...943...41C</TD>
<TD>The Hydrogen-poor Superluminous Supernovae from the Zwicky Transient Facility Phase I Survey. I. Light Curves and Measurements</TD>
<TD>Chen, Z. H.; Yan, Lin; Kangas, T.; Lunnan, R.; Schulze, S.; Sollerman, J.; Perley, D. A.; Chen, T. -W.; Taggart, K.; Hinds, K. R.; Gal-Yam, A.; Wang, X. F.; Andreoni, I.; Bellm, E.; Bloom, J. S.; Burdge, K.; Burgos, A.; Cook, D.; Dahiwale, A.; De, K.; Dekany, R.; Dugas, A.; Frederik, S.; Fremling, C.; Graham, M.; Hankins, M.; Ho, A.; Jencson, J.; Karambelkar, V.; Kasliwal, M.; Kulkarni, S.; Laher, R.; Rusholme, B.; Sharma, Y.; Taddia, F.; Tartaglia, L.; Thomas, B. P.; Tzanidakis, A.; Van Roestel, J.; Walter, R.; Yang, Y.; Yao, Y. H.; Yaron, O.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 943, Issue 1, id.41, 30 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023ApJ...943...41C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023ApJ...943...36L</TD>
<TD>Spectroastrometric Reverberation Mapping of Broad-line Regions</TD>
<TD>Li, Yan-Rong; Wang, Jian-Min</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 943, Issue 1, id.36, 21 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023ApJ...943...36L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023ApJ...943...19M</TD>
<TD>DeepZipper. II. Searching for Lensed Supernovae in Dark Energy Survey Data with Deep Learning</TD>
<TD>Morgan, R.; Nord, B.; Bechtol, K.; Möller, A.; Hartley, W. G.; Birrer, S.; González, S. J.; Martinez, M.; Gruendl, R. A.; Buckley-Geer, E. J.; Shajib, A. J.; Carnero Rosell, A.; Lidman, C.; Collett, T.; Abbott, T. M. C.; Aguena, M.; Andrade-Oliveira, F.; Annis, J.; Bacon, D.; Bocquet, S.; Brooks, D.; Burke, D. L.; Carrasco Kind, M.; Carretero, J.; Castander, F. J.; Conselice, C.; da Costa, L. N.; Costanzi, M.; De Vicente, J.; Desai, S.; Doel, P.; Everett, S.; Ferrero, I.; Flaugher, B.; Friedel, D.; Frieman, J.; García-Bellido, J.; Gaztanaga, E.; Gruen, D.; Gutierrez, G.; Hinton, S. R.; Hollowood, D. L.; Honscheid, K.; Kuehn, K.; Kuropatkin, N.; Lahav, O.; Lima, M.; Menanteau, F.; Miquel, R.; Palmese, A.; Paz-Chinchón, F.; Pereira, M. E. S.; Pieres, A.; Plazas Malagón, A. A.; Prat, J.; Rodriguez-Monroy, M.; Romer, A. K.; Roodman, A.; Sanchez, E.; Scarpine, V.; Sevilla-Noarbe, I.; Smith, M.; Suchyta, E.; Swanson, M. E. C.; Tarle, G.; Thomas, D.; Varga, T. N.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 943, Issue 1, id.19, 14 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023ApJ...943...19M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023ApJ...942...99G</TD>
<TD>A Light in the Dark: Searching for Electromagnetic Counterparts to Black Hole-Black Hole Mergers in LIGO/Virgo O3 with the Zwicky Transient Facility</TD>
<TD>Graham, Matthew J.; McKernan, Barry; Ford, K. E. Saavik; Stern, Daniel; Djorgovski, S. G.; Coughlin, Michael; Burdge, Kevin B.; Bellm, Eric C.; Helou, George; Mahabal, Ashish A.; Masci, Frank J.; Purdum, Josiah; Rosnet, Philippe; Rusholme, Ben</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 942, Issue 2, id.99, 19 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023ApJ...942...99G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023ApJ...942...88Z</TD>
<TD>Kilonovae and Optical Afterglows from Binary Neutron Star Mergers. II. Optimal Search Strategy for Serendipitous Observations and Target-of-opportunity Observations of Gravitational Wave Triggers</TD>
<TD>Zhu, Jin-Ping; Wu, Shichao; Yang, Yuan-Pei; Liu, Chang; Zhang, Bing; Song, Hao-Ran; Gao, He; Cao, Zhoujian; Yu, Yun-Wei; Kang, Yacheng; Shao, Lijing</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 942, Issue 2, id.88, 18 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023ApJ...942...88Z</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023ApJ...942...17M</TD>
<TD>A Multiwavelength View of the Rapidly Evolving SN 2018ivc: An Analog of SN IIb 1993J but Powered Primarily by Circumstellar Interaction</TD>
<TD>Maeda, Keiichi; Chandra, Poonam; Moriya, Takashi J.; Reguitti, Andrea; Ryder, Stuart; Matsuoka, Tomoki; Michiyama, Tomonari; Pignata, Giuliano; Hiramatsu, Daichi; Bostroem, K. Azalee; Kundu, Esha; Kuncarayakti, Hanindyo; Bersten, Melina C.; Pooley, David; Lee, Shiu-Hang; Patnaude, Daniel; Rodríguez, Ósmar; Folatelli, Gaston</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 942, Issue 1, id.17, 18 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023ApJ...942...17M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023ApJ...942....9H</TD>
<TD>The Final Season Reimagined: 30 Tidal Disruption Events from the ZTF-I Survey</TD>
<TD>Hammerstein, Erica; van Velzen, Sjoert; Gezari, Suvi; Cenko, S. Bradley; Yao, Yuhan; Ward, Charlotte; Frederick, Sara; Villanueva, Natalia; Somalwar, Jean J.; Graham, Matthew J.; Kulkarni, Shrinivas R.; Stern, Daniel; Andreoni, Igor; Bellm, Eric C.; Dekany, Richard; Dhawan, Suhail; Drake, Andrew J.; Fremling, Christoffer; Gatkine, Pradip; Groom, Steven L.; Ho, Anna Y. Q.; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Karambelkar, Viraj; Kool, Erik C.; Masci, Frank J.; Medford, Michael S.; Perley, Daniel A.; Purdum, Josiah; van Roestel, Jan; Sharma, Yashvi; Sollerman, Jesper; Taggart, Kirsty; Yan, Lin</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 942, Issue 1, id.9, 35 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023ApJ...942....9H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023AdSpR..71.1045N</TD>
<TD>Accretion flow properties of MAXI J1910-057/Swift J1910.2-0546 during its 2012-13 outburst</TD>
<TD>Nath, Sujoy Kumar; Debnath, Dipak; Chatterjee, Kaushik; Jana, Arghajit; Chatterjee, Debjit; Bhowmick, Riya</TD>
<TD>Advances in Space Research, Volume 71, Issue 1, p. 1045-1058.</TD>
<TD>2023-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023AdSpR..71.1045N</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023AJ....165...18P</TD>
<TD>Deep Attention-based Supernovae Classification of Multiband Light Curves</TD>
<TD>Pimentel, Óscar; Estévez, Pablo A.; Förster, Francisco</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 165, Issue 1, id.18, 32 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023AJ....165...18P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023A&amp;A...669A.140P</TD>
<TD>The rise and fall of the iron-strong nuclear transient PS16dtm</TD>
<TD>Petrushevska, T.; Leloudas, G.; Ilić, D.; Bronikowski, M.; Charalampopoulos, P.; Jaisawal, G. K.; Paraskeva, E.; Pursiainen, M.; Rakić, N.; Schulze, S.; Taggart, K.; Wedderkopp, C. K.; Anderson, J. P.; de Boer, T.; Chambers, K.; Chen, T. W.; Damljanović, G.; Fraser, M.; Gao, H.; Gomboc, A.; Gromadzki, M.; Ihanec, N.; Maguire, K.; Marčun, B.; Müller-Bravo, T. E.; Nicholl, M.; Onori, F.; Reynolds, T. M.; Smartt, S. J.; Sollerman, J.; Smith, K. W.; Wevers, T.; Wyrzykowski, Ł.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 669, id.A140, 19 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023A&amp;A...669A.140P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023A&amp;A...669A..82Z</TD>
<TD>Influence of a mass transfer stability criterion on double white dwarf populations</TD>
<TD>Zhenwei, Li; Xuefei, Chen; Hongwei, Ge; Hai-Liang, Chen; Zhanwen, Han</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 669, id.A82, 26 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023A&amp;A...669A..82Z</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023A&amp;A...669A..75L</TD>
<TD>Deciphering the extreme X-ray variability of the nuclear transient eRASSt J045650.3−203750. A likely repeating partial tidal disruption event</TD>
<TD>Liu, Z.; Malyali, A.; Krumpe, M.; Homan, D.; Goodwin, A. J.; Grotova, I.; Kawka, A.; Rau, A.; Merloni, A.; Anderson, G. E.; Miller-Jones, J. C. A.; Markowitz, A. G.; Ciroi, S.; Di Mille, F.; Schramm, M.; Tang, S.; Buckley, D. A. H.; Gromadzki, M.; Jin, C.; Buchner, J.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 669, id.A75, 26 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023A&amp;A...669A..75L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2023A&amp;A...669A..51M</TD>
<TD>A long life of excess: The interacting transient SN 2017hcc</TD>
<TD>Moran, S.; Fraser, M.; Kotak, R.; Pastorello, A.; Benetti, S.; Brennan, S. J.; Gutiérrez, C. P.; Kankare, E.; Kuncarayakti, H.; Mattila, S.; Reynolds, T. M.; Anderson, J. P.; Brown, P. J.; Campana, S.; Chambers, K. C.; Chen, T. -W.; Della Valle, M.; Dennefeld, M.; Elias-Rosa, N.; Galbany, L.; Galindo-Guil, F. J.; Gromadzki, M.; Hiramatsu, D.; Inserra, C.; Leloudas, G.; Müller-Bravo, T. E.; Nicholl, M.; Reguitti, A.; Shahbandeh, M.; Smartt, S. J.; Tartaglia, L.; Young, D. R.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 669, id.A51, 22 pp.</TD>
<TD>2023-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2023A&amp;A...669A..51M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022Univ....9....7H</TD>
<TD>Prospects of Searching for Type Ia Supernovae with 2.5-m Wide Field Survey Telescope</TD>
<TD>Hu, Maokai; Hu, Lei; Jiang, Ji-an; Xiao, Lin; Fan, Lulu; Wei, Junjie; Wu, Xuefeng</TD>
<TD>Universe, vol. 9, issue 1, p. 7</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022Univ....9....7H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022PhRvD.106l4017X</TD>
<TD>Constraining the extra polarization modes of gravitational waves with double white dwarfs</TD>
<TD>Xie, Ning; Zhang, Jian-dong; Huang, Shun-Jia; Hu, Yi-Ming; Mei, Jianwei</TD>
<TD>Physical Review D, Volume 106, Issue 12, article id.124017</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022PhRvD.106l4017X</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022PASP..134l4502T</TD>
<TD>The Spectroscopic Classification of Astronomical Transients (SCAT) Survey: Overview, Pipeline Description, Initial Results, and Future Plans</TD>
<TD>Tucker, M. A.; Shappee, B. J.; Huber, M. E.; Payne, A. V.; Do, A.; Hinkle, J. T.; de Jaeger, T.; Ashall, C.; Desai, D. D.; Hoogendam, W. B.; Aldering, G.; Auchettl, K.; Baranec, C.; Bulger, J.; Chambers, K.; Chun, M.; Hodapp, K. W.; Lowe, T. B.; McKay, L.; Rampy, R.; Rubin, D.; Tonry, J. L.</TD>
<TD>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 134, Issue 1042, id.124502, 12 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022PASP..134l4502T</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022PASJ...74.1421C</TD>
<TD>The first photometric investigation of the poor-thermal contact binary V749 Aurigae</TD>
<TD>Chang, Lin-Feng; Zhu, Li-Ying; Sarotsakulchai, Thawicharat; Soonthornthum, Boonrucksar</TD>
<TD>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Volume 74, Issue 6, pp.1421-1428</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022PASJ...74.1421C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022PASJ...74.1287T</TD>
<TD>PNV J00444033+4113068: Early superhumps with 0.7 mag amplitude and non-red color</TD>
<TD>Tampo, Yusuke; Isogai, Keisuke; Kojiguchi, Naoto; Uemura, Makoto; Kato, Taichi; Tordai, Tamás; Vanmunster, Tonny; Itoh, Hiroshi; Dubovsky, Pavol A.; Medulka, Tomáš; Sano, Yasuo; Hambsch, Franz-Josef; Taguchi, Kenta; Maehara, Hiroyuki; Ito, Junpei; Nogami, Daisaku</TD>
<TD>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Volume 74, Issue 6, pp.1287-1294</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022PASJ...74.1287T</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022NewAR..9501659P</TD>
<TD>Challenges for ΛCDM: An update</TD>
<TD>Perivolaropoulos, L.; Skara, F.</TD>
<TD>New Astronomy Reviews, Volume 95, article id. 101659.</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022NewAR..9501659P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022Natur.612..430A</TD>
<TD>A very luminous jet from the disruption of a star by a massive black hole</TD>
<TD>Andreoni, Igor; Coughlin, Michael W.; Perley, Daniel A.; Yao, Yuhan; Lu, Wenbin; Cenko, S. Bradley; Kumar, Harsh; Anand, Shreya; Ho, Anna Y. Q.; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; de Ugarte Postigo, Antonio; Sagués-Carracedo, Ana; Schulze, Steve; Kann, D. Alexander; Kulkarni, S. R.; Sollerman, Jesper; Tanvir, Nial; Rest, Armin; Izzo, Luca; Somalwar, Jean J.; Kaplan, David L.; Ahumada, Tomás; Anupama, G. C.; Auchettl, Katie; Barway, Sudhanshu; Bellm, Eric C.; Bhalerao, Varun; Bloom, Joshua S.; Bremer, Michael; Bulla, Mattia; Burns, Eric; Campana, Sergio; Chandra, Poonam; Charalampopoulos, Panos; Cooke, Jeff; D'Elia, Valerio; Das, Kaustav Kashyap; Dobie, Dougal; Agüí Fernández, José Feliciano; Freeburn, James; Fremling, Cristoffer; Gezari, Suvi; Goode, Simon; Graham, Matthew J.; Hammerstein, Erica; Karambelkar, Viraj R.; Kilpatrick, Charles D.; Kool, Erik C.; Krips, Melanie; Laher, Russ R.; Leloudas, Giorgos; Levan, Andrew; Lundquist, Michael J.; Mahabal, Ashish A.; Medford, Michael S.; Miller, M. Coleman; Möller, Anais; Mooley, Kunal P.; Nayana, A. J.; Nir, Guy; Pang, Peter T. H.; Paraskeva, Emmy; Perley, Richard A.; Petitpas, Glen; Pursiainen, Miika; Ravi, Vikram; Ridden-Harper, Ryan; Riddle, Reed; Rigault, Mickael; Rodriguez, Antonio C.; Rusholme, Ben; Sharma, Yashvi; Smith, I. A.; Stein, Robert D.; Thöne, Christina; Tohuvavohu, Aaron; Valdes, Frank; van Roestel, Jan; Vergani, Susanna D.; Wang, Qinan; Zhang, Jielai</TD>
<TD>Nature, Volume 612, Issue 7940, p.430-434</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022Natur.612..430A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022Natur.612..228T</TD>
<TD>A nearby long gamma-ray burst from a merger of compact objects</TD>
<TD>Troja, E.; Fryer, C. L.; O'Connor, B.; Ryan, G.; Dichiara, S.; Kumar, A.; Ito, N.; Gupta, R.; Wollaeger, R. T.; Norris, J. P.; Kawai, N.; Butler, N. R.; Aryan, A.; Misra, K.; Hosokawa, R.; Murata, K. L.; Niwano, M.; Pandey, S. B.; Kutyrev, A.; van Eerten, H. J.; Chase, E. A.; Hu, Y. -D.; Caballero-Garcia, M. D.; Castro-Tirado, A. J.</TD>
<TD>Nature, Volume 612, Issue 7939, p.228-231</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022Natur.612..228T</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022NatAs...6.1452A</TD>
<TD>A fast-rising tidal disruption event from a candidate intermediate-mass black hole</TD>
<TD>Angus, C. R.; Baldassare, V. F.; Mockler, B.; Foley, R. J.; Ramirez-Ruiz, E.; Raimundo, S. I.; French, K. D.; Auchettl, K.; Pfister, H.; Gall, C.; Hjorth, J.; Drout, M. R.; Alexander, K. D.; Dimitriadis, G.; Hung, T.; Jones, D. O.; Rest, A.; Siebert, M. R.; Taggart, K.; Terreran, G.; Tinyanont, S.; Carroll, C. M.; DeMarchi, L.; Earl, N.; Gagliano, A.; Izzo, L.; Villar, V. A.; Zenati, Y.; Arendse, N.; Cold, C.; de Boer, T. J. L.; Chambers, K. C.; Coulter, D. A.; Khetan, N.; Lin, C. C.; Magnier, E. A.; Rojas-Bravo, C.; Wainscoat, R. J.; Wojtak, R.</TD>
<TD>Nature Astronomy, Volume 6, p. 1452-1463</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022NatAs...6.1452A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.tmp.3485B</TD>
<TD>Pan-chromatic photometric classification of supernovae from multiple surveys and transfer learning for future surveys</TD>
<TD>Burhanudin, Umar F.; Maund, Justyn R.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Advance Access</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.tmp.3485B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.517.5921L</TD>
<TD>The orbital evolution of Atira asteroids</TD>
<TD>Lai, H. T.; Ip, W. H.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 517, Issue 4, pp.5921-5929</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.517.5921L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.517.5617S</TD>
<TD>Optical studies of a bright Type Iax supernova SN 2020rea</TD>
<TD>Singh, Mridweeka; Misra, Kuntal; Sahu, Devendra K.; Ailawadhi, Bhavya; Dutta, Anirban; Howell, D. Andrew; Anupama, G. C.; Bostroem, K. Azalee; Burke, Jamison; Dastidar, Raya; Gangopadhyay, Anjasha; Hiramatsu, Daichi; Im, Hyobin; McCully, Curtis; Pellegrino, Craig; Srivastav, Shubham; Teja, Rishabh Singh</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 517, Issue 4, pp.5617-5626</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.517.5617S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.517.5449A</TD>
<TD>The lure of sirens: joint distance and velocity measurements with third-generation detectors</TD>
<TD>Alfradique, Viviane; Quartin, Miguel; Amendola, Luca; Castro, Tiago; Toubiana, Alexandre</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 517, Issue 4, pp.5449-5462</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.517.5449A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.517.4916E</TD>
<TD>Magnetic braking saturates: evidence from the orbital period distribution of low-mass detached eclipsing binaries from ZTF</TD>
<TD>El-Badry, Kareem; Conroy, Charlie; Fuller, Jim; Kiman, Rocio; van Roestel, Jan; Rodriguez, Antonio C.; Burdge, Kevin B.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 517, Issue 4, pp.4916-4939</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.517.4916E</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.517.4098X</TD>
<TD>SN 2019ein: a Type Ia supernova likely originated from a sub-Chandrasekhar-mass explosion</TD>
<TD>Xi, Gaobo; Wang, Xiaofeng; Li, Wenxiong; Mo, Jun; Zhang, Jujia; Liu, Jialian; Chen, Zhihao; Filippenko, Alexei V.; Zheng, Weikang; Brink, Thomas G.; Zhang, Xinghan; Sai, Hanna; Ehgamberdiev, Shuhrat A.; Mirzaqulov, Davron; Zhang, Jicheng</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 517, Issue 3, pp.4098-4118</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.517.4098X</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.517.3864S</TD>
<TD>The nova KT Eri Is a recurrent nova with a recurrence time-scale of 40-50 yr</TD>
<TD>Schaefer, Bradley E.; Walter, Frederick M.; Hounsell, Rebekah; Hillman, Yael</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 517, Issue 3, pp.3864-3880</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.517.3864S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.517.3640S</TD>
<TD>Comprehensive listing of 156 reliable orbital periods for novae, including 49 new periods</TD>
<TD>Schaefer, Bradley E.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 517, Issue 3, pp.3640-3659</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.517.3640S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.517.3469E</TD>
<TD>Constraints on the Galactic Centre environment from Gaia hypervelocity stars II: The evolved population</TD>
<TD>Evans, F. A.; Marchetti, T.; Rossi, E. M.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 517, Issue 3, pp.3469-3484</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.517.3469E</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.517.3362M</TD>
<TD>Machine learning-based search for cataclysmic variables within Gaia Science Alerts</TD>
<TD>Mistry, D.; Copperwheat, C. M.; Darnley, M. J.; Olier, I.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 517, Issue 3, pp.3362-3376</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.517.3362M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.517.2801W</TD>
<TD>Radio observations of the Black Hole X-ray Binary EXO 1846-031 re-awakening from a 34-year slumber</TD>
<TD>Williams, D. R. A.; Motta, S. E.; Fender, R.; Miller-Jones, J. C. A.; Neilsen, J.; Allison, J. R.; Bright, J.; Heywood, I.; Jacob, P. F. L.; Rhodes, L.; Tremou, E.; Woudt, P. A.; Eijnden, J. van den; Carotenuto, F.; Green, D. A.; Titterington, D.; van der Horst, A. J.; Saikia, P.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 517, Issue 2, pp.2801-2817</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.517.2801W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.517.2165C</TD>
<TD>Star-spots and magnetism: testing the activity paradigm in the Pleiades and M67</TD>
<TD>Cao, Lyra; Pinsonneault, Marc H.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 517, Issue 2, pp.2165-2189</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.517.2165C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.517.2056G</TD>
<TD>SN 2020wnt: a slow-evolving carbon-rich superluminous supernova with no O II lines and a bumpy light curve</TD>
<TD>Gutiérrez, C. P.; Pastorello, A.; Bersten, M.; Benetti, S.; Orellana, M.; Fiore, A.; Karamehmetoglu, E.; Kravtsov, T.; Reguitti, A.; Reynolds, T. M.; Valerin, G.; Mazzali, P.; Sullivan, M.; Cai, Y. -Z.; Elias-Rosa, N.; Fraser, M.; Hsiao, E. Y.; Kankare, E.; Kotak, R.; Kuncarayakti, H.; Li, Z.; Mattila, S.; Mo, J.; Moran, S.; Ochner, P.; Shahbandeh, M.; Tomasella, L.; Wang, X.; Yan, S.; Zhang, J.; Zhang, T.; Stritzinger, M. D.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 517, Issue 2, pp.2056-2075</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.517.2056G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.517.1884A</TD>
<TD>Searching for the next Galactic Luminous red nova</TD>
<TD>Addison, Harry; Blagorodnova, Nadejda; Groot, Paul J.; Erasmus, Nicolas; Jones, David; Mogawana, Orapeleng</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 517, Issue 2, pp.1884-1900</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.517.1884A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022LRR....25....6M</TD>
<TD>Unveiling the Universe with emerging cosmological probes</TD>
<TD>Moresco, Michele; Amati, Lorenzo; Amendola, Luca; Birrer, Simon; Blakeslee, John P.; Cantiello, Michele; Cimatti, Andrea; Darling, Jeremy; Della Valle, Massimo; Fishbach, Maya; Grillo, Claudio; Hamaus, Nico; Holz, Daniel; Izzo, Luca; Jimenez, Raul; Lusso, Elisabeta; Meneghetti, Massimo; Piedipalumbo, Ester; Pisani, Alice; Pourtsidou, Alkistis; Pozzetti, Lucia; Quartin, Miguel; Risaliti, Guido; Rosati, Piero; Verde, Licia</TD>
<TD>Living Reviews in Relativity, Volume 25, Issue 1, article id.6</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022LRR....25....6M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022LRR....25....3B</TD>
<TD>Electromagnetic counterparts to massive black-hole mergers</TD>
<TD>Bogdanović, Tamara; Miller, M. Coleman; Blecha, Laura</TD>
<TD>Living Reviews in Relativity, Volume 25, Issue 1, article id.3</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022LRR....25....3B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022JApA...43...53S</TD>
<TD>Gravitational waves and electromagnetic transients</TD>
<TD>Singhal, Akshat; Palit, Sourav; Bala, Suman; Waratkar, Gaurav; Kumar, Harsh; Bhalerao, Varun</TD>
<TD>Journal of Astrophysics and Astronomy, Volume 43, Issue 2, article id.53</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022JApA...43...53S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022JApA...43...42W</TD>
<TD>Analysis of dual band and survey photometry of two low mass ratio contact binary systems</TD>
<TD>Wadhwa, Surjit S.; de Horta, Ain Y.; Filipović, Miroslav D.; Totohill, F. H. Nick</TD>
<TD>Journal of Astrophysics and Astronomy, Volume 43, Issue 2, article id.42</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022JApA...43...42W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022CeMDA.134...59C</TD>
<TD>Optimization of artificial neural networks models applied to the identification of images of asteroids' resonant arguments</TD>
<TD>Carruba, V.; Aljbaae, S.; Caritá, G.; Domingos, R. C.; Martins, B.</TD>
<TD>Celestial Mechanics and Dynamical Astronomy, Volume 134, Issue 6, article id.59</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022CeMDA.134...59C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022AstL...48..767K</TD>
<TD>Search for Tidal Disruption Events Based on the SRG/eROSITA Survey with Subsequent Optical Spectroscopy</TD>
<TD>Khorunzhev, G. A.; Sazonov, S. Yu.; Medvedev, P. S.; Gilfanov, M. R.; Atapin, K. E.; Belinski, A. A.; Vozyakova, O. V.; Dodin, A. V.; Safonov, B. S.; Tatarnikov, A. M.; Bikmaev, I. F.; Burenin, R. A.; Dodonov, S. N.; Eselevich, M. V.; Zaznobin, I. A.; Krivonos, R. A.; Uklein, R. I.; Postnov, K. A.; Sunyaev, R. A.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy Letters, Volume 48, Issue 12, p.767-789</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022AstL...48..767K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022AstL...48..735M</TD>
<TD>Highly Variable Active Galactic Nuclei in the SRG/eROSITA Sky Survey: I. The Constriction of a Sample and the Catalog of Objects Detected in a Low State</TD>
<TD>Medvedev, P. S.; Gilfanov, M. R.; Sazonov, S. Yu.; Sunyaev, R. A.; Khorunzhev, G. A.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy Letters, Volume 48, Issue 12, p.735-754</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022AstL...48..735M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022AstBu..77..437R</TD>
<TD>Magnetic Fields of Chemically Peculiar and Related Stars. VIII. Main Results of 2021 and Near-Future Prospects</TD>
<TD>Romanyuk, I. I.</TD>
<TD>Astrophysical Bulletin, Volume 77, Issue 4, p.437-445</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022AstBu..77..437R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...941L..32K</TD>
<TD>Late-time H/He-poor Circumstellar Interaction in the Type Ic Supernova SN 2021ocs: An Exposed Oxygen-Magnesium Layer and Extreme Stripping of the Progenitor</TD>
<TD>Kuncarayakti, H.; Maeda, K.; Dessart, L.; Nagao, T.; Fulton, M.; Gutiérrez, C. P.; Huber, M. E.; Young, D. R.; Kotak, R.; Mattila, S.; Anderson, J. P.; Ferrari, L.; Folatelli, G.; Gao, H.; Magnier, E.; Smith, K. W.; Srivastav, S.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 941, Issue 2, id.L32, 7 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...941L..32K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...941..208I</TD>
<TD>Forecasting the Detection Capabilities of Third-generation Gravitational-wave Detectors Using GWFAST</TD>
<TD>Iacovelli, Francesco; Mancarella, Michele; Foffa, Stefano; Maggiore, Michele</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 941, Issue 2, id.208, 48 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...941..208I</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...941..199S</TD>
<TD>A New Flaring Black Widow Candidate and Demographics of Black Widow Millisecond Pulsars in the Galactic Field</TD>
<TD>Swihart, Samuel J.; Strader, Jay; Chomiuk, Laura; Aydi, Elias; Sokolovsky, Kirill V.; Ray, Paul S.; Kerr, Matthew</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 941, Issue 2, id.199, 20 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...941..199S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...941..165P</TD>
<TD>Photometric and Spectroscopic Study of the EXor-like Eruptive Young Star Gaia19fct</TD>
<TD>Park, Sunkyung; Kóspál, Ágnes; Ábrahám, Péter; Cruz-Sáenz de Miera, Fernando; Fiorellino, Eleonora; Siwak, Michał; Nagy, Zsófia; Giannini, Teresa; Carini, Roberta; Szabó, Zsófia Marianna; Lee, Jeong-Eun; Lee, Jae-Joon; Vitali, Fabrizio; Kun, Mária; Cseh, Borbála; Krezinger, Máté; Kriskovics, Levente; Ordasi, András; Pál, András; Szakáts, Róbert; Vida, Krisztián; Vinkó, József</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 941, Issue 2, id.165, 19 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...941..165P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...941..116R</TD>
<TD>The Impact of Initial-Final Mass Relations on Black Hole Microlensing</TD>
<TD>Rose, Sam; Lam, Casey Y.; Lu, Jessica R.; Medford, Michael; Hosek, Matthew W.; Abrams, Natasha S.; Ramey, Emily; Vasylyev, Sergiy S.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 941, Issue 2, id.116, 18 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...941..116R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...941..107G</TD>
<TD>Luminous Supernovae: Unveiling a Population between Superluminous and Normal Core-collapse Supernovae</TD>
<TD>Gomez, Sebastian; Berger, Edo; Nicholl, Matt; Blanchard, Peter K.; Hosseinzadeh, Griffin</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 941, Issue 2, id.107, 30 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...941..107G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...941..104Y</TD>
<TD>Classifying Unidentified X-Ray Sources in the Chandra Source Catalog Using a Multiwavelength Machine-learning Approach</TD>
<TD>Yang, Hui; Hare, Jeremy; Kargaltsev, Oleg; Volkov, Igor; Chen, Steven; Rangelov, Blagoy</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 941, Issue 2, id.104, 35 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...941..104Y</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...941...28S</TD>
<TD>The Double White Dwarf Merger Progenitors of SDSS J2211+1136 and ZTF J1901+1458</TD>
<TD>Sousa, M. F.; Coelho, J. G.; de Araujo, J. C. N.; Kepler, S. O.; Rueda, J. A.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 941, Issue 1, id.28, 10 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...941...28S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...940L..56P</TD>
<TD>The Periodic Signals of Nova V1674 Herculis (2021)</TD>
<TD>Patterson, Joseph; Enenstein, Josie; de Miguel, Enrique; Epstein-Martin, Marguerite; Kemp, Jonathan; Sabo, Richard; Cooney, Walt; Vanmunster, Tonny; Dubovsky, Pavol; Hambsch, Franz-Josef; Myers, Gordon; Lemay, Damien; Sokolovsky, Kirill; Collins, Donald; Campbell, Tut; Roberts, George; Richmond, Michael; Brincat, Stephen; Ulowetz, Joseph; Dvorak, Shawn; Tordai, Tamás; Dufoer, Sjoerd; Cahaly, Andrew; Galdies, Charles; Goff, Bill; Wilkin, Francis P.; Wood, Matt A.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 940, Issue 2, id.L56, 6 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...940L..56P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...940L..44R</TD>
<TD>Interacting Kilonovae: Long-lasting Electromagnetic Counterparts to Binary Mergers in the Accretion Disks of Active Galactic Nuclei</TD>
<TD>Ren, Jia; Chen, Ken; Wang, Yun; Dai, Zi-Gao</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 940, Issue 2, id.L44, 9 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...940L..44R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...940..165Y</TD>
<TD>Discovery of One Neutron Star Candidate from Radial-velocity Monitoring</TD>
<TD>Yuan, Hailong; Wang, Song; Bai, Zhongrui; Wang, Yue; Dong, Yiqiao; Wang, Mengxin; Yu, Sicheng; Zhao, Yongheng; Chu, Yaoquan; Liu, Jifeng; Zhang, Haotong</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 940, Issue 2, id.165, 12 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...940..165Y</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...940..155D</TD>
<TD>Contracting and Expanding Binary Black Holes in 3D Low-mass AGN Disks: The Importance of Separation</TD>
<TD>Dempsey, Adam M.; Li, Hui; Mishra, Bhupendra; Li, Shengtai</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 940, Issue 2, id.155, 19 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...940..155D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022AJ....164..263M</TD>
<TD>Deep Generative Modeling of Periodic Variable Stars Using Physical Parameters</TD>
<TD>Martínez-Palomera, Jorge; Bloom, Joshua S.; Abrahams, Ellianna S.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 164, Issue 6, id.263, 14 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022AJ....164..263M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022AJ....164..251L</TD>
<TD>Bridging the Gap-The Disappearance of the Intermediate Period Gap for Fully Convective Stars, Uncovered by New ZTF Rotation Periods</TD>
<TD>Lu, Yuxi Lucy; Curtis, Jason L.; Angus, Ruth; David, Trevor J.; Hattori, Soichiro</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 164, Issue 6, id.251, 15 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022AJ....164..251L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022AJ....164..229B</TD>
<TD>Magnetic Interactions in Orbital Dynamics</TD>
<TD>Bromley, Benjamin C.; Kenyon, Scott J.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 164, Issue 6, id.229, 18 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022AJ....164..229B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;ARv..30....8T</TD>
<TD>Strong lensing time-delay cosmography in the 2020s</TD>
<TD>Treu, Tommaso; Suyu, Sherry H.; Marshall, Philip J.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomy and Astrophysics Review, Volume 30, Issue 1, article id.8</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;ARv..30....8T</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...668A.112X</TD>
<TD>Shell helium-burning hot subdwarf B stars as candidates for blue large-amplitude pulsators</TD>
<TD>Xiong, H.; Casagrande, L.; Chen, X.; Vos, J.; Zhang, X.; Justham, S.; Li, J.; Wu, T.; Li, Y.; Han, Z.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 668, id.A112, 22 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...668A.112X</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...668A..97K</TD>
<TD>Examining the dust of the tailless Oort-cloud comet C/2020 T2</TD>
<TD>Kwon, Yuna G.; Masiero, Joseph R.; Markkanen, Johannes</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 668, id.A97, 10 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...668A..97K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...668A..80L</TD>
<TD>He-star donor AM CVn stars and their progenitors as LISA sources</TD>
<TD>Liu, W. -M.; Yungelson, L.; Kuranov, A.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 668, id.A80, 9 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...668A..80L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...668A..58A</TD>
<TD>Structure and evolution of ultra-massive white dwarfs in general relativity</TD>
<TD>Althaus, Leandro G.; Camisassa, María E.; Torres, Santiago; Battich, Tiara; Córsico, Alejandro H.; Rebassa-Mansergas, Alberto; Raddi, Roberto</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 668, id.A58, 11 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...668A..58A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...668A..43L</TD>
<TD>HyperGal: Hyperspectral scene modeling for supernova typing with the SED Machine integral field spectrograph</TD>
<TD>Lezmy, J.; Copin, Y.; Rigault, M.; Smith, M.; Neill, J. D.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 668, id.A43, 14 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...668A..43L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...668A..40L</TD>
<TD>Tracing the Milky Way warp and spiral arms with classical Cepheids</TD>
<TD>Lemasle, B.; Lala, H. N.; Kovtyukh, V.; Hanke, M.; Prudil, Z.; Bono, G.; Braga, V. F.; da Silva, R.; Fabrizio, M.; Fiorentino, G.; François, P.; Grebel, E. K.; Kniazev, A.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 668, id.A40, 28 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...668A..40L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...668A..13H</TD>
<TD>Open clusters housing classical Cepheids in Gaia DR3</TD>
<TD>Hao, C. J.; Xu, Y.; Wu, Z. Y.; Lin, Z. H.; Bian, S. B.; Li, Y. J.; Liu, D. J.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 668, id.A13, 13 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...668A..13H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022PhRvD.106j4015S</TD>
<TD>Premerger localization of intermediate mass binary black holes with LISA and prospects of joint observations with Athena and LSST</TD>
<TD>Saini, Pankaj; Bhat, Sajad A.; Arun, K. G.</TD>
<TD>Physical Review D, Volume 106, Issue 10, article id.104015</TD>
<TD>2022-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022PhRvD.106j4015S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022PASP..134k4507X</TD>
<TD>A New Period Determination Method for Periodic Variable Stars</TD>
<TD>Xu, Xiao-Hui; Zhu, Qing-Feng; Li, Xu-Zhi; Li, Bin; Zheng, Hang; Qiu, Jin-Sheng; Zhao, Hai-Bin</TD>
<TD>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 134, Issue 1041, id.114507, 19 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022PASP..134k4507X</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022Natur.611..256C</TD>
<TD>Shock cooling of a red-supergiant supernova at redshift 3 in lensed images</TD>
<TD>Chen, Wenlei; Kelly, Patrick L.; Oguri, Masamune; Broadhurst, Thomas J.; Diego, Jose M.; Emami, Najmeh; Filippenko, Alexei V.; Treu, Tommaso L.; Zitrin, Adi</TD>
<TD>Nature, Volume 611, Issue 7935, p.256-259</TD>
<TD>2022-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022Natur.611..256C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022NatRP...4..697G</TD>
<TD>High-energy neutrino transients and the future of multi-messenger astronomy</TD>
<TD>Guépin, Claire; Kotera, Kumiko; Oikonomou, Foteini</TD>
<TD>Nature Reviews Physics, Volume 4, Issue 11, p.697-712</TD>
<TD>2022-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022NatRP...4..697G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.517L..97L</TD>
<TD>Investigation of a likely orbital periodicity of Nova Hercules 2021 in X-rays and γ-rays</TD>
<TD>Lin, Lupin Chun-Che; Fan, Jhih-Ling; Hu, Chin-Ping; Takata, Jumpei; Li, Kwan-Lok</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 517, Issue 1, pp.L97-L101</TD>
<TD>2022-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.517L..97L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.517L..71Z</TD>
<TD>Modelling the flare in NGC 1097 from 1991 to 2004 as a tidal disruption event</TD>
<TD>Zhang, Xue-Guang</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 517, Issue 1, pp.L71-L75</TD>
<TD>2022-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.517L..71Z</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.517L..49B</TD>
<TD>The discovery and characterization of (594913) 'Ayló'chaxnim, a kilometre sized asteroid inside the orbit of Venus</TD>
<TD>Bolin, Bryce T.; Ahumada, T.; van Dokkum, P.; Fremling, C.; Granvik, M.; Hardegree-Ullman, K. K.; Harikane, Y.; Purdum, J. N.; Serabyn, E.; Southworth, J.; Zhai, C.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 517, Issue 1, pp.L49-L54</TD>
<TD>2022-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.517L..49B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.517..393M</TD>
<TD>Real-time detection of anomalies in large-scale transient surveys</TD>
<TD>Muthukrishna, Daniel; Mandel, Kaisey S.; Lochner, Michelle; Webb, Sara; Narayan, Gautham</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 517, Issue 1, pp.393-419</TD>
<TD>2022-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.517..393M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.516.5945J</TD>
<TD>The 'Giraffe': discovery of a stripped red giant in an interacting binary with an 2 M&lt;SUB&gt;⊙&lt;/SUB&gt; lower giant</TD>
<TD>Jayasinghe, T.; Thompson, Todd A.; Kochanek, C. S.; Stanek, K. Z.; Rowan, D. M.; Martin, D. V.; El-Badry, Kareem; Vallely, P. J.; Hinkle, J. T.; Huber, D.; Isaacson, H.; Tayar, J.; Auchettl, K.; Ilyin, I.; Howard, A. W.; Badenes, C.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 516, Issue 4, pp.5945-5963</TD>
<TD>2022-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.516.5945J</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.516.5935W</TD>
<TD>The emergence of diffused gamma-ray burst afterglows from the discs of active galactic nuclei</TD>
<TD>Wang, Yi-Han; Lazzati, Davide; Perna, Rosalba</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 516, Issue 4, pp.5935-5944</TD>
<TD>2022-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.516.5935W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.516.5785W</TD>
<TD>Discovering faint and high apparent motion rate near-Earth asteroids using a deep learning program</TD>
<TD>Wang, Franklin; Ge, Jian; Willis, Kevin</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 516, Issue 4, pp.5785-5798</TD>
<TD>2022-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.516.5785W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.516.4980L</TD>
<TD>Orphan optical flare as SOSS emission afterglow, localization in time</TD>
<TD>Lipunov, V.; Kornilov, V.; Zhirkov, K.; Tyurina, N.; Gorbovskoy, E.; Vlasenko, D.; Simakov, S.; Topolev, V.; Francile, C.; Podesta, R.; Podesta, F.; Svinkin, D.; Budnev, N.; Gress, O.; Balanutsa, P.; Kuznetsov, A.; Chasovnikov, A.; Serra-Ricart, M.; Gabovich, A.; Minkina, E.; Antipov, G.; Svertilov, S.; Tlatov, A.; Senik, V.; Tselik, Yu; Kechin, Ya; Yurkov, V.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 516, Issue 4, pp.4980-4987</TD>
<TD>2022-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.516.4980L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.516.4949S</TD>
<TD>On the diversity of magnetar-driven kilonovae</TD>
<TD>Sarin, Nikhil; Omand, Conor M. B.; Margalit, Ben; Jones, David I.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 516, Issue 4, pp.4949-4962</TD>
<TD>2022-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.516.4949S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.516.4833J</TD>
<TD>A detailed study of the barium central star of the planetary nebula Abell 70</TD>
<TD>Jones, David; Boffin, Henri M. J.; Brown, Alex J.; Zak, Jiri; Hume, George; Munday, James; Miszalski, Brent</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 516, Issue 4, pp.4833-4843</TD>
<TD>2022-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.516.4833J</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.516.4822R</TD>
<TD>Constraining R&lt;SUB&gt;V&lt;/SUB&gt; variation using highly reddened Type Ia supernovae from the Pantheon+ sample</TD>
<TD>Rose, B. M.; Popovic, B.; Scolnic, D.; Brout, D.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 516, Issue 4, pp.4822-4832</TD>
<TD>2022-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.516.4822R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.516.4805M</TD>
<TD>Multiple flares caused by mass ejection episodes during the advanced nebular phase of Nova Scuti 2019</TD>
<TD>Munari, U.; Righetti, G. L.; Dallaporta, S.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 516, Issue 4, pp.4805-4813</TD>
<TD>2022-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.516.4805M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.516.4760C</TD>
<TD>Numerical relativity simulations of the neutron star merger GW190425: microphysics and mass ratio effects</TD>
<TD>Camilletti, Alessandro; Chiesa, Leonardo; Ricigliano, Giacomo; Perego, Albino; Lippold, Lukas Chris; Padamata, Surendra; Bernuzzi, Sebastiano; Radice, David; Logoteta, Domenico; Guercilena, Federico Maria</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 516, Issue 4, pp.4760-4781</TD>
<TD>2022-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.516.4760C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.516.4517K</TD>
<TD>GROWTH on S190426c II: GROWTH-India Telescope search for an optical counterpart with a custom image reduction and candidate vetting pipeline</TD>
<TD>Kumar, Harsh; Bhalerao, Varun; Anupama, G. C.; Barway, Sudhanshu; Coughlin, Michael W.; De, Kishalay; Deshmukh, Kunal; Dutta, Anirban; Goldstein, Daniel A.; Jassani, Adeem; Joharle, Simran; Karambelker, Viraj; Khandagale, Maitreya; Kumar, Brajesh; Saraogi, Divita; Sharma, Yashvi; Shenoy, Vedant; singer, Leo; Singh, Avinash; Waratkar, Gaurav</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 516, Issue 3, pp.4517-4528</TD>
<TD>2022-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.516.4517K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.516.4497S</TD>
<TD>The recurrent nova U Scorpii from the 2010.1 to 2022.4 eruptions; the missed eruption of 2016.78 ± 0.10 and the critical complex period changes</TD>
<TD>Schaefer, Bradley E.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 516, Issue 3, pp.4497-4516</TD>
<TD>2022-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.516.4497S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.516.3650Z</TD>
<TD>A 3.8 yr optical quasi-periodic oscillations in blue quasar SDSS J132144+033055 through combined light curves from CSS and ZTF</TD>
<TD>Zhang, XueGuang</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 516, Issue 3, pp.3650-3660</TD>
<TD>2022-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.516.3650Z</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.516.3602E</TD>
<TD>Birth of a Be star: an APOGEE search for Be stars forming through binary mass transfer</TD>
<TD>El-Badry, Kareem; Conroy, Charlie; Quataert, Eliot; Rix, Hans-Walter; Labadie-Bartz, Jonathan; Jayasinghe, Tharindu; Thompson, Todd; Cargile, Phillip; Stassun, Keivan G.; Ilyin, Ilya</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 516, Issue 3, pp.3602-3630</TD>
<TD>2022-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.516.3602E</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.516.3144D</TD>
<TD>Short-duration accretion states of Polars as seen in TESS and ZTF data</TD>
<TD>Duffy, C.; Ramsay, G.; Wu, Kinwah; Mason, Paul A.; Hakala, P.; Steeghs, D.; Wood, M. A.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 516, Issue 3, pp.3144-3158</TD>
<TD>2022-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.516.3144D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022EPJP..137.1274J</TD>
<TD>Physical analysis of Yukawa-Casimir traversable wormhole solutions in non-minimally coupled f(T) gravity</TD>
<TD>Jawad, Abdul; Sulehri, M. Bilal Amin; Rani, Shamaila</TD>
<TD>The European Physical Journal Plus, Volume 137, Issue 11, article id.1274</TD>
<TD>2022-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022EPJP..137.1274J</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ChPhL..39k9801L</TD>
<TD>Strongly Lensed Transient Sources: A Review</TD>
<TD>Liao, Kai; Biesiada, Marek; Zhu, Zong-Hong</TD>
<TD>Chinese Physics Letters, Volume 39, Issue 11, id.119801, 20 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ChPhL..39k9801L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022AstL...48..623L</TD>
<TD>The First Detection of an Orphan Burst at the Rise Phase</TD>
<TD>Lipunov, V. M.; Kornilov, V. G.; Topolev, V. V.; Tyurina, N. V.; Gorbovskoy, E. S.; Simakov, S. G.; Zhirkov, K. K.; Vlasenko, D. S.; Francile, C.; Podesta, R.; Podesta, F.; Svinkin, D. S.; Budnev, N. M.; Balanutsa, P. V.; Cheryasov, D. V.; Chasovnikov, A. R.; Rebolo, R.; Serra-Ricart, M.; Gress, O. A.; Ershova, O. A.; Yurkov, V. V.; Gabovich, A. S.; Tlatov, A. G.; Minkina, E. M.; Vladimirov, V. V.; Kuznetsov, A. S.; Antipov, G. A.; Svertilov, S. I.; Tselik, Yu.; Kechin, Ya.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy Letters, Volume 48, Issue 11, p.623-635</TD>
<TD>2022-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022AstL...48..623L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...940L..27W</TD>
<TD>Extreme Mass Loss in Low-mass Type Ib/c Supernova Progenitors</TD>
<TD>Wu, Samantha C.; Fuller, Jim</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 940, Issue 1, id.L27, 6 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...940L..27W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...940...90C</TD>
<TD>Orbital Decay of Double White Dwarfs: Beyond Gravitational-wave Radiation Effects</TD>
<TD>Carvalho, G. A.; Anjos, R. C. dos; Coelho, J. G.; Lobato, R. V.; Malheiro, M.; Marinho, R. M.; Rodriguez, J. F.; Rueda, J. A.; Ruffini, R.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 940, Issue 1, id.90, 9 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...940...90C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...940...20G</TD>
<TD>Active Galactic Nuclei Continuum Reverberation Mapping Based on Zwicky Transient Facility Light Curves</TD>
<TD>Guo, Hengxiao; Barth, Aaron J.; Wang, Shu</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 940, Issue 1, id.20, 20 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...940...20G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...940...19C</TD>
<TD>Perfecting Our Set of Spectrophotometric Standard DA White Dwarfs</TD>
<TD>Calamida, Annalisa; Matheson, Thomas; Olszewski, Edward W.; Saha, Abhijit; Axelrod, Tim; Shanahan, Clare; Holberg, Jay; Points, Sean; Narayan, Gautham; Malanchev, Konstantin; Ridden-Harper, Ryan; Gentile-Fusillo, Nicola; Raddi, Roberto; Bohlin, Ralph; Rest, Armin; Hubeny, Ivan; Deustua, Susana; Mackenty, John; Sabbi, Elena; Stubbs, Christopher W.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 940, Issue 1, id.19, 38 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...940...19C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...939L..33L</TD>
<TD>The Luminosity Function of Tidal Disruption Flares for the ZTF-I Survey</TD>
<TD>Lin, Zheyu; Jiang, Ning; Kong, Xu; Huang, Shifeng; Lin, Zesen; Zhu, Jiazheng; Wang, Yibo</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 939, Issue 2, id.L33, 10 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...939L..33L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...939L..16Z</TD>
<TD>A Transient "Changing-look" Active Galactic Nucleus Resolved on Month Timescales from First-year Sloan Digital Sky Survey V Data</TD>
<TD>Zeltyn, Grisha; Trakhtenbrot, Benny; Eracleous, Michael; Runnoe, Jessie; Trump, Jonathan R.; Stern, Jonathan; Shen, Yue; Hernández-García, Lorena; Bauer, Franz E.; Yang, Qian; Dwelly, Tom; Ricci, Claudio; Green, Paul; Anderson, Scott F.; Assef, Roberto J.; Guolo, Muryel; MacLeod, Chelsea; Davis, Megan C.; Fries, Logan; Gezari, Suvi; Grogin, Norman A.; Homan, David; Koekemoer, Anton M.; Krumpe, Mirko; LaMassa, Stephanie; Liu, Xin; Merloni, Andrea; Martínez-Aldama, Mary Loli; Schneider, Donald P.; Temple, Matthew J.; Brownstein, Joel R.; Ibarra-Medel, Hector; Burke, Jamison; Pellegrino, Craig; Kollmeier, Juna A.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 939, Issue 1, id.L16, 9 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...939L..16Z</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...939L...9H</TD>
<TD>Spectral Evolution of Dark Asteroid Surfaces Induced by Space Weathering over a Decade</TD>
<TD>Hasegawa, Sunao; DeMeo, Francesca E.; Marsset, Michaël; Hanuš, Josef; Avdellidou, Chrysa; Delbo, Marco; Bus, Schelte J.; Hanayama, Hidekazu; Horiuchi, Takashi; Takir, Driss; Jehin, Emmanuël; Ferrais, Marin; Geem, Jooyeon; Im, Myungshin; Seo, Jinguk; Bach, Yoonsoo P.; Jin, Sunho; Ishiguro, Masateru; Kuroda, Daisuke; Binzel, Richard P.; Nakamura, Akiko M.; Yang, Bin; Vernazza, Pierre</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 939, Issue 1, id.L9, 12 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...939L...9H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...939..105B</TD>
<TD>Seven Years of Coordinated Chandra-NuSTAR Observations of SN 2014C Unfold the Extreme Mass-loss History of Its Stellar Progenitor</TD>
<TD>Brethauer, Daniel; Margutti, Raffaella; Milisavljevic, Dan; Bietenholz, Michael F.; Chornock, Ryan; Coppejans, Deanne L.; De Colle, Fabio; Hajela, Aprajita; Terreran, Giacomo; Vargas, Felipe; DeMarchi, Lindsay; Harris, Chelsea; Jacobson-Galán, Wynn V.; Kamble, Atish; Patnaude, Daniel; Stroh, Michael C.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 939, Issue 2, id.105, 30 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...939..105B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...939...24A</TD>
<TD>Detecting Magnetospheric Radio Emission from Giant Exoplanets</TD>
<TD>Ashtari, Reza; Sciola, Anthony; Turner, Jake D.; Stevenson, Kevin</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 939, Issue 1, id.24, 20 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...939...24A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...939...18Y</TD>
<TD>Spectropolarimetry of the Thermonuclear Supernova SN 2021rhu: High Calcium Polarization 79 Days after Peak Luminosity</TD>
<TD>Yang, Yi; Yan, Huirong; Wang, Lifan; Wheeler, J. Craig; Baade, Dietrich; Isaacson, Howard; Cikota, Aleksandar; Maund, Justyn R.; Hoeflich, Peter; Patat, Ferdinando; Giacalone, Steven; Rice, Malena; Tyler, Dakotah B.; Mishra, Divya; Ashall, Chris; Brink, Thomas G.; Filippenko, Alexei V.; Galbany, Llíus; Patra, Kishore C.; Shahbandeh, Melissa; Vasylyev, Sergiy S.; Vinkó, Jozsef</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 939, Issue 1, id.18, 13 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...939...18Y</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...939...11P</TD>
<TD>SALT3-NIR: Taking the Open-source Type Ia Supernova Model to Longer Wavelengths for Next-generation Cosmological Measurements</TD>
<TD>Pierel, J. D. R.; Jones, D. O.; Kenworthy, W. D.; Dai, M.; Kessler, R.; Ashall, C.; Do, A.; Peterson, E. R.; Shappee, B. J.; Siebert, M. R.; Barna, T.; Brink, T. G.; Burke, J.; Calamida, A.; Camacho-Neves, Y.; de Jaeger, T.; Filippenko, A. V.; Foley, R. J.; Galbany, L.; Fox, O. D.; Gomez, S.; Hiramatsu, D.; Hounsell, R.; Howell, D. A.; Jha, S. W.; Kwok, L. A.; Pérez-Fournon, I.; Poidevin, F.; Rest, A.; Rubin, D.; Scolnic, D. M.; Shirley, R.; Strolger, L. G.; Tinyanont, S.; Wang, Q.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 939, Issue 1, id.11, 16 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...939...11P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022Ap&amp;SS.367..108K</TD>
<TD>GLEAM-X J162759.5−523504.3 as a white dwarf pulsar</TD>
<TD>Katz, J. I.</TD>
<TD>Astrophysics and Space Science, Volume 367, Issue 11, article id.108</TD>
<TD>2022-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022Ap&amp;SS.367..108K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022AJ....164..215B</TD>
<TD>Kepler and the Behemoth: Three Mini-Neptunes in a 40 Million Year Old Association</TD>
<TD>Bouma, L. G.; Kerr, R.; Curtis, J. L.; Isaacson, H.; Hillenbrand, L. A.; Howard, A. W.; Kraus, A. L.; Bieryla, A.; Latham, D. W.; Petigura, E. A.; Huber, D.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 164, Issue 5, id.215, 18 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022AJ....164..215B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022AJ....164..202L</TD>
<TD>Extremely Low Mass Ratio Contact Binaries. I. The First Photometric and Spectroscopic Investigations of Ten Systems</TD>
<TD>Li, Kai; Gao, Xiang; Liu, Xin-Yi; Gao, Xing; Li, Ling-Zhi; Chen, Xu; Sun, Guo-You</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 164, Issue 5, id.202, 15 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022AJ....164..202L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022AJ....164..200D</TD>
<TD>Fast Derivation of Contact Binary Parameters for Large Photometric Surveys</TD>
<TD>Ding, Xu; Ji, KaiFan; Li, XuZhi; Xiong, JianPing; Cheng, QiYuan; Wang, JinLiang; Liu, Hui</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 164, Issue 5, id.200, 12 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022AJ....164..200D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022AJ....164..195F</TD>
<TD>DELIGHT: Deep Learning Identification of Galaxy Hosts of Transients using Multiresolution Images</TD>
<TD>Förster, Francisco; Muñoz Arancibia, Alejandra M.; Reyes-Jainaga, Ignacio; Gagliano, Alexander; Britt, Dylan; Cuellar-Carrillo, Sara; Figueroa-Tapia, Felipe; Polzin, Ava; Yousef, Yara; Arredondo, Javier; Rodríguez-Mancini, Diego; Correa-Orellana, Javier; Bayo, Amelia; Bauer, Franz E.; Catelan, Márcio; Cabrera-Vives, Guillermo; Dastidar, Raya; Estévez, Pablo A.; Pignata, Giuliano; Hernández-García, Lorena; Huijse, Pablo; Reyes, Esteban; Sánchez-Sáez, Paula; Ramírez, Mauricio; Grandón, Daniela; Pineda-García, Jonathan; Chabour-Barra, Francisca; Silva-Farfán, Javier</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 164, Issue 5, id.195, 14 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022AJ....164..195F</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022AJ....164..191N</TD>
<TD>Zwicky Transient Facility and Globular Clusters: The Period-Luminosity and Period-Wesenheit Relations for Anomalous Cepheids Supplemented with Large Magellanic Cloud Sample</TD>
<TD>Ngeow, Chow-Choong; Bhardwaj, Anupam; Graham, Matthew J.; Groom, Steven L.; Masci, Frank J.; Riddle, Reed</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 164, Issue 5, id.191, 6 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022AJ....164..191N</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...667A..92O</TD>
<TD>Supernova double-peaked light curves from double-nickel distribution</TD>
<TD>Orellana, Mariana; Bersten, Melina C.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 667, id.A92, 11 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...667A..92O</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...667A..45G</TD>
<TD>Satellite shadows through stellar occultations</TD>
<TD>Groot, Paul J.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 667, id.A45, 3 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...667A..45G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022PhRvD.106h4005W</TD>
<TD>Tests of gravitational-wave birefringence with the open gravitational-wave catalog</TD>
<TD>Wang, Yi-Fan; Brown, Stephanie M.; Shao, Lijing; Zhao, Wen</TD>
<TD>Physical Review D, Volume 106, Issue 8, article id.084005</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022PhRvD.106h4005W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022NewA...9601846A</TD>
<TD>SNAD transient miner: Finding missed transient events in ZTF DR4 using k-D trees</TD>
<TD>Aleo, P. D.; Malanchev, K. L.; Pruzhinskaya, M. V.; Ishida, E. E. O.; Russeil, E.; Kornilov, M. V.; Korolev, V. S.; Sreejith, S.; Volnova, A. A.; Narayan, G. S.</TD>
<TD>New Astronomy, Volume 96, article id. 101846.</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022NewA...9601846A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022Natur.610..467B</TD>
<TD>A dense 0.1-solar-mass star in a 51-minute-orbital-period eclipsing binary</TD>
<TD>Burdge, Kevin B.; El-Badry, Kareem; Marsh, Thomas R.; Rappaport, Saul; Brown, Warren R.; Caiazzo, Ilaria; Chakrabarty, Deepto; Dhillon, V. S.; Fuller, Jim; Gänsicke, Boris T.; Graham, Matthew J.; Kara, Erin; Kulkarni, S. R.; Littlefair, S. P.; Mróz, Przemek; Rodríguez-Gil, Pablo; Roestel, Jan van; Simcoe, Robert A.; Bellm, Eric C.; Drake, Andrew J.; Dekany, Richard G.; Groom, Steven L.; Laher, Russ R.; Masci, Frank J.; Riddle, Reed; Smith, Roger M.; Prince, Thomas A.</TD>
<TD>Nature, Volume 610, Issue 7932, p.467-471</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022Natur.610..467B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.516L..18C</TD>
<TD>Persistence of the blazar state in flat-spectrum radio quasars</TD>
<TD>Chand, Krishan; Gopal-Krishna</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 516, Issue 1, pp.L18-L23</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.516L..18C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.516.2736B</TD>
<TD>Dwarf AGNs from Optical Variability for the Origins of Seeds (DAVOS): insights from the dark energy survey deep fields</TD>
<TD>Burke, Colin J.; Liu, Xin; Shen, Yue; Phadke, Kedar A.; Yang, Qian; Hartley, Will G.; Harrison, Ian; Palmese, Antonella; Guo, Hengxiao; Zhang, Kaiwen; Kron, Richard; Turner, David J.; Giles, Paul A.; Lidman, Christopher; Chen, Yu-Ching; Gruendl, Robert A.; Choi, Ami; Amon, Alexandra; Sheldon, Erin; Aguena, M.; Allam, S.; Andrade-Oliveira, F.; Bacon, D.; Bertin, E.; Brooks, D.; Rosell, A. Carnero; Kind, M. Carrasco; Carretero, J.; Conselice, C.; Costanzi, M.; da Costa, L. N.; Pereira, M. E. S.; Davis, T. M.; De Vicente, J.; Desai, S.; Diehl, H. T.; Everett, S.; Ferrero, I.; Flaugher, B.; García-Bellido, J.; Gaztanaga, E.; Gruen, D.; Gschwend, J.; Gutierrez, G.; Hinton, S. R.; Hollowood, D. L.; Honscheid, K.; Hoyle, B.; James, D. J.; Kuehn, K.; Maia, M. A. G.; Marshall, J. L.; Menanteau, F.; Miquel, R.; Morgan, R.; Paz-Chinchón, F.; Pieres, A.; Malagón, A. A. Plazas; Reil, K.; Romer, A. K.; Sanchez, E.; Schubnell, M.; Serrano, S.; Sevilla-Noarbe, I.; Smith, M.; Suchyta, E.; Tarle, G.; Thomas, D.; To, C.; Varga, T. N.; Wilkinson, R. D.; DES Collaboration</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 516, Issue 2, pp.2736-2756</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.516.2736B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.516.2540K</TD>
<TD>Candidate and confirmed ultrashort period main-sequence binary stars</TD>
<TD>Koen, C.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 516, Issue 2, pp.2540-2553</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.516.2540K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.516.2470Z</TD>
<TD>Estimating sizes of type-2 AGN narrow-line regions from multiple survey spectra - a demonstration</TD>
<TD>Zhang, Xue-Guang; Zhao, YuanBo</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 516, Issue 2, pp.2470-2474</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.516.2470Z</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.516.2455N</TD>
<TD>ASAS-SN follow-up of IceCube high-energy neutrino alerts</TD>
<TD>Necker, Jannis; de Jaeger, Thomas; Stein, Robert; Franckowiak, Anna; Shappee, Benjamin J.; Kowalski, Marek; Kochanek, Christopher S.; Stanek, Krzysztof Z.; Beacom, John F.; Desai, Dhvanil D.; Neumann, Kyle; Jayasinghe, Tharindu; Holoien, T. W. -S.; Thompson, Todd A.; Holmbo, Simon</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 516, Issue 2, pp.2455-2469</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.516.2455N</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.516.2204R</TD>
<TD>Close encounters of stars with stellar-mass black hole binaries</TD>
<TD>Ryu, Taeho; Perna, Rosalba; Wang, Yi-Han</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 516, Issue 2, pp.2204-2217</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.516.2204R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.516.1509K</TD>
<TD>A search for hot subdwarf binaries in data from the Transiting Exoplanet Survey Satellite</TD>
<TD>Krzesinski, J.; Şener, H. T.; Zola, S.; Siwak, M.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 516, Issue 1, pp.1509-1523</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.516.1509K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.516.1339S</TD>
<TD>Emergence of a new H I 21-cm absorption component at z   1.1726 towards the γ-ray blazar PKS 2355-106</TD>
<TD>Srianand, Raghunathan; Gupta, Neeraj; Petitjean, Patrick; Momjian, Emmanuel; Balashev, Sergei A.; Combes, Françoise; Chen, Hsiao-Wen; Krogager, Jens-Kristian; Noterdaeme, Pasquier; Rahmani, Hadi; Baker, Andrew J.; Emig, Kimberly L.; Józsa, Gyula I. G.; Kloeckner, Hans-Rainer; Moodley, Kavilan</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 516, Issue 1, pp.1339-1346</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.516.1339S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.516.1193K</TD>
<TD>The Zwicky Transient Facility phase I sample of hydrogen-rich superluminous supernovae without strong narrow emission lines</TD>
<TD>Kangas, T.; Yan, Lin; Schulze, S.; Fransson, C.; Sollerman, J.; Lunnan, R.; Omand, C. M. B.; Andreoni, I.; Burruss, R.; Chen, T. -W.; Drake, A. J.; Fremling, C.; Gal-Yam, A.; Graham, M. J.; Groom, S. L.; Lezmy, J.; Mahabal, A. A.; Masci, F. J.; Perley, D.; Riddle, R.; Tartaglia, L.; Yao, Y.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 516, Issue 1, pp.1193-1218</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.516.1193K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.516..720K</TD>
<TD>Four new deeply eclipsing white dwarfs in Zwicky Transient Facility</TD>
<TD>Kosakowski, A.; Kilic, M.; Brown, W. R.; Bergeron, P.; Kupfer, T.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 516, Issue 1, pp.720-730</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.516..720K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.516..529C</TD>
<TD>The fall of CSS100217: a tidal disruption-induced low state in an apparently hostless active galactic nucleus</TD>
<TD>Cannizzaro, G.; Levan, A. J.; van Velzen, S.; Brown, G.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 516, Issue 1, pp.529-539</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.516..529C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.515.6007A</TD>
<TD>GRANDMA observations of ZTF/Fink transients during summer 2021</TD>
<TD>Aivazyan, V.; Almualla, M.; Antier, S.; Baransky, A.; Barynova, K.; Basa, S.; Bayard, F.; Beradze, S.; Berezin, D.; Blazek, M.; Boutigny, D.; Boust, D.; Broens, E.; Burkhonov, O.; Cailleau, A.; Christensen, N.; Cejudo, D.; Coleiro, A.; Coughlin, M. W.; Datashvili, D.; Dietrich, T.; Dolon, F.; Ducoin, J. -G.; Duverne, P. -A.; Marchal-Duval, G.; Galdies, C.; Granier, L.; Godunova, V.; Gokuldass, P.; Eggenstein, H. B.; Freeberg, M.; Hello, P.; Inasaridze, R.; Ishida, E. E. O.; Jaquiery, P.; Kann, D. A.; Kapanadze, G.; Karpov, S.; Kiendrebeogo, R. W.; Klotz, A.; Kneip, R.; Kochiashvili, N.; Kou, W.; Kugel, F.; Lachaud, C.; Leonini, S.; Leroy, A.; Leroy, N.; Van Su, A. Le; Marchais, D.; Mašek, M.; Midavaine, T.; Möller, A.; Morris, D.; Natsvlishvili, R.; Navarete, F.; Noysena, K.; Nissanke, S.; Noonan, K.; Orange, N. B.; Peloton, J.; Popowicz, A.; Pradier, T.; Prouza, M.; Raaijmakers, G.; Rajabov, Y.; Richmond, M.; Romanyuk, Ya; Rousselot, L.; Sadibekova, T.; Serrau, M.; Sokoliuk, O.; Song, X.; Simon, A.; Stachie, C.; Taylor, A.; Tillayev, Y.; Turpin, D.; Vardosanidze, M.; Vlieghe, J.; Melo, I. Tosta e.; Wang, X. F.; Zhu, J.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 515, Issue 4, pp.6007-6022</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.515.6007A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.515.5905C</TD>
<TD>Photometric variability in star-forming galaxies as evidence for low-mass AGN and a precursor to quenching</TD>
<TD>Cleland, Cressida; McGee, Sean L.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 515, Issue 4, pp.5905-5913</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.515.5905C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.515.5682Y</TD>
<TD>The moving mirror model for fast radio bursts</TD>
<TD>Yalinewich, Almog; Pen, Ue-Li</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 515, Issue 4, pp.5682-5688</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.515.5682Y</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.515.5604N</TD>
<TD>Systematic light-curve modelling of TDEs: statistical differences between the spectroscopic classes</TD>
<TD>Nicholl, Matt; Lanning, Daniel; Ramsden, Paige; Mockler, Brenna; Lawrence, Andy; Short, Phil; Ridley, Evan J.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 515, Issue 4, pp.5604-5616</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.515.5604N</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.515.5198Y</TD>
<TD>An X-ray view of the ambiguous nuclear transient AT2019pev</TD>
<TD>Yu, Zhefu; Kochanek, C. S.; Mathur, S.; Auchettl, K.; Grupe, D.; Holoien, T. W. -S.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 515, Issue 4, pp.5198-5210</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.515.5198Y</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022JATIS...8d4003C</TD>
<TD>All-sky Medium Energy Gamma-ray Observatory eXplorer mission concept</TD>
<TD>Caputo, Regina; Ajello, Marco; Kierans, Carolyn A.; Perkins, Jeremy S.; Racusin, Judith L.; Baldini, Luca; Baring, Matthew G.; Bissaldi, Elisabetta; Burns, Eric; Cannady, Nicholas; Charles, Eric; da Silva, Rui M. Curado; Fang, Ke; Fleischhack, Henrike; Fryer, Chris; Fukazawa, Yasushi; Grove, J. Eric; Hartmann, Dieter; Howell, Eric J.; Jadhav, Manoj; Karwin, Christopher M.; Kocevski, Daniel; Kurahashi, Naoko; Latronico, Luca; Lewis, Tiffany R.; Leys, Richard; Lien, Amy; Marcotulli, Lea; Martinez-Castellanos, Israel; Mazziotta, Mario Nicola; McEnery, Julie; Metcalfe, Jessica; Murase, Kohta; Negro, Michela; Parker, Lucas; Phlips, Bernard; Prescod-Weinstein, Chanda; Razzaque, Soebur; Shawhan, Peter S.; Sheng, Yong; Shutt, Tom A.; Shy, Daniel; Sleator, Clio; Steinhebel, Amanda L.; Striebig, Nicolas; Suda, Yusuke; Tak, Donggeun; Tajima, Hiro; Valverde, Janeth; Venters, Tonia M.; Wadiasingh, Zorawar; Woolf, Richard S.; Wulf, Eric A.; Zhang, Haocheng; Zoglauer, Andreas</TD>
<TD>Journal of Astronomical Telescopes, Instruments, and Systems, Volume 8, id. 044003 (2022).</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022JATIS...8d4003C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJS..262...49K</TD>
<TD>The LSST Era of Supermassive Black Hole Accretion Disk Reverberation Mapping</TD>
<TD>Kovačević, Andjelka B.; Radović, Viktor; Ilić, Dragana; Popović, Luka Č.; Assef, Roberto J.; Sánchez-Sáez, Paula; Nikutta, Robert; Raiteri, Claudia M.; Yoon, Ilsang; Homayouni, Yasaman; Li, Yan-Rong; Caplar, Neven; Czerny, Bozena; Panda, Swayamtrupta; Ricci, Claudio; Jankov, Isidora; Landt, Hermine; Wolf, Christian; Kovačević-Dojčinović, Jelena; Lakićević, Maša; Savić, Đorđe V.; Vince, Oliver; Simić, Saša; Čvorović-Hajdinjak, Iva; Marčeta-Mandić, Sladjana</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 262, Issue 2, id.49, 37 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJS..262...49K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...938..147Z</TD>
<TD>Kilonova and Optical Afterglow from Binary Neutron Star Mergers. I. Luminosity Function and Color Evolution</TD>
<TD>Zhu, Jin-Ping; Yang, Yuan-Pei; Zhang, Bing; Gao, He; Yu, Yun-Wei</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 938, Issue 2, id.147, 13 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...938..147Z</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...938..113S</TD>
<TD>The Pantheon+ Analysis: The Full Data Set and Light-curve Release</TD>
<TD>Scolnic, Dan; Brout, Dillon; Carr, Anthony; Riess, Adam G.; Davis, Tamara M.; Dwomoh, Arianna; Jones, David O.; Ali, Noor; Charvu, Pranav; Chen, Rebecca; Peterson, Erik R.; Popovic, Brodie; Rose, Benjamin M.; Wood, Charlotte M.; Brown, Peter J.; Chambers, Ken; Coulter, David A.; Dettman, Kyle G.; Dimitriadis, Georgios; Filippenko, Alexei V.; Foley, Ryan J.; Jha, Saurabh W.; Kilpatrick, Charles D.; Kirshner, Robert P.; Pan, Yen-Chen; Rest, Armin; Rojas-Bravo, Cesar; Siebert, Matthew R.; Stahl, Benjamin E.; Zheng, WeiKang</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 938, Issue 2, id.113, 15 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...938..113S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...938..111B</TD>
<TD>The Pantheon+ Analysis: SuperCal-fragilistic Cross Calibration, Retrained SALT2 Light-curve Model, and Calibration Systematic Uncertainty</TD>
<TD>Brout, Dillon; Taylor, Georgie; Scolnic, Dan; Wood, Charlotte M.; Rose, Benjamin M.; Vincenzi, Maria; Dwomoh, Arianna; Lidman, Christopher; Riess, Adam; Ali, Noor; Qu, Helen; Dai, Mi</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 938, Issue 2, id.111, 21 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...938..111B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...938..110B</TD>
<TD>The Pantheon+ Analysis: Cosmological Constraints</TD>
<TD>Brout, Dillon; Scolnic, Dan; Popovic, Brodie; Riess, Adam G.; Carr, Anthony; Zuntz, Joe; Kessler, Rick; Davis, Tamara M.; Hinton, Samuel; Jones, David; Kenworthy, W. D'Arcy; Peterson, Erik R.; Said, Khaled; Taylor, Georgie; Ali, Noor; Armstrong, Patrick; Charvu, Pranav; Dwomoh, Arianna; Meldorf, Cole; Palmese, Antonella; Qu, Helen; Rose, Benjamin M.; Sanchez, Bruno; Stubbs, Christopher W.; Vincenzi, Maria; Wood, Charlotte M.; Brown, Peter J.; Chen, Rebecca; Chambers, Ken; Coulter, David A.; Dai, Mi; Dimitriadis, Georgios; Filippenko, Alexei V.; Foley, Ryan J.; Jha, Saurabh W.; Kelsey, Lisa; Kirshner, Robert P.; Möller, Anais; Muir, Jessie; Nadathur, Seshadri; Pan, Yen-Chen; Rest, Armin; Rojas-Bravo, Cesar; Sako, Masao; Siebert, Matthew R.; Smith, Mat; Stahl, Benjamin E.; Wiseman, Phil</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 938, Issue 2, id.110, 24 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...938..110B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...938...85H</TD>
<TD>Cosmological Fast Optical Transients with the Zwicky Transient Facility: A Search for Dirty Fireballs</TD>
<TD>Ho, Anna Y. Q.; Perley, Daniel A.; Yao, Yuhan; Svinkin, Dmitry; de Ugarte Postigo, A.; Perley, R. A.; Kann, D. Alexander; Burns, Eric; Andreoni, Igor; Bellm, Eric C.; Bissaldi, Elisabetta; Bloom, Joshua S.; Brink, Thomas G.; Dekany, Richard; Drake, Andrew J.; Agüí Fernández, José Feliciano; Filippenko, Alexei V.; Frederiks, Dmitry; Graham, Matthew J.; Hristov, Boyan A.; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Kulkarni, S. R.; Kumar, Harsh; Laher, Russ R.; Lysenko, Alexandra L.; Mailyan, Bagrat; Malacaria, Christian; Miller, A. A.; Poolakkil, S.; Riddle, Reed; Ridnaia, Anna; Rusholme, Ben; Savchenko, Volodymyr; Sollerman, Jesper; Thöne, Christina; Tsvetkova, Anastasia; Ulanov, Mikhail; von Kienlin, Andreas</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 938, Issue 1, id.85, 27 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...938...85H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...938...84D</TD>
<TD>Radio Analysis of SN2004C Reveals an Unusual CSM Density Profile as a Harbinger of Core Collapse</TD>
<TD>DeMarchi, Lindsay; Margutti, R.; Dittman, J.; Brunthaler, A.; Milisavljevic, D.; Bietenholz, Michael F.; Stauffer, C.; Brethauer, D.; Coppejans, D.; Auchettl, K.; Alexander, K. D.; Kilpatrick, C. D.; Bright, Joe S.; Kelley, L. Z.; Stroh, Michael C.; Jacobson-Galán, W. V.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 938, Issue 1, id.84, 21 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...938...84D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...938...78L</TD>
<TD>Binaries with Possible Compact Components Discovered from the LAMOST Time-domain Survey of Four K2 Plates</TD>
<TD>Li, Xue; Wang, Song; Zhao, Xinlin; Bai, Zhongrui; Yuan, Hailong; Zhang, Haotong; Liu, Jifeng</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 938, Issue 1, id.78, 20 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...938...78L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...938...73P</TD>
<TD>The Diverse Properties of Type Icn Supernovae Point to Multiple Progenitor Channels</TD>
<TD>Pellegrino, C.; Howell, D. A.; Terreran, G.; Arcavi, I.; Bostroem, K. A.; Brown, P. J.; Burke, J.; Dong, Y.; Gilkis, A.; Hiramatsu, D.; Hosseinzadeh, G.; McCully, C.; Modjaz, M.; Newsome, M.; Gonzalez, E. Padilla; Pritchard, T. A.; Sand, D. J.; Valenti, S.; Williamson, M.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 938, Issue 1, id.73, 18 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...938...73P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...938...52K</TD>
<TD>Probe for Type Ia Supernova Progenitor in Decihertz Gravitational Wave Astronomy</TD>
<TD>Kinugawa, Tomoya; Takeda, Hiroki; Tanikawa, Ataru; Yamaguchi, Hiroya</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 938, Issue 1, id.52, 9 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...938...52K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...938...46A</TD>
<TD>Informing the Cataclysmic Variable Sequence from Gaia Data: The Orbital-period-Color-Absolute-magnitude Relationship</TD>
<TD>Abrahams, Ellianna S.; Bloom, Joshua S.; Szkody, Paula; Rix, Hans-Walter; Mowlavi, Nami</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 938, Issue 1, id.46, 14 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...938...46A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...938...43Z</TD>
<TD>Transient Radio Emission from Low-redshift Galaxies at z &lt; 0.3 Revealed by the VLASS and FIRST Surveys</TD>
<TD>Zhang, Fabao; Shu, Xinwen; Sun, Luming; Yang, Lei; Jiang, Ning; Dou, Liming; Wang, Jianguo; Wang, Tinggui</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 938, Issue 1, id.43, 19 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...938...43Z</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...938...37S</TD>
<TD>Variable Star Classification with a Multiple-input Neural Network</TD>
<TD>Szklenár, T.; Bódi, A.; Tarczay-Nehéz, D.; Vida, K.; Mező, Gy.; Szabó, R.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 938, Issue 1, id.37, 14 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...938...37S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...938...28C</TD>
<TD>A Mildly Relativistic Outflow Launched Two Years after Disruption in Tidal Disruption Event AT2018hyz</TD>
<TD>Cendes, Y.; Berger, E.; Alexander, K. D.; Gomez, S.; Hajela, A.; Chornock, R.; Laskar, T.; Margutti, R.; Metzger, B.; Bietenholz, M. F.; Brethauer, D.; Wieringa, M. H.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 938, Issue 1, id.28, 14 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...938...28C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...938....9Y</TD>
<TD>MEGASIM: Lifetimes and Resonances of Earth Trojan Asteroids-The Death of Primordial ETAs?</TD>
<TD>Yeager, Travis; Golovich, Nathan</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 938, Issue 1, id.9, 13 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...938....9Y</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...937L..28T</TD>
<TD>Dynamical Unification of Tidal Disruption Events</TD>
<TD>Thomsen, Lars L.; Kwan, Tom M.; Dai, Lixin; Wu, Samantha C.; Roth, Nathaniel; Ramirez-Ruiz, Enrico</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 937, Issue 2, id.L28, 16 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...937L..28T</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...937..108Y</TD>
<TD>Identifying High-energy Neutrino Transients by Neutrino Multiplet-triggered Follow-ups</TD>
<TD>Yoshida, Shigeru; Murase, Kohta; Tanaka, Masaomi; Shimizu, Nobuhiro; Ishihara, Aya</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 937, Issue 2, id.108, 11 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...937..108Y</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022AJ....164..168S</TD>
<TD>A Deep and Wide Twilight Survey for Asteroids Interior to Earth and Venus</TD>
<TD>Sheppard, Scott S.; Tholen, David J.; Pokorný, Petr; Micheli, Marco; Dell'Antonio, Ian; Fu, Shenming; Trujillo, Chadwick A.; Beaton, Rachael; Carlsten, Scott; Drlica-Wagner, Alex; Martínez-Vázquez, Clara; Mau, Sidney; Santana-Ros, Toni; Santana-Silva, Luidhy; Sifón, Cristóbal; Simha, Sunil; Thirouin, Audrey; Trilling, David; Vivas, A. Katherina; Zenteno, Alfredo</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 164, Issue 4, id.168, 15 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022AJ....164..168S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022AJ....164..167M</TD>
<TD>Implications for the Collisional Strength of Jupiter Trojans from the Eurybates Family</TD>
<TD>Marschall, Raphael; Nesvorný, David; Deienno, Rogerio; Wong, Ian; Levison, Harold F.; Bottke, William F.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 164, Issue 4, id.167, 15 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022AJ....164..167M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022AJ....164..166N</TD>
<TD>Zwicky Transient Facility and Globular Clusters: Calibration of the gr-band Absolute Magnitudes for the Yellow Post-asymptotic-giant-branch Stars</TD>
<TD>Ngeow, Chow-Choong; Bhardwaj, Anupam; Reiley, Daniel; Laher, Russ R.; Purdum, Josiah; Rusholme, Ben</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 164, Issue 4, id.166, 4 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022AJ....164..166N</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022AJ....164..162S</TD>
<TD>Double-mode Cepheids from the Zwicky Transient Facility Survey</TD>
<TD>Shah, Vishwangi; Chen, Xiaodian; de Grijs, Richard</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 164, Issue 4, id.162, 8 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022AJ....164..162S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022AJ....164..154N</TD>
<TD>Zwicky Transient Facility and Globular Clusters: The Period-Luminosity and Period-Wesenheit Relations for Type II Cepheids</TD>
<TD>Ngeow, Chow-Choong; Bhardwaj, Anupam; Henderson, Jing-Yi; Graham, Matthew J.; Laher, Russ R.; Medford, Michael S.; Purdum, Josiah; Rusholme, Ben</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 164, Issue 4, id.154, 11 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022AJ....164..154N</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022AJ....164..131W</TD>
<TD>The Rapid Rotation of the Strongly Magnetic Ultramassive White Dwarf EGGR 156</TD>
<TD>Williams, Kurtis A.; Hermes, J. J.; Vanderbosch, Zachary P.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 164, Issue 4, id.131, 8 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022AJ....164..131W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;C....4100652C</TD>
<TD>Impact simulation of Starlink satellites on astronomical observation using worldwide telescope</TD>
<TD>Cui, Z.; Xu, Y.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy and Computing, Volume 41, article id. 100652.</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;C....4100652C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...666A.176A</TD>
<TD>Inferring properties of dust in supernovae with neural networks</TD>
<TD>Ansari, Zoe; Gall, Christa; Wesson, Roger; Krause, Oswin</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 666, id.A176, 24 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...666A.176A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...666A.116A</TD>
<TD>Asteroid spin-states of a 4 Gyr collisional family</TD>
<TD>Athanasopoulos, D.; Hanuš, J.; Avdellidou, C.; Bonamico, R.; Delbo, M.; Conjat, M.; Ferrero, A.; Gazeas, K.; Rivet, J. P.; Sioulas, N.; van Belle, G.; Antonini, P.; Audejean, M.; Behrend, R.; Bernasconi, L.; Brinsfield, J. W.; Brouillard, S.; Brunetto, L.; Fauvaud, M.; Fauvaud, S.; Gonzalez, R.; Higgins, D.; Holoien, T. W. -S.; Kober, G.; Koff, R. A.; Kryszczynska, A.; Livet, F.; Marciniak, A.; Oey, J.; Pejcha, O.; Rives, J. J.; Roy, R.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 666, id.A116, 19 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...666A.116A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...666A..88X</TD>
<TD>Trojan asteroids and the co-orbital dust ring of Venus</TD>
<TD>Xu, Yang-Bo; Zhou, Lei; Lhotka, Christoph; Zhou, Li-Yong; Ip, Wing-Huen</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 666, id.A88, 10 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...666A..88X</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...666A..79F</TD>
<TD>SN 2019zrk, a bright SN 2009ip analog with a precursor</TD>
<TD>Fransson, Claes; Sollerman, Jesper; Strotjohann, Nora L.; Yang, Sheng; Schulze, Steve; Barbarino, Cristina; Kool, Erik C.; Ofek, Eran O.; Crellin-Quick, Arien; De, Kishalay; Drake, Andrew J.; Fremling, Christoffer; Gal-Yam, Avishay; Ho, Anna Y. Q.; Kasliwal, Mansi M.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 666, id.A79, 15 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...666A..79F</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...666A..67P</TD>
<TD>Hubble constant and nuclear equation of state from kilonova spectro-photometric light curves</TD>
<TD>Pérez-García, M. A.; Izzo, L.; Barba-González, D.; Bulla, M.; Sagués-Carracedo, A.; Pérez, E.; Albertus, C.; Dhawan, S.; Prada, F.; Agnello, A.; Angus, C. R.; Bruun, S. H.; del Burgo, C.; Dominguez-Tagle, C.; Gall, C.; Goobar, A.; Hjorth, J.; Jones, D.; López-Sánchez, A. R.; Sollerman, J.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 666, id.A67, 20 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...666A..67P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...666A..13G</TD>
<TD>The Hubble constant from two sibling Type Ia supernovae in the nearby galaxy NGC 4414: SN 1974G and SN 2021J</TD>
<TD>Gallego-Cano, Eulalia; Izzo, Luca; Dominguez-Tagle, Carlos; Prada, Francisco; Pérez, Enrique; Khetan, Nandita; Jang, In Sung</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 666, id.A13, 10 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...666A..13G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...666A...6W</TD>
<TD>An elliptical accretion disk following the tidal disruption event AT 2020zso</TD>
<TD>Wevers, T.; Nicholl, M.; Guolo, M.; Charalampopoulos, P.; Gromadzki, M.; Reynolds, T. M.; Kankare, E.; Leloudas, G.; Anderson, J. P.; Arcavi, I.; Cannizzaro, G.; Chen, T. -W.; Ihanec, N.; Inserra, C.; Gutiérrez, C. P.; Jonker, P. G.; Lawrence, A.; Magee, M. R.; Müller-Bravo, T. E.; Onori, F.; Ridley, E.; Schulze, S.; Short, P.; Hiramatsu, D.; Newsome, M.; Terwel, J. H.; Yang, S.; Young, D.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 666, id.A6, 30 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...666A...6W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...666A...4K</TD>
<TD>Validation and atmospheric exploration of the sub-Neptune TOI-2136b around a nearby M3 dwarf</TD>
<TD>Kawauchi, K.; Murgas, F.; Palle, E.; Narita, N.; Fukui, A.; Hirano, T.; Parviainen, H.; Ishikawa, H. T.; Watanabe, N.; Esparaza-Borges, E.; Kuzuhara, M.; Orell-Miquel, J.; Krishnamurthy, V.; Mori, M.; Kagetani, T.; Zou, Y.; Isogai, K.; Livingston, J. H.; Howell, S. B.; Crouzet, N.; de Leon, J. P.; Kimura, T.; Kodama, T.; Korth, J.; Kurita, S.; Laza-Ramos, A.; Luque, R.; Madrigal-Aguado, A.; Miyakawa, K.; Morello, G.; Nishiumi, T.; Rodríguez, G. E. F.; Sánchez-Benavente, M.; Stangret, M.; Teng, H.; Terada, Y.; Gnilka, C. L.; Guerrero, N.; Harakawa, H.; Hodapp, K.; Hori, Y.; Ikoma, M.; Jacobson, S.; Konishi, M.; Kotani, T.; Kudo, T.; Kurokowa, T.; Kusakabe, N.; Nishikawa, J.; Omiya, M.; Serizawa, T.; Tamura, M.; Ueda, A.; Vievard, S.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 666, id.A4, 19 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...666A...4K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022Univ....8..493C</TD>
<TD>Gap Transients Interacting with Circumstellar Medium</TD>
<TD>Cai, Yongzhi; Reguitti, Andrea; Valerin, Giorgio; Wang, Xiaofeng</TD>
<TD>Universe, vol. 8, issue 10, p. 493</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022Univ....8..493C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022Tectp.83929525L</TD>
<TD>Velocity and azimuthal anisotropy structures beneath the Dianzhong Block and its vicinity, SE Tibetan Plateau, revealed by eikonal equation-based traveltime tomography</TD>
<TD>Liu, Shaolin; Chang, Kai; Yang, Dinghui; Xu, Xiwei; Wang, Wenshuai; Yang, Shuxin; Li, Mengyang</TD>
<TD>Tectonophysics, Volume 839, article id. 229525.</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022Tectp.83929525L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022RAA....22i5017M</TD>
<TD>A Photometric Study of Two Contact Binaries: CRTS J025408.1+265957 and CRTS J012111.1+272933</TD>
<TD>Ma, Shuo; Liu, Jin-Zhong; Zhang, Yu; Hu, Qingshun; Lü, Guo-Liang</TD>
<TD>Research in Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 22, Issue 9, id.095017, 16 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022RAA....22i5017M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022PhRvD.106f4056S</TD>
<TD>Observing GW190521-like binary black holes and their environment with LISA</TD>
<TD>Sberna, Laura; Babak, Stanislav; Marsat, Sylvain; Caputo, Andrea; Cusin, Giulia; Toubiana, Alexandre; Barausse, Enrico; Caprini, Chiara; Dal Canton, Tito; Sesana, Alberto; Tamanini, Nicola</TD>
<TD>Physical Review D, Volume 106, Issue 6, article id.064056</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022PhRvD.106f4056S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022PhRvD.106f3530P</TD>
<TD>Determining the Hubble constant without the sound horizon: A 3.6 % constraint on H&lt;SUB&gt;0&lt;/SUB&gt; from galaxy surveys, CMB lensing, and supernovae</TD>
<TD>Philcox, Oliver H. E.; Farren, Gerrit S.; Sherwin, Blake D.; Baxter, Eric J.; Brout, Dillon J.</TD>
<TD>Physical Review D, Volume 106, Issue 6, article id.063530</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022PhRvD.106f3530P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022PASP..134i4501A</TD>
<TD>Identifying Transient Candidates in the Dark Energy Survey Using Convolutional Neural Networks</TD>
<TD>Ayyar, Venkitesh; Knop, Robert; Awbrey, Autumn; Andersen, Alexis; Nugent, Peter</TD>
<TD>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 134, Issue 1039, id.094501, 14 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022PASP..134i4501A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022PASP..134i4201C</TD>
<TD>Optical Time-series Photometry of the Symbiotic Nova V1835 Aquilae</TD>
<TD>Caddy, Robert V.; Layden, Andrew C.; Reichart, Daniel E.; Haislip, Joshua B.; Kouprianov, Vladimir V.; Ivarsen, Kevin M.; Moore, Justin P.; LaCluyze, Aaron P.; Linder, Tyler R.; Nysewander, Melissa C.</TD>
<TD>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 134, Issue 1039, id.094201, 13 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022PASP..134i4201C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022NatAs...6.1203Y</TD>
<TD>A dynamically discovered and characterized non-accreting neutron star-M dwarf binary candidate</TD>
<TD>Yi, Tuan; Gu, Wei-Min; Zhang, Zhi-Xiang; Zheng, Ling-Lin; Sun, Mouyuan; Wang, Junfeng; Bai, Zhongrui; Wang, Pei; Wu, Jianfeng; Bai, Yu; Wang, Song; Zhang, Haotong; Dong, Yize; Shao, Yong; Li, Xiang-Dong; Zhang, Jia; Huang, Yang; Yang, Fan; Yu, Qingzheng; Mu, Hui-Jun; Fu, Jin-Bo; Qi, Senyu; Guo, Jing; Fang, Xuan; Zheng, Chuanjie; Li, Chun-Qian; Shi, Jian-Rong; Chen, Huanyang; Liu, Jifeng</TD>
<TD>Nature Astronomy, Volume 6, p. 1203-1212</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022NatAs...6.1203Y</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.515.3370L</TD>
<TD>A Roche lobe-filling hot subdwarf and white dwarf binary: possible detection of an ejected common envelope</TD>
<TD>Li, Jiangdan; Onken, Christopher A.; Wolf, Christian; Németh, Péter; Bessell, Mike; Li, Zhenwei; Zhang, Xiaobin; Li, Jiao; Wang, Luqian; Li, Lifang; Luo, Yangping; Chen, Hailiang; Ji, Kaifan; Chen, Xuefei; Han, Zhanwen</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 515, Issue 3, pp.3370-3382</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.515.3370L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.515.2496P</TD>
<TD>Discovery and analysis of three magnetic hot subdwarf stars: evidence for merger-induced magnetic fields</TD>
<TD>Pelisoli, Ingrid; Dorsch, M.; Heber, U.; Gänsicke, B.; Geier, S.; Kupfer, T.; Németh, P.; Scaringi, S.; Schaffenroth, V.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 515, Issue 2, pp.2496-2510</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.515.2496P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.515.1774N</TD>
<TD>Photometric and spectroscopic study of the burst-like brightening of two Gaia-alerted young stellar objects</TD>
<TD>Nagy, Zsófia; Ábrahám, Péter; Kóspál, Ágnes; Park, Sunkyung; Siwak, Michał; Cruz-Sáenz de Miera, Fernando; Fiorellino, Eleonora; García-Álvarez, David; Szabó, Zsófia Marianna; Antoniucci, Simone; Giannini, Teresa; Giunta, Alessio; Kriskovics, Levente; Kun, Mária; Marton, Gábor; Moór, Attila; Nisini, Brunella; Pál, Andras; Szabados, László; Zieliński, Paweł; Wyrzykowski, Łukasz</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 515, Issue 2, pp.1774-1787</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.515.1774N</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.515.1699S</TD>
<TD>Radio emission from simulated tidal disruption events</TD>
<TD>Spaulding, Alexandra; Chang, Philip</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 515, Issue 2, pp.1699-1704</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.515.1699S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.515.1380S</TD>
<TD>Discovering vanishing objects in POSS I red images using the Virtual Observatory</TD>
<TD>Solano, Enrique; Villarroel, B.; Rodrigo, C.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 515, Issue 1, pp.1380-1391</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.515.1380S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.515.1228K</TD>
<TD>A gap in the double white dwarf separation distribution caused by the common-envelope evolution: astrometric evidence from Gaia</TD>
<TD>Korol, Valeriya; Belokurov, Vasily; Toonen, Silvia</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 515, Issue 1, pp.1228-1246</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.515.1228K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.515.1146R</TD>
<TD>The bulge masses of TDE host galaxies and their scaling with black hole mass</TD>
<TD>Ramsden, Paige; Lanning, Daniel; Nicholl, Matt; McGee, Sean L.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 515, Issue 1, pp.1146-1157</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.515.1146R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.515..555B</TD>
<TD>Robust features of off-axis gamma-ray burst afterglow light curves</TD>
<TD>Beniamini, Paz; Gill, Ramandeep; Granot, Jonathan</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 515, Issue 1, pp.555-570</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.515..555B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.515..286G</TD>
<TD>Confronting double-detonation sub-Chandrasekhar models with the low-luminosity suppression of Type Ia supernovae</TD>
<TD>Ghosh, Arka; Kushnir, Doron</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 515, Issue 1, pp.286-292</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.515..286G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.515..138P</TD>
<TD>Spectropolarimetry of the tidal disruption event AT 2019qiz: a quasi-spherical reprocessing layer</TD>
<TD>Patra, Kishore C.; Lu, Wenbin; Brink, Thomas G.; Yang, Yi; Filippenko, Alexei V.; Vasylyev, Sergiy S.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 515, Issue 1, pp.138-145</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.515..138P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.515..110K</TD>
<TD>Multiple giant eruptions and X-ray emission in the recoiling AGN/LBV candidate SDSS1133</TD>
<TD>Kokubo, Mitsuru</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 515, Issue 1, pp.110-137</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.515..110K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022AstL...48..530B</TD>
<TD>SRGe J214919.3+673634—a Candidate for AM Her Variables Discovered by the eROSITA Telescope onboard the Spectrum-Roentgen-Gamma Orbital Observatory</TD>
<TD>Bikmaev, I. F.; Kolbin, A. I.; Shimansky, V. V.; Khamitov, I. M.; Irtuganov, E. N.; Nikolaeva, E. A.; Sakhibullin, N. A.; Gumerov, R. I.; Burenin, R. A.; Gilfanov, M. R.; Zaznobin, I. A.; Krivonos, R. A.; Medvedev, P. S.; Meshcheryakov, A. V.; Sazonov, S. Yu.; Sunyaev, R. A.; Khorunzhev, G. A.; Moiseev, A. V.; Malygin, E. A.; Shablovinskaya, E. S.; Zheltoukhov, S. G.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy Letters, Volume 48, Issue 9, p.530-541</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022AstL...48..530B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJS..262...14B</TD>
<TD>Monitoring AGNs with Hβ Asymmetry. III. Long-term Reverberation Mapping Results of 15 Palomar-Green Quasars</TD>
<TD>Bao, Dong-Wei; Brotherton, Michael S.; Du, Pu; McLane, Jacob N.; Zastrocky, T. E.; Olson, Kianna A.; Fang, Feng-Na; Zhai, Shuo; Huang, Zheng-Peng; Wang, Kai; Zhao, Bi-Xuan; Li, Sha-Sha; Yang, Sen; Chen, Yong-Jie; Liu, Jun-Rong; Yao, Zhu-Heng; Peng, Yue-Chang; Guo, Wei-Jian; Songsheng, Yu-Yang; Li, Yan-Rong; Jiang, Bo-Wei; Kasper, David H.; Chick, William T.; Nguyen, My L.; Maithil, Jaya; Kobulnicky, H. A.; Dale, D. A.; Hand, Derek; Adelman, C.; Carter, Z.; Murphree, A. M.; Oeur, M.; Schonsberg, S.; Roth, T.; Winkler, Hartmut; Marziani, Paola; D'Onofrio, Mauro; Hu, Chen; Xiao, Ming; Xue, Suijian; Czerny, Bożena; Aceituno, Jesús; Ho, Luis C.; Bai, Jin-Ming; Wang, Jian-Min; MAHA Collaboration</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 262, Issue 1, id.14, 31 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJS..262...14B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJS..262...12K</TD>
<TD>A Bayesian Analysis of Physical Parameters for 783 Kepler Close Binaries: Extreme-mass-ratio Systems and a New Mass Ratio versus Period Lower Limit</TD>
<TD>Kobulnicky, Henry A.; Molnar, Lawrence A.; Cook, Evan M.; Henderson, Lauren E.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 262, Issue 1, id.12, 51 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJS..262...12K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...937L..12M</TD>
<TD>Cooling Envelope Model for Tidal Disruption Events</TD>
<TD>Metzger, Brian D.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 937, Issue 1, id.L12, 11 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...937L..12M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...937L...2C</TD>
<TD>Migratory Outbursting Quasi-Hilda Object 282P/(323137) 2003 BM80</TD>
<TD>Chandler, Colin Orion; Oldroyd, William J.; Trujillo, Chadwick A.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 937, Issue 1, id.L2, 13 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...937L...2C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...937...13H</TD>
<TD>Photometrically Classified Superluminous Supernovae from the Pan-STARRS1 Medium Deep Survey: A Case Study for Science with Machine-learning-based Classification</TD>
<TD>Hsu, Brian; Hosseinzadeh, Griffin; Villar, V. Ashley; Berger, Edo</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 937, Issue 1, id.13, 11 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...937...13H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...937....8Y</TD>
<TD>The Tidal Disruption Event AT2021ehb: Evidence of Relativistic Disk Reflection, and Rapid Evolution of the Disk-Corona System</TD>
<TD>Yao, Yuhan; Lu, Wenbin; Guolo, Muryel; Pasham, Dheeraj R.; Gezari, Suvi; Gilfanov, Marat; Gendreau, Keith C.; Harrison, Fiona; Cenko, S. Bradley; Kulkarni, S. R.; Miller, Jon M.; Walton, Dominic J.; García, Javier A.; van Velzen, Sjoert; Alexander, Kate D.; Miller-Jones, James C. A.; Nicholl, Matt; Hammerstein, Erica; Medvedev, Pavel; Stern, Daniel; Ravi, Vikram; Sunyaev, R.; Bloom, Joshua S.; Graham, Matthew J.; Kool, Erik C.; Mahabal, Ashish A.; Masci, Frank J.; Purdum, Josiah; Rusholme, Ben; Sharma, Yashvi; Smith, Roger; Sollerman, Jesper</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 937, Issue 1, id.8, 25 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...937....8Y</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...937....5S</TD>
<TD>Radio Nebulae from Hyperaccreting X-Ray Binaries as Common-envelope Precursors and Persistent Counterparts of Fast Radio Bursts</TD>
<TD>Sridhar, Navin; Metzger, Brian D.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 937, Issue 1, id.5, 22 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...937....5S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...937....3S</TD>
<TD>A Mid-infrared Flare in the Seyfert Galaxy NGC 3786: A Changing-look Event Triggered by an Obscured Tidal Disruption Event?</TD>
<TD>Son, Suyeon; Kim, Minjin; Ho, Luis C.; Kim, Dohyeong; Kim, Taehyun</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 937, Issue 1, id.3, 9 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...937....3S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...936..157H</TD>
<TD>Image Subtraction in Fourier Space</TD>
<TD>Hu, Lei; Wang, Lifan; Chen, Xingzhuo; Yang, Jiawen</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 936, Issue 2, id.157, 19 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...936..157H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...936..134T</TD>
<TD>Searching for Cataclysmic Variable Stars in Unidentified X-Ray Sources</TD>
<TD>Takata, J.; Wang, X. F.; Kong, A. K. H.; Mao, J.; Hou, X.; Hu, C. -P.; Lin, L. C. -C.; Li, K. L.; Hui, C. Y.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 936, Issue 2, id.134, 17 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...936..134T</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...936..117R</TD>
<TD>The Rate and Spatial Distribution of Novae in M31 as Determined by a 20 Year Survey</TD>
<TD>Rector, Travis A.; Shafter, Allen W.; Burris, William A.; Walentosky, Matthew J.; Viafore, Kendall D.; Strom, Allison L.; Cool, Richard J.; Sola, Nicole A.; Crayton, Hannah; Pilachowski, Catherine A.; Jacoby, George H.; Corbett, Danielle L.; Rene, Michelle; Hernandez, Denise</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 936, Issue 2, id.117, 15 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...936..117R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...936..109P</TD>
<TD>Constraints on the Spindown of Fully Convective M Dwarfs Using Wide Field Binaries</TD>
<TD>Pass, Emily K.; Charbonneau, David; Irwin, Jonathan M.; Winters, Jennifer G.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 936, Issue 2, id.109, 20 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...936..109P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...936..104W</TD>
<TD>Variability-selected Intermediate-mass Black Hole Candidates in Dwarf Galaxies from ZTF and WISE</TD>
<TD>Ward, Charlotte; Gezari, Suvi; Nugent, Peter; Bellm, Eric C.; Dekany, Richard; Drake, Andrew; Duev, Dmitry A.; Graham, Matthew J.; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Kool, Erik C.; Masci, Frank J.; Riddle, Reed L.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 936, Issue 2, id.104, 19 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...936..104W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...936...95W</TD>
<TD>NuSTAR Observations of Intrinsically X-Ray Weak Quasar Candidates: An Obscuration-only Scenario</TD>
<TD>Wang, Chaojun; Luo, B.; Brandt, W. N.; Alexander, D. M.; Bauer, F. E.; Gallagher, S. C.; Huang, Jian; Liu, Hezhen; Stern, D.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 936, Issue 2, id.95, 17 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...936...95W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...936...75L</TD>
<TD>Velocity-resolved Reverberation Mapping of Changing-look Active Galactic Nucleus NGC 4151 during Outburst Stage: Evidence for Kinematics Evolution of Broad-line Region</TD>
<TD>Li, Sha-Sha; Feng, Hai-Cheng; Liu, H. T.; Bai, J. M.; Li, Rui; Lu, Kai-Xing; Wang, Jian-Guo; Huang, Ying-Ke; Zhang, Zhi-Xiang</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 936, Issue 1, id.75, 15 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...936...75L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...936...64S</TD>
<TD>A Multi-epoch, Multiwavelength Study of the Classical FUor V1515 Cyg Approaching Quiescence</TD>
<TD>Szabó, Zs. M.; Kóspál, Á.; Ábrahám, P.; Park, S.; Siwak, M.; Green, J. D.; Pál, A.; Acosta-Pulido, J. A.; Lee, J. -E.; Ibrahimov, M.; Grankin, K.; Kovács, B.; Bora, Zs.; Bódi, A.; Cseh, B.; Csörnyei, G.; Dróżdż, Marek; Hanyecz, O.; Ignácz, B.; Kalup, Cs.; Könyves-Tóth, R.; Krezinger, M.; Kriskovics, L.; Ogłoza, Waldemar; Ordasi, A.; Sárneczky, K.; Seli, B.; Szakáts, R.; Sódor, Á.; Szing, A.; Vida, K.; Vinkó, J.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 936, Issue 1, id.64, 20 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...936...64S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...936...63S</TD>
<TD>Modeling Long-term Variability in Stellar-compact Object Binary Systems for Mass Determinations</TD>
<TD>Sorabella, Nicholas M.; Bhattacharya, Sayantan; Laycock, Silas G. T.; Christodoulou, Dimitris M.; Massarotti, Alessandro</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 936, Issue 1, id.63, 7 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...936...63S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...936...33Z</TD>
<TD>A White Dwarf-Main-sequence Binary Unveiled by Time-domain Observations from LAMOST and TESS</TD>
<TD>Zheng, Ling-Lin; Gu, Wei-Min; Sun, Mouyuan; Zhang, Zhi-Xiang; Yi, Tuan; Wu, Jianfeng; Wang, Junfeng; Fu, Jin-Bo; Qi, Sen-Yu; Yang, Fan; Wang, Song; Wang, Liang; Bai, Zhong-Rui; Zhang, Haotong; Li, Chun-Qian; Shi, Jian-Rong; Zong, Weikai; Bai, Yu; Liu, Jifeng</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 936, Issue 1, id.33, 10 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...936...33Z</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022AcA....72..103Z</TD>
<TD>TIC 452991707 and TIC 452991693 as a Candidate Sextuple System with Three Eclipsing Binaries</TD>
<TD>Zasche, P.; Henzl, Z.</TD>
<TD>Acta Astronomica, vol 72, no 2, p. 103-111</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022AcA....72..103Z</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ARNPS..72..365K</TD>
<TD>High-Energy Extragalactic Neutrino Astrophysics</TD>
<TD>Kurahashi, Naoko; Murase, Kohta; Santander, Marcos</TD>
<TD>Annual Review of Nuclear and Particle Science, Volume 72, pp. 365-387</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ARNPS..72..365K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022AJ....164..117D</TD>
<TD>Searching the SETI Ellipsoid with Gaia</TD>
<TD>Davenport, James R. A.; Cabrales, Bárbara; Sheikh, Sofia; Croft, Steve; Siemion, Andrew P. V.; Giles, Daniel; Cody, Ann Marie</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 164, Issue 3, id.117, 6 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022AJ....164..117D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022AJ....164..115N</TD>
<TD>TESS Hunt for Young and Maturing Exoplanets (THYME). VII. Membership, Rotation, and Lithium in the Young Cluster Group-X and a New Young Exoplanet</TD>
<TD>Newton, Elisabeth R.; Rampalli, Rayna; Kraus, Adam L.; Mann, Andrew W.; Curtis, Jason L.; Vanderburg, Andrew; Krolikowski, Daniel M.; Huber, Daniel; Petter, Grayson C.; Bieryla, Allyson; Tofflemire, Benjamin M.; Thao, Pa Chia; Wood, Mackenna L.; Kerr, Ronan; Safanov, Boris S.; Strakhov, Ivan A.; Ciardi, David R.; Giacalone, Steven; Dressing, Courtney D.; Gill, Holden; Savel, Arjun B.; Collins, Karen A.; Brown, Peyton; Murgas, Felipe; Isogai, Keisuke; Narita, Norio; Palle, Enric; Quinn, Samuel N.; Eastman, Jason D.; Fűrész, Gábor; Shiao, Bernie; Daylan, Tansu; Caldwell, Douglas A.; Ricker, George R.; Vanderspek, Roland; Seager, Sara; Winn, Joshua N.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Latham, David W.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 164, Issue 3, id.115, 23 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022AJ....164..115N</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022AJ....164...90K</TD>
<TD>India's First Robotic Eye for Time-domain Astrophysics: The GROWTH-India Telescope</TD>
<TD>Kumar, Harsh; Bhalerao, Varun; Anupama, G. C.; Barway, Sudhanshu; Basu, Judhajeet; Deshmukh, Kunal; De, Kishalay; Dutta, Anirban; Fremling, Christoffer; Iyer, Hrishikesh; Jassani, Adeem; Joharle, Simran; Karambelkar, Viraj; Khandagale, Maitreya; Krishna, K. Adithya; Kulkarni, Sumeet; Mate, Sujay; Patil, Atharva; Phanindra, DVS; Samantaray, Subham; Sharma, Kritti; Sharma, Yashvi; Shenoy, Vedant; Singh, Avinash; Srivastava, Shubham; Swain, Vishwajeet; Waratkar, Gaurav; Angchuk, Dorje; Dorjay, Padma; Dorjai, Tsewang; Gyalson, Tsewang; Jorphail, Sonam; Mahay, Tashi Thsering; Norbu, Rigzin; Sharma, Tarun Kumar; Stanzin, Jigmet; Stanzin, Tsewang; Stanzin, Urgain</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 164, Issue 3, id.90, 13 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022AJ....164...90K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022AJ....164...81K</TD>
<TD>TOI-3757 b: A Low-density Gas Giant Orbiting a Solar-metallicity M Dwarf</TD>
<TD>Kanodia, Shubham; Libby-Roberts, Jessica; Cañas, Caleb I.; Ninan, Joe P.; Mahadevan, Suvrath; Stefansson, Gudmundur; Lin, Andrea S. J.; Jones, Sinclaire; Monson, Andrew; Parker, Brock A.; Kobulnicky, Henry A.; Swaby, Tera N.; Powers, Luke; Beard, Corey; Bender, Chad F.; Blake, Cullen H.; Cochran, William D.; Dong, Jiayin; Diddams, Scott A.; Fredrick, Connor; Gupta, Arvind F.; Halverson, Samuel; Hearty, Fred; Logsdon, Sarah E.; Metcalf, Andrew J.; McElwain, Michael W.; Morley, Caroline; Rajagopal, Jayadev; Ramsey, Lawrence W.; Robertson, Paul; Roy, Arpita; Schwab, Christian; Terrien, Ryan C.; Wisniewski, John; Wright, Jason T.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 164, Issue 3, id.81, 17 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022AJ....164...81K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...665L...3D</TD>
<TD>X-ray view of a merging supermassive black hole binary candidate SDSS J1430+2303: Results from the first ∼200 days of observations</TD>
<TD>Dou, Liming; Jiang, Ning; Wang, Tinggui; Shu, Xinwen; Yang, Huan; Pan, Zhen; Zhu, Jiazheng; An, Tao; Zheng, Zhen-Ya; Ai, Yanli</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 665, id.L3, 7 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...665L...3D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...665A.139S</TD>
<TD>Accretion flows around exotic tidal wormholes. I. Ray-tracing</TD>
<TD>Sokoliuk, O.; Praharaj, S.; Baransky, A.; Sahoo, P. K.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 665, id.A139, 16 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...665A.139S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...665A.123M</TD>
<TD>Testing the homogeneity of type Ia Supernovae in near-infrared for accurate distance estimations</TD>
<TD>Müller-Bravo, T. E.; Galbany, L.; Karamehmetoglu, E.; Stritzinger, M.; Burns, C.; Phan, K.; Iáñez Ferres, A.; Anderson, J. P.; Ashall, C.; Baron, E.; Hoeflich, P.; Hsiao, E. Y.; de Jaeger, T.; Kumar, S.; Lu, J.; Phillips, M. M.; Shahbandeh, M.; Suntzeff, N.; Uddin, S. A.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 665, id.A123, 14 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...665A.123M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...665A.120C</TD>
<TD>A detailed analysis of the Gl 486 planetary system</TD>
<TD>Caballero, J. A.; González-Álvarez, E.; Brady, M.; Trifonov, T.; Ellis, T. G.; Dorn, C.; Cifuentes, C.; Molaverdikhani, K.; Bean, J. L.; Boyajian, T.; Rodríguez, E.; Sanz-Forcada, J.; Zapatero Osorio, M. R.; Abia, C.; Amado, P. J.; Anugu, N.; Béjar, V. J. S.; Davies, C. L.; Dreizler, S.; Dubois, F.; Ennis, J.; Espinoza, N.; Farrington, C. D.; López, A. García; Gardner, T.; Hatzes, A. P.; Henning, Th.; Herrero, E.; Herrero-Cisneros, E.; Kaminski, A.; Kasper, D.; Klement, R.; Kraus, S.; Labdon, A.; Lanthermann, C.; Le Bouquin, J. -B.; López González, M. J.; Luque, R.; Mann, A. W.; Marfil, E.; Monnier, J. D.; Montes, D.; Morales, J. C.; Pallé, E.; Pedraz, S.; Quirrenbach, A.; Reffert, S.; Reiners, A.; Ribas, I.; Rodríguez-López, C.; Schaefer, G.; Schweitzer, A.; Seifahrt, A.; Setterholm, B. R.; Shan, Y.; Shulyak, D.; Solano, E.; Sreenivas, K. R.; Stefánsson, G.; Stürmer, J.; Tabernero, H. M.; Tal-Or, L.; ten Brummelaar, T.; Vanaverbeke, S.; von Braun, K.; Youngblood, A.; Zechmeister, M.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 665, id.A120, 41 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...665A.120C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...665A..99M</TD>
<TD>SNGuess: A method for the selection of young extragalactic transients</TD>
<TD>Miranda, N.; Freytag, J. C.; Nordin, J.; Biswas, R.; Brinnel, V.; Fremling, C.; Kowalski, M.; Mahabal, A.; Reusch, S.; van Santen, J.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 665, id.A99, 14 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...665A..99M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022PSJ.....3..187H</TD>
<TD>Surface Properties of Near-Sun Asteroids</TD>
<TD>Holt, Carrie E.; Knight, Matthew M.; Kelley, Michael S. P.; Ye, Quanzhi; Hsieh, Henry H.; Snodgrass, Colin; Fitzsimmons, Alan; Richardson, Derek C.; Sunshine, Jessica M.; Eisner, Nora L.; Gustaffson, Annika</TD>
<TD>The Planetary Science Journal, Volume 3, Issue 8, id.187, 17 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022PSJ.....3..187H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022PASJ...74..946T</TD>
<TD>Deep-learning real/bogus classification for the Tomo-e Gozen transient survey</TD>
<TD>Takahashi, Ichiro; Hamasaki, Ryo; Ueda, Naonori; Tanaka, Masaomi; Tominaga, Nozomu; Sako, Shigeyuki; Ohsawa, Ryou; Yoshida, Naoki</TD>
<TD>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Volume 74, Issue 4, pp.946-960</TD>
<TD>2022-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022PASJ...74..946T</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022NewA...9501813S</TD>
<TD>Automatic detection of accretion bursts in young stellar objects: A new algorithm for long-term sky surveys</TD>
<TD>Strafella, F.; Altavilla, G.; Giannini, T.; Giunta, A.; Lorenzetti, D.; Nucita, A.; Franco, A.</TD>
<TD>New Astronomy, Volume 95, article id. 101813.</TD>
<TD>2022-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022NewA...9501813S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022NCimR..45..549C</TD>
<TD>Supernovae and their cosmological implications</TD>
<TD>Cappellaro, Enrico</TD>
<TD>La Rivista del Nuovo Cimento, vol. 45, issue 8, pp. 549-586</TD>
<TD>2022-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022NCimR..45..549C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.514.5528L</TD>
<TD>CoBiToM Project - II. Evolution of contact binary systems close to the orbital period cut-off</TD>
<TD>Loukaidou, G. A.; Gazeas, K. D.; Palafouta, S.; Athanasopoulos, D.; Zola, S.; Liakos, A.; Niarchos, P. G.; Hakala, P.; Essam, A.; Hatzidimitriou, D.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 514, Issue 4, pp.5528-5547</TD>
<TD>2022-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.514.5528L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.514.4932C</TD>
<TD>Statistics of BY Draconis chromospheric variable stars</TD>
<TD>Chahal, Deepak; de Grijs, Richard; Kamath, Devika; Chen, Xiaodian</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 514, Issue 4, pp.4932-4943</TD>
<TD>2022-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.514.4932C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.514.4756L</TD>
<TD>TSCat: data model and storage engine for AI-based light-curve analysis</TD>
<TD>Li, Kun; Yu, Ce; Zhang, Yanxia; Sun, Chao; Xiao, Jian; Cui, Chenzhou; Zhang, Yajie; Mu, Yifei</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 514, Issue 4, pp.4756-4764</TD>
<TD>2022-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.514.4756L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.514.4406W</TD>
<TD>Could TDE outflows produce the PeV neutrino events?</TD>
<TD>Wu, Han-Ji; Mou, Guobin; Wang, Kai; Wang, Wei; Li, Zhuo</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 514, Issue 3, pp.4406-4412</TD>
<TD>2022-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.514.4406W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.514.4120G</TD>
<TD>TESS discovery of a sub-Neptune orbiting a mid-M dwarf TOI-2136</TD>
<TD>Gan, Tianjun; Soubkiou, Abderahmane; Wang, Sharon X.; Benkhaldoun, Zouhair; Mao, Shude; Artigau, Étienne; Fouqué, Pascal; Arnold, Luc; Giacalone, Steven; Theissen, Christopher A.; Aganze, Christian; Burgasser, Adam; Collins, Karen A.; Shporer, Avi; Barkaoui, Khalid; Ghachoui, Mourad; Howell, Steve B.; Lamman, Claire; Demangeon, Olivier D. S.; Burdanov, Artem; Cadieux, Charles; Chouqar, Jamila; Collins, Kevin I.; Cook, Neil J.; Delrez, Laetitia; Demory, Brice-Olivier; Doyon, René; Dransfield, Georgina; Dressing, Courtney D.; Ducrot, Elsa; Fan, Jiahao; Garcia, Lionel; Gill, Holden; Gillon, Michaël; Gnilka, Crystal L.; Gómez Maqueo Chew, Yilen; Günther, Maximilian N.; Henze, Christopher E.; Huang, Chelsea X.; Jehin, Emmanuel; Jensen, Eric L. N.; Lin, Zitao; Manset, Nadine; McCormac, James; Murray, Catriona A.; Niraula, Prajwal; Pedersen, Peter P.; Pozuelos, Francisco J.; Queloz, Didier; Rackham, Benjamin V.; Savel, Arjun B.; Schanche, Nicole; Schwarz, Richard P.; Sebastian, Daniel; Thompson, Samantha; Timmermans, Mathilde; Triaud, Amaury H. M. J.; Vezie, Michael; Wells, Robert D.; de Wit, Julien; Ricker, George R.; Vanderspek, Roland; Latham, David W.; Seager, Sara; Winn, Joshua N.; Jenkins, Jon M.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 514, Issue 3, pp.4120-4139</TD>
<TD>2022-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.514.4120G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.514.4102M</TD>
<TD>Starfall: a heavy rain of stars in 'turning on' AGN</TD>
<TD>McKernan, B.; Ford, K. E. S.; Cantiello, M.; Graham, M.; Jermyn, A. S.; Leigh, N. W. C.; Ryu, T.; Stern, D.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 514, Issue 3, pp.4102-4110</TD>
<TD>2022-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.514.4102M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.514.3541S</TD>
<TD>Observations of the very young Type Ia Supernova 2019np with early-excess emission</TD>
<TD>Sai, Hanna; Wang, Xiaofeng; Elias-Rosa, Nancy; Yang, Yi; Zhang, Jujia; Lin, Weili; Mo, Jun; Piro, Anthony L.; Zeng, Xiangyun; Reguitti, Andrea; Brown, Peter; Burns, Christopher R.; Cai, Yongzhi; Fiore, Achille; Hsiao, Eric Y.; Isern, Jordi; Itagaki, K.; Li, Wenxiong; Li, Zhitong; Pessi, Priscila J.; Phillips, M. M.; Schuldt, Stefan; Shahbandeh, Melissa; Stritzinger, Maximilian D.; Tomasella, Lina; Vogl, Christian; Wang, Bo; Wang, Lingzhi; Wu, Chengyuan; Yang, Sheng; Zhang, Jicheng; Zhang, Tianmeng; Zhang, Xinghan</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 514, Issue 3, pp.3541-3558</TD>
<TD>2022-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.514.3541S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.514.1975A</TD>
<TD>Coordinated time variability of multi-phase ultra-fast outflows in J132216.25 + 052446.3</TD>
<TD>Aromal, P.; Srianand, R.; Petitjean, P.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 514, Issue 2, pp.1975-1989</TD>
<TD>2022-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.514.1975A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022JHEAp..35....1V</TD>
<TD>ASTRI Mini-Array core science at the Observatorio del Teide</TD>
<TD>Vercellone, S.; Bigongiari, C.; Burtovoi, A.; Cardillo, M.; Catalano, O.; Franceschini, A.; Lombardi, S.; Nava, L.; Pintore, F.; Stamerra, A.; Tavecchio, F.; Zampieri, L.; Alves Batista, R.; Amato, E.; Antonelli, L. A.; Arcaro, C.; Becerra González, J.; Bonnoli, G.; Böttcher, M.; Brunetti, G.; Compagnino, A. A.; Crestan, S.; D'Aì, A.; Fiori, M.; Galanti, G.; Giuliani, A.; de Gouveia Dal Pino, E. M.; Green, J. G.; Lamastra, A.; Landoni, M.; Lucarelli, F.; Morlino, G.; Olmi, B.; Peretti, E.; Piano, G.; Ponti, G.; Poretti, E.; Romano, P.; Saturni, F. G.; Scuderi, S.; Tutone, A.; Umana, G.; Acosta-Pulido, J. A.; Barai, P.; Bonanno, A.; Bonanno, G.; Bruno, P.; Bulgarelli, A.; Conforti, V.; Costa, A.; Cusumano, G.; Del Santo, M.; del Valle, M. V.; Della Ceca, R.; Falceta-Gonçalves, D. A.; Fioretti, V.; Germani, S.; García-López, R. J.; Ghedina, A.; Gianotti, F.; Giordano, V.; Kreter, M.; Incardona, F.; Iovenitti, S.; La Barbera, A.; La Palombara, N.; La Parola, V.; Leto, G.; Longo, F.; López-Oramas, A.; Maccarone, M. C.; Mereghetti, S.; Millul, R.; Naletto, G.; Pagliaro, A.; Parmiggiani, N.; Righi, C.; Rodríguez-Ramírez, J. C.; Romeo, G.; Sangiorgi, P.; Santos de Lima, R.; Tagliaferri, G.; Testa, V.; Tosti, G.; Vázquez Acosta, M.; Żywucka, N.; Caraveo, P. A.; Pareschi, G.</TD>
<TD>Journal of High Energy Astrophysics, Volume 35, p. 1-42.</TD>
<TD>2022-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022JHEAp..35....1V</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022CeMDA.134...36C</TD>
<TD>Machine learning applied to asteroid dynamics</TD>
<TD>Carruba, V.; Aljbaae, S.; Domingos, R. C.; Huaman, M.; Barletta, W.</TD>
<TD>Celestial Mechanics and Dynamical Astronomy, Volume 134, Issue 4, article id.36</TD>
<TD>2022-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022CeMDA.134...36C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...935L..34L</TD>
<TD>Magnetar Engines in Fast Blue Optical Transients and Their Connections with SLSNe, SNe Ic-BL, and lGRBs</TD>
<TD>Liu, Jian-Feng; Zhu, Jin-Ping; Liu, Liang-Duan; Yu, Yun-Wei; Zhang, Bing</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 935, Issue 2, id.L34, 12 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...935L..34L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...935L...6I</TD>
<TD>Discovery of the First Known Asteroid Confined within the Orbit of Venus</TD>
<TD>Ip, Wing-Huen; Masci, Frank J.; Ye, Quanzhi; Kramer, Emily A.; Helou, George; Prince, Thomas A.; Kulkarni, S. R.; Dekany, Richard; Drake, Andrew; Graham, Matthew J.; Groom, Steven; Laher, Russ R.; Mahabal, Ashish A.; Rusholme, Ben</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 935, Issue 1, id.L6, 4 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...935L...6I</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...935..151H</TD>
<TD>Luminous Optical and X-Ray Flaring of the Putative Redback Millisecond Pulsar 1FGL J0523.5-2529</TD>
<TD>Halpern, Jules P.; Perez, Karen I.; Bogdanov, Slavko</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 935, Issue 2, id.151, 17 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...935..151H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...935..139M</TD>
<TD>Observing Scenarios for the Next Decade of Early Warning Detection of Binary Neutron Stars</TD>
<TD>Magee, Ryan; Borhanian, Ssohrab</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 935, Issue 2, id.139, 8 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...935..139M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...935...87P</TD>
<TD>Foraging with MUSHROOMS: A Mixed-integer Linear Programming Scheduler for Multimessenger Target of Opportunity Searches with the Zwicky Transient Facility</TD>
<TD>Parazin, B.; Coughlin, Michael W.; Singer, Leo P.; Gupta, Vaidehi; Anand, Shreya</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 935, Issue 2, id.87, 8 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...935...87P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...935...43G</TD>
<TD>Evolution of X-Ray Activity in &lt;25 Myr Old Pre-main Sequence Stars</TD>
<TD>Getman, Konstantin V.; Feigelson, Eric D.; Garmire, Gordon P.; Broos, Patrick S.; Kuhn, Michael A.; Preibisch, Thomas; Airapetian, Vladimir S.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 935, Issue 1, id.43, 29 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...935...43G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...935...36D</TD>
<TD>SRGA J181414.6-225604: A New Galactic Symbiotic X-Ray Binary Outburst Triggered by an Intense Mass-loss Episode of a Heavily Obscured Mira Variable</TD>
<TD>De, Kishalay; Mereminskiy, Ilya; Soria, Roberto; Conroy, Charlie; Kara, Erin; Anand, Shreya; Ashley, Michael C. B.; Boyer, Martha L.; Chakrabarty, Deepto; Grefenstette, Brian; Hankins, Matthew J.; Hillenbrand, Lynne A.; Jencson, Jacob E.; Karambelkar, Viraj; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Lau, Ryan M.; Lutovinov, Alexander; Moore, Anna M.; Ng, Mason; Panagiotou, Christos; Pasham, Dheeraj R.; Semena, Andrey; Simcoe, Robert; Soon, Jamie; Srinivasaragavan, Gokul P.; Travouillon, Tony; Yao, Yuhan</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 935, Issue 1, id.36, 24 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...935...36D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...935...31H</TD>
<TD>Weak Mass Loss from the Red Supergiant Progenitor of the Type II SN 2021yja</TD>
<TD>Hosseinzadeh, Griffin; Kilpatrick, Charles D.; Dong, Yize; Sand, David J.; Andrews, Jennifer E.; Bostroem, K. Azalee; Janzen, Daryl; Jencson, Jacob E.; Lundquist, Michael; Meza Retamal, Nicolas E.; Pearson, Jeniveve; Valenti, Stefano; Wyatt, Samuel; Burke, Jamison; Hiramatsu, Daichi; Howell, D. Andrew; McCully, Curtis; Newsome, Megan; Gonzalez, Estefania Padilla; Pellegrino, Craig; Terreran, Giacomo; Auchettl, Katie; Davis, Kyle W.; Foley, Ryan J.; Miao, Hao-Yu; Pan, Yen-Chen; Rest, Armin; Siebert, Matthew R.; Taggart, Kirsty; Tucker, Brad E.; Cyrus Leung, Feng Lin; Swift, Jonathan J.; Yang, Grace; Anderson, Joseph P.; Ashall, Chris; Benetti, Stefano; Brown, Peter J.; Cartier, Régis; Chen, Ting-Wan; Della Valle, Massimo; Galbany, Lluís; Gomez, Sebastian; Gromadzki, Mariusz; Haislip, Joshua; Hsiao, Eric Y.; Inserra, Cosimo; Jha, Saurabh W.; Killestein, Thomas L.; Kouprianov, Vladimir; Kozyreva, Alexandra; Müller-Bravo, Tomás E.; Nicholl, Matt; Paraskeva, Emmy; Reichart, Daniel E.; Ryder, Stuart; Shahbandeh, Melissa; Shappee, Ben; Smith, Nathan; Young, David R.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 935, Issue 1, id.31, 24 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...935...31H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...935...23G</TD>
<TD>Improving Astronomical Time-series Classification via Data Augmentation with Generative Adversarial Networks</TD>
<TD>García-Jara, Germán; Protopapas, Pavlos; Estévez, Pablo A.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 935, Issue 1, id.23, 14 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...935...23G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...935...15Z</TD>
<TD>COol Companions ON Ultrawide orbiTS (COCONUTS). III. A Very Red L6 Benchmark Brown Dwarf around a Young M5 Dwarf</TD>
<TD>Zhang, Zhoujian; Liu, Michael C.; Morley, Caroline V.; Magnier, Eugene A.; Tucker, Michael A.; Vanderbosch, Zachary P.; Do, Aaron; Shappee, Benjamin J.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 935, Issue 1, id.15, 25 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...935...15Z</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...934..185D</TD>
<TD>A Uniform Type Ia Supernova Distance Ladder with the Zwicky Transient Facility: Absolute Calibration Based on the Tip of the Red Giant Branch Method</TD>
<TD>Dhawan, Suhail; Goobar, Ariel; Johansson, Joel; Jang, In Sung; Rigault, Mickael; Harvey, Luke; Maguire, Kate; Freedman, Wendy L.; Madore, Barry F.; Smith, Mathew; Sollerman, Jesper; Kim, Young-Lo; Andreoni, Igor; Bellm, Eric C.; Coughlin, Michael W.; Dekany, Richard; Graham, Matthew J.; Kulkarni, Shrinivas R.; Laher, Russ R.; Medford, Michael S.; Neill, James D.; Nir, Guy; Riddle, Reed; Rusholme, Ben</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 934, Issue 2, id.185, 8 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...934..185D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...934..142S</TD>
<TD>1RXH J082623.6-505741: A New Long-period Cataclysmic Variable with an Evolved Donor and a Low Mass-transfer Rate</TD>
<TD>Sokolovsky, Kirill V.; Strader, Jay; Swihart, Samuel J.; Aydi, Elias; Bahramian, Arash; Chomiuk, Laura; Heinke, Craig O.; Hughes, Allison K.; Li, Kwan-Lok; de Oliveira, Raimundo Lopes; Miller-Jones, James C. A.; Mukai, Koji; Sand, David J.; Shishkovsky, Laura; Tremou, Evangelia; Voggel, Karina</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 934, Issue 2, id.142, 15 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...934..142S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...934..104Y</TD>
<TD>The X-Ray and Radio Loud Fast Blue Optical Transient AT2020mrf: Implications for an Emerging Class of Engine-driven Massive Star Explosions</TD>
<TD>Yao, Yuhan; Ho, Anna Y. Q.; Medvedev, Pavel; Nayana, A. J.; Perley, Daniel A.; Kulkarni, S. R.; Chandra, Poonam; Sazonov, Sergey; Gilfanov, Marat; Khorunzhev, Georgii; Khatami, David K.; Sunyaev, Rashid</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 934, Issue 2, id.104, 20 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...934..104Y</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...934...97F</TD>
<TD>The Nature of Luminous Quasars with Very Large C IV Equivalent Widths</TD>
<TD>Fu, Shuqi; Brandt, W. N.; Zou, Fan; Laor, Ari; Garmire, Gordon P.; Ni, Qingling; Timlin, John D., III; Xue, Yongquan</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 934, Issue 2, id.97, 13 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...934...97F</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022AnPhy.44368968S</TD>
<TD>Traversable wormholes with charge and non-commutative geometry in the f(Q) gravity</TD>
<TD>Sokoliuk, Oleksii; Hassan, Zinnat; Sahoo, P. K.; Baransky, Alexander</TD>
<TD>Annals of Physics, Volume 443, article id. 168968.</TD>
<TD>2022-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022AnPhy.44368968S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ARA&amp;A..60...31K</TD>
<TD>Asteroseismology Across the Hertzsprung-Russell Diagram</TD>
<TD>Kurtz, Donald W.</TD>
<TD>Annual Review of Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 60, pp. 31-71</TD>
<TD>2022-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ARA&amp;A..60...31K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022AJ....164...68S</TD>
<TD>The Astronomy Commons Platform: A Deployable Cloud-based Analysis Platform for Astronomy</TD>
<TD>Stetzler, Steven; Jurić, Mario; Boone, Kyle; Connolly, Andrew; Slater, Colin T.; Zečević, Petar</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 164, Issue 2, id.68, 18 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022AJ....164...68S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022AJ....164...50C</TD>
<TD>TOI-3714 b and TOI-3629 b: Two Gas Giants Transiting M Dwarfs Confirmed with the Habitable-zone Planet Finder and NEID</TD>
<TD>Cañas, Caleb I.; Kanodia, Shubham; Bender, Chad F.; Mahadevan, Suvrath; Stefánsson, Guđhmundur; Cochran, William D.; Lin, Andrea S. J.; Hwang, Hsiang-Chih; Powers, Luke; Monson, Andrew; Green, Elizabeth M.; Parker, Brock A.; Swaby, Tera N.; Kobulnicky, Henry A.; Wisniewski, John; Gupta, Arvind F.; Everett, Mark E.; Jones, Sinclaire; Anjakos, Benjamin; Beard, Corey; Blake, Cullen H.; Diddams, Scott A.; Dong, Zehao; Fredrick, Connor; Hakemiamjad, Elnaz; Hebb, Leslie; Libby-Roberts, Jessica E.; Logsdon, Sarah E.; McElwain, Michael W.; Metcalf, Andrew J.; Ninan, Joe P.; Rajagopal, Jayadev; Ramsey, Lawrence W.; Robertson, Paul; Roy, Arpita; Ruhle, Jacob; Schwab, Christian; Terrien, Ryan C.; Wright, Jason T.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 164, Issue 2, id.50, 24 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022AJ....164...50C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022AJ....164...45N</TD>
<TD>Evaluating the V-band Photometric Metallicity with Fundamental Mode RR Lyrae in the Kepler Field</TD>
<TD>Ngeow, Chow-Choong</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 164, Issue 2, id.45, 10 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022AJ....164...45N</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...664A.165M</TD>
<TD>TUVO-21acq: A new cataclysmic variable discovered through a UV outburst</TD>
<TD>Modiano, David; Wijnands, Rudy; Buckley, David A. H.; Gromadzki, Mariusz; Verberne, Sill; van Etten, Marieke</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 664, id.A165, 10 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...664A.165M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...664A.158R</TD>
<TD>Energetic nuclear transients in luminous and ultraluminous infrared galaxies</TD>
<TD>Reynolds, T. M.; Mattila, S.; Efstathiou, A.; Kankare, E.; Kool, E.; Ryder, S.; Peña-Moñino, L.; Pérez-Torres, M. A.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 664, id.A158, 15 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...664A.158R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...664A.148P</TD>
<TD>Milky Way archaeology using RR Lyrae and type II Cepheids. II. High-velocity RR Lyrae stars and Milky Way mass</TD>
<TD>Prudil, Z.; Koch-Hansen, A. J.; Lemasle, B.; Grebel, E. K.; Marchetti, T.; Hansen, C. J.; Crestani, J.; Braga, V. F.; Bono, G.; Chaboyer, B.; Fabrizio, M.; Dall'Ora, M.; Martínez-Vázquez, C. E.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 664, id.A148, 15 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...664A.148P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...664A.109P</TD>
<TD>The Gaia EDR3 view of Johnson-Kron-Cousins standard stars: the curated Landolt and Stetson collections</TD>
<TD>Pancino, E.; Marrese, P. M.; Marinoni, S.; Sanna, N.; Turchi, A.; Tsantaki, M.; Rainer, M.; Altavilla, G.; Monelli, M.; Monaco, L.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 664, id.A109, 19 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...664A.109P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...664A..96Z</TD>
<TD>Multiply eclipsing candidates from the TESS satellite</TD>
<TD>Zasche, P.; Henzl, Z.; Mašek, M.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 664, id.A96, 15 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...664A..96Z</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...664A..81M</TD>
<TD>O'TRAIN: A robust and flexible `real or bogus' classifier for the study of the optical transient sky</TD>
<TD>Makhlouf, K.; Turpin, D.; Corre, D.; Karpov, S.; Kann, D. A.; Klotz, A.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 664, id.A81, 18 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...664A..81M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022PrPNP.12503948A</TD>
<TD>Quantum gravity phenomenology at the dawn of the multi-messenger era-A review</TD>
<TD>Addazi, A.; Alvarez-Muniz, J.; Alves Batista, R.; Amelino-Camelia, G.; Antonelli, V.; Arzano, M.; Asorey, M.; Atteia, J. -L.; Bahamonde, S.; Bajardi, F.; Ballesteros, A.; Baret, B.; Barreiros, D. M.; Basilakos, S.; Benisty, D.; Birnholtz, O.; Blanco-Pillado, J. J.; Blas, D.; Bolmont, J.; Boncioli, D.; Bosso, P.; Calcagni, G.; Capozziello, S.; Carmona, J. M.; Cerci, S.; Chernyakova, M.; Clesse, S.; Coelho, J. A. B.; Colak, S. M.; Cortes, J. L.; Das, S.; D'Esposito, V.; Demirci, M.; Di Luca, M. G.; di Matteo, A.; Dimitrijevic, D.; Djordjevic, G.; Prester, D. Dominis; Eichhorn, A.; Ellis, J.; Escamilla-Rivera, C.; Fabiano, G.; Franchino-Viñas, S. A.; Frassino, A. M.; Frattulillo, D.; Funk, S.; Fuster, A.; Gamboa, J.; Gent, A.; Gergely, L. Á.; Giammarchi, M.; Giesel, K.; Glicenstein, J. -F.; Gracia-Bondía, J.; Gracia-Ruiz, R.; Gubitosi, G.; Guendelman, E. I.; Gutierrez-Sagredo, I.; Haegel, L.; Heefer, S.; Held, A.; Herranz, F. J.; Hinderer, T.; Illana, J. I.; Ioannisian, A.; Jetzer, P.; Joaquim, F. R.; Kampert, K. -H.; Uysal, A. Karasu; Katori, T.; Kazarian, N.; Kerszberg, D.; Kowalski-Glikman, J.; Kuroyanagi, S.; Lämmerzahl, C.; Said, J. Levi; Liberati, S.; Lim, E.; Lobo, I. P.; López-Moya, M.; Luciano, G. G.; Manganaro, M.; Marcianò, A.; Martín-Moruno, P.; Martinez, Manel; Martinez, Mario; Martínez-Huerta, H.; Martínez-Miravé, P.; Masip, M.; Mattingly, D.; Mavromatos, N.; Mazumdar, A.; Méndez, F.; Mercati, F.; Micanovic, S.; Mielczarek, J.; Miller, A. L.; Milosevic, M.; Minic, D.; Miramonti, L.; Mitsou, V. A.; Moniz, P.; Mukherjee, S.; Nardini, G.; Navas, S.; Niechciol, M.; Nielsen, A. B.; Obers, N. A.; Oikonomou, F.; Oriti, D.; Paganini, C. F.; Palomares-Ruiz, S.; Pasechnik, R.; Pasic, V.; Pérez de los Heros, C.; Pfeifer, C.; Pieroni, M.; Piran, T.; Platania, A.; Rastgoo, S.; Relancio, J. J.; Reyes, M. A.; Ricciardone, A.; Risse, M.; Frias, M. D. Rodriguez; Rosati, G.; Rubiera-Garcia, D.; Sahlmann, H.; Sakellariadou, M.; Salamida, F.; Saridakis, E. N.; Satunin, P.; Schiffer, M.; Schüssler, F.; Sigl, G.; Sitarek, J.; Peracaula, J. Solà; Sopuerta, C. F.; Sotiriou, T. P.; Spurio, M.; Staicova, D.; Stergioulas, N.; Stoica, S.; Strišković, J.; Stuttard, T.; Cerci, D. Sunar; Tavakoli, Y.; Ternes, C. A.; Terzić, T.; Thiemann, T.; Tinyakov, P.; Torri, M. D. C.; Tórtola, M.; Trimarelli, C.; Trześniewski, T.; Tureanu, A.; Urban, F. R.; Vagenas, E. C.; Vernieri, D.; Vitagliano, V.; Wallet, J. -C.; Zornoza, J. D.</TD>
<TD>Progress in Particle and Nuclear Physics, Volume 125, article id. 103948.</TD>
<TD>2022-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022PrPNP.12503948A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022PhRvD.106b3520Q</TD>
<TD>Strongly lensed type Ia supernovae as a precise late-Universe probe of measuring the Hubble constant and cosmic curvature</TD>
<TD>Qi, Jing-Zhao; Cui, Yu; Hu, Wei-Hong; Zhang, Jing-Fei; Cui, Jing-Lei; Zhang, Xin</TD>
<TD>Physical Review D, Volume 106, Issue 2, article id.023520</TD>
<TD>2022-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022PhRvD.106b3520Q</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022PSJ.....3..173L</TD>
<TD>The LCO Outbursting Objects Key Project: Overview and Year 1 Status</TD>
<TD>Lister, Tim; Kelley, Michael S. P.; Holt, Carrie E.; Hsieh, Henry H.; Bannister, Michele T.; Verma, Aayushi A.; Dobson, Matthew M.; Knight, Matthew M.; Moulane, Youssef; Schwamb, Megan E.; Bodewits, Dennis; Bauer, James; Chatelain, Joseph; Fernández-Valenzuela, Estela; Gardener, Daniel; Gyuk, Geza; Hammergren, Mark; Huynh, Ky; Jehin, Emmanuel; Kokotanekova, Rosita; Lilly, Eva; Hui, Man-To; McKay, Adam; Opitom, Cyrielle; Protopapa, Silvia; Ridden-Harper, Ryan; Schambeau, Charles; Snodgrass, Colin; Stoddard-Jones, Cai; Usher, Helen; Wierzchos, Kacper; Yanamandra-Fisher, Padma A.; Ye, Quanzhi; Gomez, Edward; Greenstreet, Sarah</TD>
<TD>The Planetary Science Journal, Volume 3, Issue 7, id.173, 18 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022PSJ.....3..173L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022NuPhB.98015845S</TD>
<TD>Probing the existence of the ZTF Casimir wormholes in the framework of f (R) gravity</TD>
<TD>Sokoliuk, Oleksii; Baransky, Alexander; Sahoo, P. K.</TD>
<TD>Nuclear Physics, Section B, Volume 980, article id. 115845.</TD>
<TD>2022-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022NuPhB.98015845S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.514.1315B</TD>
<TD>Estimating transient rates from cosmological simulations and BPASS</TD>
<TD>Briel, Max M.; Eldridge, J. J.; Stanway, Elizabeth R.; Stevance, H. F.; Chrimes, A. A.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 514, Issue 1, pp.1315-1334</TD>
<TD>2022-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.514.1315B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.514.1188B</TD>
<TD>Nothing to see here: failed supernovae are faint or rare</TD>
<TD>Byrne, R. A.; Fraser, M.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 514, Issue 1, pp.1188-1205</TD>
<TD>2022-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.514.1188B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.514..806V</TD>
<TD>Stellar graveyards: clustering of compact objects in globular clusters NGC 3201 and NGC 6397</TD>
<TD>Vitral, Eduardo; Kremer, Kyle; Libralato, Mattia; Mamon, Gary A.; Bellini, Andrea</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 514, Issue 1, pp.806-825</TD>
<TD>2022-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.514..806V</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.514..227Z</TD>
<TD>Infrared and optical detectability of Dyson spheres at white dwarf stars</TD>
<TD>Zuckerman, B.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 514, Issue 1, pp.227-233</TD>
<TD>2022-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.514..227Z</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.514..200W</TD>
<TD>Discovery of a highly eccentric, chromospherically active binary: ASASSN-V J192114.84+624950.8</TD>
<TD>Way, Zachary S.; Jayasinghe, T.; Kochanek, C. S.; Stanek, K. Z.; Vallely, Patrick; Thompson, Todd A.; Holoien, Thomas W. -S.; Shappee, Benjamin J.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 514, Issue 1, pp.200-207</TD>
<TD>2022-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.514..200W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.513.5752M</TD>
<TD>How long can luminous blue variables sleep? A long-term photometric variability and spectral study of the Galactic candidate luminous blue variable MN 112</TD>
<TD>Maryeva, O. V.; Karpov, S. V.; Kniazev, A. Y.; Gvaramadze, V. V.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 513, Issue 4, pp.5752-5765</TD>
<TD>2022-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.513.5752M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.513.5540M</TD>
<TD>SN 2020acat: an energetic fast rising Type IIb supernova</TD>
<TD>Medler, K.; Mazzali, P. A.; Teffs, J.; Ashall, C.; Anderson, J. P.; Arcavi, I.; Benetti, S.; Bostroem, K. A.; Burke, J.; Cai, Y. -Z.; Charalampopoulos, P.; Elias-Rosa, N.; Ergon, M.; Galbany, L.; Gromadzki, M.; Hiramatsu, D.; Howell, D. A.; Inserra, C.; Lundqvist, P.; McCully, C.; Müller-Bravo, T.; Newsome, M.; Nicholl, M.; Padilla Gonzalez, E.; Paraskeva, E.; Pastorello, A.; Pellegrino, C.; Pessi, P. J.; Reguitti, A.; Reynolds, T. M.; Roy, R.; Terreran, G.; Tomasella, L.; Young, D. R.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 513, Issue 4, pp.5540-5558</TD>
<TD>2022-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.513.5540M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.513.4983V</TD>
<TD>Low luminosity Type II supernovae - IV. SN 2020cxd and SN 2021aai, at the edges of the sub-luminous supernovae class</TD>
<TD>Valerin, G.; Pumo, M. L.; Pastorello, A.; Reguitti, A.; Elias-Rosa, N.; Gútierrez, C. P.; Kankare, E.; Fraser, M.; Mazzali, P. A.; Howell, D. A.; Kotak, R.; Galbany, L.; Williams, S. C.; Cai, Y. -Z.; Salmaso, I.; Pinter, V.; Müller-Bravo, T. E.; Burke, J.; Padilla Gonzalez, E.; Hiramatsu, D.; McCully, C.; Newsome, M.; Pellegrino, C.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 513, Issue 4, pp.4983-4999</TD>
<TD>2022-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.513.4983V</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.513.4556Z</TD>
<TD>SN 2019va: a Type IIP Supernova with Large Influence of Nickel-56 Decay on the Plateau-phase Light Curve</TD>
<TD>Zhang, Xinghan; Wang, Xiaofeng; Sai, Hanna; Mo, Jun; Nagy, A. P.; Zhang, Jicheng; Cai, Yongzhi; Lin, Han; Zhang, Jujia; Baron, Eddie; DerKacy, James M.; Zhang, Tianmeng; Li, Zhitong; Graham, Melissa; Huang, Fang</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 513, Issue 3, pp.4556-4572</TD>
<TD>2022-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.513.4556Z</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.513.3858H</TD>
<TD>Circular polarimetry of suspect wind-accreting magnetic pre-polars</TD>
<TD>Hakala, Pasi; Parsons, Steven G.; Marsh, Thomas R.; Gänsicke, Boris T.; Ramsay, Gavin; Schwope, Axel; Hermes, J. J.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 513, Issue 3, pp.3858-3870</TD>
<TD>2022-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.513.3858H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.513.3587Z</TD>
<TD>Close detached white dwarf + brown dwarf binaries: further evidence for low values of the common envelope efficiency</TD>
<TD>Zorotovic, Monica; Schreiber, MatthiasR</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 513, Issue 3, pp.3587-3595</TD>
<TD>2022-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.513.3587Z</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.513.3564R</TD>
<TD>An Hα survey of the host environments of 77 type IIn supernovae within z &lt; 0.02</TD>
<TD>Ransome, C. L.; Habergham-Mawson, S. M.; Darnley, M. J.; James, P. A.; Percival, S. M.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 513, Issue 3, pp.3564-3576</TD>
<TD>2022-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.513.3564R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.513.3242W</TD>
<TD>Asteroid phase curves using sparse Gaia DR2 data and differential dense light curves</TD>
<TD>Wilawer, E.; Oszkiewicz, D.; Kryszczyńska, A.; Marciniak, A.; Shevchenko, V.; Belskaya, I.; Kwiatkowski, T.; Kankiewicz, P.; Horbowicz, J.; Kudak, V.; Kulczak, P.; Perig, V.; Sobkowiak, K.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 513, Issue 3, pp.3242-3251</TD>
<TD>2022-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.513.3242W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022FrASS...9.7100S</TD>
<TD>Pipeline for the Antarctic Survey Telescope 3-3 in Yaoan, Yunnan</TD>
<TD>Sun, Tianrui; Hu, Lei; Zhang, Songbo; Li, Xiaoyan; Meng, Kelai; Wu, Xuefeng; Wang, Lifan; Castro-Tirado, A. J.</TD>
<TD>Frontiers in Astronomy and Space Sciences, vol. 9, id. 897100</TD>
<TD>2022-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022FrASS...9.7100S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022FrASS...9.1486H</TD>
<TD>pyobs - An Observatory Control System for Robotic Telescopes</TD>
<TD>Husser, Tim-Oliver; Hessman, Frederic V.; Martens, Sven; Masur, Tilman; Royen, Karl; Schäfer, Sebastian</TD>
<TD>Frontiers in Astronomy and Space Sciences, vol. 9, id. 891486</TD>
<TD>2022-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022FrASS...9.1486H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022BlgAJ..37...46K</TD>
<TD>Ultra-short period contact binaries: restricting the parameters of the primary using Gaia parallax</TD>
<TD>Kurtenkov, Alexander</TD>
<TD>Bulgarian Astronomical Journal, Vol. 37, p. 46</TD>
<TD>2022-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022BlgAJ..37...46K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022AstL...48..370M</TD>
<TD>Search for Pre-Burst Emission from Binary Neutron Star Mergers with Spectrum-Roentgen-Gamma</TD>
<TD>Mereminskiy, I. A.; Lutovinov, A. A.; Postnov, K. A.; Arefiev, V. A.; Lapshov, I. Yu.; Molkov, S. V.; Sazonov, S. Yu.; Semena, A. N.; Tkachenko, A. Yu.; Shtykovsky, A. E.; Liu, Z.; Wilms, J.; Rau, A.; Dauser, T.; Kreykenbohm, I.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy Letters, Volume 48, Issue 7, p.370-375</TD>
<TD>2022-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022AstL...48..370M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...934...84L</TD>
<TD>Realistic Detection and Early Warning of Binary Neutron Stars with Decihertz Gravitational-wave Observatories</TD>
<TD>Liu, Chang; Kang, Yacheng; Shao, Lijing</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 934, Issue 1, id.84, 11 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...934...84L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...934....5Y</TD>
<TD>Models of Millimeter and Radio Emission from Interacting Supernovae</TD>
<TD>Yadlapalli, Nitika; Ravi, Vikram; Ho, Anna Y. Q.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 934, Issue 1, id.5, 9 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...934....5Y</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...933L..36J</TD>
<TD>MUSSES2020J: The Earliest Discovery of a Fast Blue Ultraluminous Transient at Redshift 1.063</TD>
<TD>Jiang, Ji-an; Yasuda, Naoki; Maeda, Keiichi; Tominaga, Nozomu; Doi, Mamoru; Ivezić, Željko; Yoachim, Peter; Uno, Kohki; Moriya, Takashi J.; Kumar, Brajesh; Pan, Yen-Chen; Tanaka, Masayuki; Tanaka, Masaomi; Nomoto, Ken'ichi; Jha, Saurabh W.; Ruiz-Lapuente, Pilar; Jones, David; Shigeyama, Toshikazu; Suzuki, Nao; Kokubo, Mitsuru; Furusawa, Hisanori; Miyazaki, Satoshi; Connolly, Andrew J.; Sahu, D. K.; Anupama, G. C.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 933, Issue 2, id.L36, 9 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...933L..36J</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...933L..28Y</TD>
<TD>Tidal Disruption on Stellar-mass Black Holes in Active Galactic Nuclei</TD>
<TD>Yang, Y.; Bartos, I.; Fragione, G.; Haiman, Z.; Kowalski, M.; Márka, S.; Perna, R.; Tagawa, H.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 933, Issue 2, id.L28, 6 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...933L..28Y</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...933L..21Z</TD>
<TD>Two Candidate KH 15D-like Systems from the Zwicky Transient Facility</TD>
<TD>Zhu, Wei; Bernhard, Klaus; Dai, Fei; Fang, Min; Zanazzi, J. J.; Zang, Weicheng; Dong, Subo; Hambsch, Franz-Josef; Gan, Tianjun; Wu, Zexuan; Poon, Michael</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 933, Issue 1, id.L21, 7 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...933L..21Z</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...933L..15K</TD>
<TD>Hubble Space Telescope Observations of Active Asteroid P/2020 O1 (Lemmon-PANSTARRS)</TD>
<TD>Kim, Yoonyoung; Jewitt, David; Agarwal, Jessica; Mutchler, Max; Li, Jing; Weaver, Harold</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 933, Issue 1, id.L15, 10 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...933L..15K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...933..203K</TD>
<TD>Hydrodynamics of Collisions and Close Encounters between Stellar Black Holes and Main-sequence Stars</TD>
<TD>Kremer, Kyle; Lombardi, James C.; Lu, Wenbin; Piro, Anthony L.; Rasio, Frederic A.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 933, Issue 2, id.203, 18 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...933..203K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...933..196H</TD>
<TD>Investigating the Nature of the Luminous Ambiguous Nuclear Transient ASASSN-17jz</TD>
<TD>Holoien, Thomas W. -S.; Neustadt, Jack M. M.; Vallely, Patrick J.; Auchettl, Katie; Hinkle, Jason T.; Romero-Cañizales, Cristina; Shappee, Benjamin. J.; Kochanek, Christopher S.; Stanek, K. Z.; Chen, Ping; Dong, Subo; Prieto, Jose L.; Thompson, Todd A.; Brink, Thomas G.; Filippenko, Alexei V.; Zheng, WeiKang; Bersier, David; Bose, Subhash; Burgasser, Adam J.; Channa, Sanyum; de Jaeger, Thomas; Hestenes, Julia; Im, Myungshin; Jeffers, Benjamin; Jun, Hyunsung D.; Lansbury, George; Post, Richard S.; Ross, Timothy W.; Stern, Daniel; Tang, Kevin; Tucker, Michael A.; Valenti, Stefano; Yunus, Sameen; Zhang, Keto D.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 933, Issue 2, id.196, 28 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...933..196H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...933..193Z</TD>
<TD>A Long-period Pre-ELM System Discovered from the LAMOST Medium-resolution Survey</TD>
<TD>Zhang, Zhi-Xiang; Zheng, Ling-Lin; Gu, Wei-Min; Sun, Mouyuan; Yi, Tuan; Shi, Jian-Rong; Wang, Song; Bai, Zhong-Rui; Zhang, Hao-Tong; Cui, Wen-Yuan; Wang, Junfeng; Wu, Jianfeng; Li, Xiang-Dong; Shao, Yong; Lu, Kai-Xing; Bai, Yu; Li, Chunqian; Fu, Jin-Bo; Liu, Jifeng</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 933, Issue 2, id.193, 18 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...933..193Z</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...933..180G</TD>
<TD>The Time Domain Spectroscopic Survey: Changing-look Quasar Candidates from Multi-epoch Spectroscopy in SDSS-IV</TD>
<TD>Green, Paul J.; Pulgarin-Duque, Lina; Anderson, Scott F.; MacLeod, Chelsea L.; Eracleous, Michael; Ruan, John J.; Runnoe, Jessie; Graham, Matthew; Roulston, Benjamin R.; Schneider, Donald P.; Ahlf, Austin; Bizyaev, Dmitry; Brownstein, Joel R.; del Casal, Sonia Joesephine; Dodd, Sierra A.; Hoover, Daniel; Matt, Cayenne; Merloni, Andrea; Pan, Kaike; Ramirez, Arnulfo; Ridder, Margaret; Moseley, Serena</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 933, Issue 2, id.180, 22 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...933..180G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...933..176S</TD>
<TD>A Late-time Radio Flare Following a Possible Transition in Accretion State in the Tidal Disruption Event AT 2019azh</TD>
<TD>Sfaradi, Itai; Horesh, Assaf; Fender, Rob; Green, David A.; Williams, David R. A.; Bright, Joe; Schulze, Steve</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 933, Issue 2, id.176, 8 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...933..176S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...933..155S</TD>
<TD>Photometry on Structured Backgrounds: Local Pixel-wise Infilling by Regression</TD>
<TD>Saydjari, Andrew K.; Finkbeiner, Douglas P.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 933, Issue 2, id.155, 19 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...933..155S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...933..119L</TD>
<TD>Mass-ratio Distribution of Binaries from the LAMOST-MRS Survey</TD>
<TD>Li, Jiangdan; Li, Jiao; Liu, Chao; Li, Chunqian; Guo, Yanjun; Wang, Luqian; Chen, Xuefei; Xing, Lifeng; Hou, Yonghui; Han, Zhanwen</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 933, Issue 2, id.119, 13 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...933..119L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...933...37W</TD>
<TD>Variable Active Galactic Nuclei in the Galaxy Evolution Explorer Time Domain Survey</TD>
<TD>Wasleske, Erik J.; Baldassare, Vivienne F.; Carroll, Christopher M.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 933, Issue 1, id.37, 14 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...933...37W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...933...31W</TD>
<TD>A Library of Synthetic X-Ray Spectra for Fitting Tidal Disruption Events</TD>
<TD>Wen, Sixiang; Jonker, Peter G.; Stone, Nicholas C.; Zabludoff, Ann I.; Cao, Zheng</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 933, Issue 1, id.31, 15 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...933...31W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...933...14H</TD>
<TD>Bumpy Declining Light Curves Are Common in Hydrogen-poor Superluminous Supernovae</TD>
<TD>Hosseinzadeh, Griffin; Berger, Edo; Metzger, Brian D.; Gomez, Sebastian; Nicholl, Matt; Blanchard, Peter</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 933, Issue 1, id.14, 15 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...933...14H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022AJ....164...23S</TD>
<TD>An ALMA Search for High-albedo Objects Among the Midsized Jupiter Trojan Population</TD>
<TD>Simpson, Anna M.; Brown, Michael E.; Schemel, Madeline J.; Butler, Bryan J.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 164, Issue 1, id.23, 8 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022AJ....164...23S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;C....4000629C</TD>
<TD>Transient simulations for radio surveys</TD>
<TD>Chastain, S. I.; van der Horst, A. J.; Carbone, D.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy and Computing, Volume 40, article id. 100629.</TD>
<TD>2022-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;C....4000629C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;C....4000582S</TD>
<TD>The NASA Multi-Messenger Astrophysics Science Support Center (MOSSAIC)</TD>
<TD>Sambruna, R. M.; Schlieder, J. E.; Kocevski, D.; Caputo, R.; Hui, M. C.; Markwardt, C. B.; Powell, B. P.; Racusin, J. L.; Roberts, C.; Singer, L. P.; Smale, A. P.; Venters, T. M.; Wilson-Hodge, C. A.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy and Computing, Volume 40, article id. 100582.</TD>
<TD>2022-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;C....4000582S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...663A.139A</TD>
<TD>VLBI imaging of the pre-coalescence SMBHB candidate SDSS J143016.05+230344.4</TD>
<TD>An, Tao; Zhang, Yingkang; Wang, Ailing; Shu, Xinwen; Yang, Huan; Jiang, Ning; Dou, Liming; Pan, Zhen; Wang, Tinggui; Zheng, Zhenya</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 663, id.A139, 9 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...663A.139A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...663A..63Z</TD>
<TD>The 2175 Å bump features in FeLoBAL quasars: One indicator of MW-like dust in the nuclear region of quasars</TD>
<TD>Zhang, Shaohua; Ge, Jian; Ji, Tuo; Jiang, Peng; Luo, Zhijian; Pan, Xiang; Shi, Xiheng; Shu, Chenggang; Wang, Jianguo; Xiao, Hubing; Zhou, Hongyan</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 663, id.A63, 12 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...663A..63Z</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...663A..62P</TD>
<TD>HD 133729: A blue large-amplitude pulsator in orbit around a main-sequence B-type star</TD>
<TD>Pigulski, A.; Kotysz, K.; Kołaczek-Szymański, P. A.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 663, id.A62, 10 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...663A..62P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...663A..13L</TD>
<TD>Fink: Early supernovae Ia classification using active learning</TD>
<TD>Leoni, M.; Ishida, E. E. O.; Peloton, J.; Möller, A.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 663, id.A13, 10 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...663A..13L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...663A...5M</TD>
<TD>TUVOpipe: A pipeline to search for UV transients with Swift-UVOT</TD>
<TD>Modiano, David; Wijnands, Rudy; Parikh, Aastha; van Opijnen, Jari; Verberne, Sill; van Etten, Marieke</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 663, id.A5, 30 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...663A...5M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022PhyOJ..15...77B</TD>
<TD>Neutrinos from a Black Hole Snack</TD>
<TD>Buchanan, Mark</TD>
<TD>Physics, Volume 15, article id. 77</TD>
<TD>2022-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022PhyOJ..15...77B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022PhRvL.128v1101R</TD>
<TD>Candidate Tidal Disruption Event AT2019fdr Coincident with a High-Energy Neutrino</TD>
<TD>Reusch, Simeon; Stein, Robert; Kowalski, Marek; van Velzen, Sjoert; Franckowiak, Anna; Lunardini, Cecilia; Murase, Kohta; Winter, Walter; Miller-Jones, James C. A.; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Gilfanov, Marat; Garrappa, Simone; Paliya, Vaidehi S.; Ahumada, Tomás; Anand, Shreya; Barbarino, Cristina; Bellm, Eric C.; Brinnel, Valéry; Buson, Sara; Cenko, S. Bradley; Coughlin, Michael W.; De, Kishalay; Dekany, Richard; Frederick, Sara; Gal-Yam, Avishay; Gezari, Suvi; Giroletti, Marcello; Graham, Matthew J.; Karambelkar, Viraj; Kimura, Shigeo S.; Kong, Albert K. H.; Kool, Erik C.; Laher, Russ R.; Medvedev, Pavel; Necker, Jannis; Nordin, Jakob; Perley, Daniel A.; Rigault, Mickael; Rusholme, Ben; Schulze, Steve; Schweyer, Tassilo; Singer, Leo P.; Sollerman, Jesper; Strotjohann, Nora Linn; Sunyaev, Rashid; van Santen, Jakob; Walters, Richard; Zhang, B. Theodore; Zimmerman, Erez</TD>
<TD>Physical Review Letters, Volume 128, Issue 22, article id.221101</TD>
<TD>2022-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022PhRvL.128v1101R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022PASP..134f5001B</TD>
<TD>Laboratory and On-sky Testing of an InGaAs Detector for Infrared Imaging</TD>
<TD>Batty, Kristoffor; Steele, Iain; Copperwheat, Chris</TD>
<TD>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 134, Issue 1036, id.065001, 14 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022PASP..134f5001B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.513L..57L</TD>
<TD>Confirming new changing-look AGNs discovered through optical variability using a random forest-based light-curve classifier</TD>
<TD>López-Navas, E.; Martínez-Aldama, M. L.; Bernal, S.; Sánchez-Sáez, P.; Arévalo, P.; Graham, Matthew J.; Hernández-García, L.; Lira, P.; Rojas Lobos, P. A.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 513, Issue 1, pp.L57-L62</TD>
<TD>2022-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.513L..57L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.513.3050B</TD>
<TD>Characterizing eclipsing white dwarf M dwarf binaries from multiband eclipse photometry</TD>
<TD>Brown, Alex J.; Parsons, Steven G.; Littlefair, Stuart P.; Wild, James F.; Ashley, R. P.; Breedt, E.; Dhillon, V. S.; Dyer, M. J.; Green, M. J.; Kerry, P.; Marsh, T. R.; Pelisoli, I.; Sahman, D. I.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 513, Issue 2, pp.3050-3064</TD>
<TD>2022-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.513.3050B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.513.3035M</TD>
<TD>The detection efficiency of Type Ia supernovae from the Zwicky Transient Facility: limits on the intrinsic rate of early flux excesses</TD>
<TD>Magee, M. R.; Cuddy, C.; Maguire, K.; Deckers, M.; Dhawan, S.; Frohmaier, C.; Miller, A. A.; Nordin, J.; Coughlin, M. W.; Feinstein, F.; Riddle, R.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 513, Issue 2, pp.3035-3049</TD>
<TD>2022-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.513.3035M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.513.2777K</TD>
<TD>The long-active afterglow of GRB 210204A: detection of the most delayed flares in a gamma-ray burst</TD>
<TD>Kumar, Harsh; Gupta, Rahul; Saraogi, Divita; Ahumada, Tomás; Andreoni, Igor; Anupama, G. C.; Aryan, Amar; Barway, Sudhanshu; Bhalerao, Varun; Chandra, Poonam; Coughlin, Michael W.; Dimple; Dutta, Anirban; ghosh, Ankur; Ho, Anna Y. Q.; Kool, E. C.; Kumar, Amit; Medford, Michael S.; Misra, Kuntal; Pandey, Shashi B.; Perley, Daniel A.; Riddle, Reed; Ror, Amit Kumar; Setiadi, Jason M.; Yao, Yuhan</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 513, Issue 2, pp.2777-2793</TD>
<TD>2022-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.513.2777K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.513.2422L</TD>
<TD>The prospects of finding tidal disruption events with 2.5-m Wide-Field Survey Telescope based on mock observations</TD>
<TD>Lin, Zheyu; Jiang, Ning; Kong, Xu</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 513, Issue 2, pp.2422-2436</TD>
<TD>2022-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.513.2422L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.513.2215R</TD>
<TD>The OmegaWhite survey for short-period variable stars - VII. High amplitude short-period blue variables</TD>
<TD>Ramsay, Gavin; Woudt, Patrick A.; Kupfer, Thomas; van Roestel, Jan; Paterson, Kerry; Warner, Brian; Buckley, David A. H.; Groot, Paul J.; Heber, Ulrich; Irrgang, Andreas; Jeffery, C. Simon; Motsoaledi, Mokhine; Schwartz, Martinus J.; Wevers, Thomas</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 513, Issue 2, pp.2215-2225</TD>
<TD>2022-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.513.2215R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.513.2152C</TD>
<TD>A standard siren cosmological measurement from the potential GW190521 electromagnetic counterpart ZTF19abanrhr</TD>
<TD>Chen, Hsin-Yu; Haster, Carl-Johan; Vitale, Salvatore; Farr, Will M.; Isi, Maximiliano</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 513, Issue 2, pp.2152-2157</TD>
<TD>2022-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.513.2152C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.513.1742G</TD>
<TD>Machine learning for fast transients for the Deeper, Wider, Faster programme with the Removal Of BOgus Transients (ROBOT) pipeline</TD>
<TD>Goode, Simon; Cooke, Jeff; Zhang, Jielai; Mahabal, Ashish; Webb, Sara; Hegarty, Sarah</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 513, Issue 2, pp.1742-1754</TD>
<TD>2022-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.513.1742G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.513..468T</TD>
<TD>The OmegaWhite survey for short-period variable stars - VI. Open clusters</TD>
<TD>Toma, R.; Ramsay, G.; Jeffery, C. S.; Macfarlane, S. A.; Woudt, P.; Groot, P. J.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 513, Issue 1, pp.468-486</TD>
<TD>2022-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.513..468T</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.513..420B</TD>
<TD>Periodic stellar variability from almost a million NGTS light curves</TD>
<TD>Briegal, Joshua T.; Gillen, Edward; Queloz, Didier; Hodgkin, Simon; Acton, Jack S.; Anderson, David R.; Armstrong, David J.; Battley, Matthew P.; Bayliss, Daniel; Burleigh, Matthew R.; Bryant, Edward M.; Casewell, Sarah L.; Costes, Jean C.; Eigmüller, Philipp; Gill, Samuel; Goad, Michael R.; Günther, Maximilian N.; Henderson, Beth A.; Jackman, James A. G.; Jenkins, James S.; Kreutzer, Lars T.; Moyano, Maximiliano; Lendl, Monika; Smith, Gareth D.; Tilbrook, Rosanna H.; Watson, Christopher A.; West, Richard G.; Wheatley, Peter J.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 513, Issue 1, pp.420-438</TD>
<TD>2022-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.513..420B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.512.6122C</TD>
<TD>The SN Ia runaway LP 398-9: detection of circumstellar material and surface rotation</TD>
<TD>Chandra, Vedant; Hwang, Hsiang-Chih; Zakamska, Nadia L.; Blouin, Simon; Swan, Andrew; Marsh, Thomas R.; Shen, Ken J.; Gänsicke, Boris T.; Hermes, J. J.; Putterman, Odelia; Bauer, Evan B.; Petrosky, Evan; Dhillon, Vikram S.; Littlefair, Stuart P.; Ashley, Richard P.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 512, Issue 4, pp.6122-6133</TD>
<TD>2022-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.512.6122C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.512.6054R</TD>
<TD>A step towards unveiling the nature of three cataclysmic variables: LS Cam, V902 Mon, and SWIFT J0746.3-1608</TD>
<TD>Rawat, Nikita; Pandey, J. C.; Joshi, Arti; Yadava, Umesh</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 512, Issue 4, pp.6054-6066</TD>
<TD>2022-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.512.6054R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.512.5620E</TD>
<TD>Unicorns and giraffes in the binary zoo: stripped giants with subgiant companions</TD>
<TD>El-Badry, Kareem; Seeburger, Rhys; Jayasinghe, Tharindu; Rix, Hans-Walter; Almada, Silvia; Conroy, Charlie; Price-Whelan, Adrian M.; Burdge, Kevin</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 512, Issue 4, pp.5620-5641</TD>
<TD>2022-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.512.5620E</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.512.5440V</TD>
<TD>Discovery and characterization of five new eclipsing AM CVn systems</TD>
<TD>van Roestel, J.; Kupfer, T.; Green, M. J.; Wong, T. L. S.; Bildsten, L.; Burdge, K.; Prince, T.; Marsh, T. R.; Szkody, P.; Fremling, C.; Graham, M. J.; Dhillon, V. S.; Littlefair, S. P.; Bellm, E. C.; Coughlin, M.; Duev, D. A.; Goldstein, D. A.; Laher, R. R.; Rusholme, B.; Riddle, R.; Dekany, R.; Kulkarni, S. R.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 512, Issue 4, pp.5440-5461</TD>
<TD>2022-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.512.5440V</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022JHEAp..34...49A</TD>
<TD>Cosmology intertwined: A review of the particle physics, astrophysics, and cosmology associated with the cosmological tensions and anomalies</TD>
<TD>Abdalla, Elcio; Abellán, Guillermo Franco; Aboubrahim, Amin; Agnello, Adriano; Akarsu, Özgür; Akrami, Yashar; Alestas, George; Aloni, Daniel; Amendola, Luca; Anchordoqui, Luis A.; Anderson, Richard I.; Arendse, Nikki; Asgari, Marika; Ballardini, Mario; Barger, Vernon; Basilakos, Spyros; Batista, Ronaldo C.; Battistelli, Elia S.; Battye, Richard; Benetti, Micol; Benisty, David; Berlin, Asher; de Bernardis, Paolo; Berti, Emanuele; Bidenko, Bohdan; Birrer, Simon; Blakeslee, John P.; Boddy, Kimberly K.; Bom, Clecio R.; Bonilla, Alexander; Borghi, Nicola; Bouchet, François R.; Braglia, Matteo; Buchert, Thomas; Buckley-Geer, Elizabeth; Calabrese, Erminia; Caldwell, Robert R.; Camarena, David; Capozziello, Salvatore; Casertano, Stefano; Chen, Geoff C. -F.; Chluba, Jens; Chen, Angela; Chen, Hsin-Yu; Chudaykin, Anton; Cicoli, Michele; Copi, Craig J.; Courbin, Fred; Cyr-Racine, Francis-Yan; Czerny, Bożena; Dainotti, Maria; D'Amico, Guido; Davis, Anne-Christine; de Cruz Pérez, Javier; de Haro, Jaume; Delabrouille, Jacques; Denton, Peter B.; Dhawan, Suhail; Dienes, Keith R.; Di Valentino, Eleonora; Du, Pu; Eckert, Dominique; Escamilla-Rivera, Celia; Ferté, Agnès; Finelli, Fabio; Fosalba, Pablo; Freedman, Wendy L.; Frusciante, Noemi; Gaztañaga, Enrique; Giarè, William; Giusarma, Elena; Gómez-Valent, Adrià; Handley, Will; Harrison, Ian; Hart, Luke; Hazra, Dhiraj Kumar; Heavens, Alan; Heinesen, Asta; Hildebrandt, Hendrik; Hill, J. Colin; Hogg, Natalie B.; Holz, Daniel E.; Hooper, Deanna C.; Hosseininejad, Nikoo; Huterer, Dragan; Ishak, Mustapha; Ivanov, Mikhail M.; Jaffe, Andrew H.; Jang, In Sung; Jedamzik, Karsten; Jimenez, Raul; Joseph, Melissa; Joudaki, Shahab; Kamionkowski, Marc; Karwal, Tanvi; Kazantzidis, Lavrentios; Keeley, Ryan E.; Klasen, Michael; Komatsu, Eiichiro; Koopmans, Léon V. E.; Kumar, Suresh; Lamagna, Luca; Lazkoz, Ruth; Lee, Chung-Chi; Lesgourgues, Julien; Levi Said, Jackson; Lewis, Tiffany R.; L'Huillier, Benjamin; Lucca, Matteo; Maartens, Roy; Macri, Lucas M.; Marfatia, Danny; Marra, Valerio; Martins, Carlos J. A. P.; Masi, Silvia; Matarrese, Sabino; Mazumdar, Arindam; Melchiorri, Alessandro; Mena, Olga; Mersini-Houghton, Laura; Mertens, James; Milaković, Dinko; Minami, Yuto; Miranda, Vivian; Moreno-Pulido, Cristian; Moresco, Michele; Mota, David F.; Mottola, Emil; Mozzon, Simone; Muir, Jessica; Mukherjee, Ankan; Mukherjee, Suvodip; Naselsky, Pavel; Nath, Pran; Nesseris, Savvas; Niedermann, Florian; Notari, Alessio; Nunes, Rafael C.; Ó Colgáin, Eoin; Owens, Kayla A.; Özülker, Emre; Pace, Francesco; Paliathanasis, Andronikos; Palmese, Antonella; Pan, Supriya; Paoletti, Daniela; Perez Bergliaffa, Santiago E.; Perivolaropoulos, Leandros; Pesce, Dominic W.; Pettorino, Valeria; Philcox, Oliver H. E.; Pogosian, Levon; Poulin, Vivian; Poulot, Gaspard; Raveri, Marco; Reid, Mark J.; Renzi, Fabrizio; Riess, Adam G.; Sabla, Vivian I.; Salucci, Paolo; Salzano, Vincenzo; Saridakis, Emmanuel N.; Sathyaprakash, Bangalore S.; Schmaltz, Martin; Schöneberg, Nils; Scolnic, Dan; Sen, Anjan A.; Sehgal, Neelima; Shafieloo, Arman; Sheikh-Jabbari, M. M.; Silk, Joseph; Silvestri, Alessandra; Skara, Foteini; Sloth, Martin S.; Soares-Santos, Marcelle; Solà Peracaula, Joan; Songsheng, Yu-Yang; Soriano, Jorge F.; Staicova, Denitsa; Starkman, Glenn D.; Szapudi, István; Teixeira, Elsa M.; Thomas, Brooks; Treu, Tommaso; Trott, Emery; van de Bruck, Carsten; Vazquez, J. Alberto; Verde, Licia; Visinelli, Luca; Wang, Deng; Wang, Jian-Min; Wang, Shao-Jiang; Watkins, Richard; Watson, Scott; Webb, John K.; Weiner, Neal; Weltman, Amanda; Witte, Samuel J.; Wojtak, Radosław; Yadav, Anil Kumar; Yang, Weiqiang; Zhao, Gong-Bo; Zumalacárregui, Miguel</TD>
<TD>Journal of High Energy Astrophysics, Volume 34, p. 49-211.</TD>
<TD>2022-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022JHEAp..34...49A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022JApA...43...11G</TD>
<TD>Revealing nature of GRB 210205A, ZTF21aaeyldq (AT2021any) and follow-up observations with the 4K×4K CCD imager + 3.6m DOT</TD>
<TD>Gupta, Rahul; Kumar, Amit; Pandey, Shashi Bhushan; Castro-Tirado, A. J.; Ghosh, Ankur; Dimple, Hu, Y. -D.; Fernández-García, E.; Caballero-García, M. D.; Castro-Tirado, M. Á.; Hedrosa, R. P.; Hermelo, I.; Vico, I.; Misra, Kuntal; Kumar, Brajesh; Aryan, Amar; Tiwari, Sugriva Nath</TD>
<TD>Journal of Astrophysics and Astronomy, Volume 43, Issue 1, article id.11</TD>
<TD>2022-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022JApA...43...11G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022JApA...43....9A</TD>
<TD>Optical flux and spectral characterization of the blazar PG 1553 + 113 based on the past 15 years of data</TD>
<TD>Agarwal, Aditi; Mihov, B.; Andruchow, I.; Cellone, Sergio A.; Anupama, G. C.; Agrawal, V.; Zola, S.; Özdönmez, Aykut; Ege, Ergün</TD>
<TD>Journal of Astrophysics and Astronomy, Volume 43, Issue 1, article id.9</TD>
<TD>2022-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022JApA...43....9A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022Geote..56..382R</TD>
<TD>Influence of Tectonic Factor on Porphyry Copper Deposits Localization and Distribution (Arasbaran District, NW Iran): Synthesis of Alteration Patterns and Lineaments Using Digital Techniques</TD>
<TD>Ramezani, T.; Maanijou, M.; Taghavi, A.; Lentz, D. R.</TD>
<TD>Geotectonics, Volume 56, Issue 3, p.382-403</TD>
<TD>2022-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022Geote..56..382R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022Galax..10...76S</TD>
<TD>Compact Binary Coalescences: Astrophysical Processes and Lessons Learned</TD>
<TD>Spera, Mario; Trani, Alessandro Alberto; Mencagli, Mattia</TD>
<TD>Galaxies, vol. 10, issue 4, p. 76</TD>
<TD>2022-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022Galax..10...76S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022EPJC...82..517B</TD>
<TD>A pure hadronic model description of the observed neutrino emission from the tidal disruption event AT2019dsg</TD>
<TD>Banik, Prabir; Bhadra, Arunava</TD>
<TD>The European Physical Journal C, Volume 82, Issue 6, article id.517</TD>
<TD>2022-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022EPJC...82..517B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJS..260...46I</TD>
<TD>The OGLE Collection of Variable Stars: Nearly 66,000 Mira Stars in the Milky Way</TD>
<TD>Iwanek, Patryk; Soszyński, Igor; Kozłowski, Szymon; Poleski, Radosław; Pietrukowicz, Paweł; Skowron, Jan; Wrona, Marcin; Mróz, Przemysław; Udalski, Andrzej; Szymański, Michał K.; Skowron, Dorota M.; Ulaczyk, Krzysztof; Gromadzki, Mariusz; Rybicki, Krzysztof; Ratajczak, Milena</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 260, Issue 2, id.46, 15 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJS..260...46I</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...932L..25L</TD>
<TD>GB6 J2113+1121: A Multiwavelength Flaring γ-Ray Blazar Temporally and Spatially Coincident with the Neutrino Event IceCube-191001A</TD>
<TD>Liao, Neng-Hui; Sheng, Zhen-Feng; Jiang, Ning; Chang, Yu-Ling; Wang, Yi-Bo; Xu, Dong-Lian; Shu, Xin-Wen; Fan, Yi-Zhong; Wang, Ting-Gui</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 932, Issue 2, id.L25, 10 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...932L..25L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...932L...8H</TD>
<TD>Optical Light Curve of 4FGL J0935.3+0901: A Flaring Black Widow Candidate</TD>
<TD>Halpern, Jules P.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 932, Issue 1, id.L8, 6 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...932L...8H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...932L...5C</TD>
<TD>The Large Superfast Rotators Discovered by the Zwicky Transient Facility</TD>
<TD>Chang, Chan-Kao; Yeh, Ting-Shuo; Tan, HanJie; Ip, Wing-Huen; Kelley, Michael S. P.; Ye, Quanzhi; Lin, Zhong-Yi; Ngeow, Chow-Choong; Bolin, Bryce T.; Prince, Thomas. A.; Bellm, Eric C.; Dekany, Richard; Duev, Dmitry A.; Graham, Matthew; Zwicky Transient Facility Collaboration</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 932, Issue 1, id.L5, 7 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...932L...5C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...932L...2A</TD>
<TD>A Speed Bump: SN 2021aefx Shows that Doppler Shift Alone Can Explain Early Excess Blue Flux in Some Type Ia Supernovae</TD>
<TD>Ashall, C.; Lu, J.; Shappee, B. J.; Burns, C. R.; Hsiao, E. Y.; Kumar, S.; Morrell, N.; Phillips, M. M.; Shahbandeh, M.; Baron, E.; Boutsia, K.; Brown, P. J.; DerKacy, J. M.; Galbany, L.; Hoeflich, P.; Krisciunas, K.; Mazzali, P.; Piro, A. L.; Stritzinger, M. D.; Suntzeff, N. B.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 932, Issue 1, id.L2, 8 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...932L...2A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...932..118C</TD>
<TD>Searching for Anomalies in the ZTF Catalog of Periodic Variable Stars</TD>
<TD>Chan, Ho-Sang; Villar, V. Ashley; Cheung, Siu-Hei; Ho, Shirley; O'Grady, Anna J. G.; Drout, Maria R.; Renzo, Mathieu</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 932, Issue 2, id.118, 21 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...932..118C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...932..116H</TD>
<TD>Luminous Millimeter, Radio, and X-Ray Emission from ZTF 20acigmel (AT 2020xnd)</TD>
<TD>Ho, Anna Y. Q.; Margalit, Ben; Bremer, Michael; Perley, Daniel A.; Yao, Yuhan; Dobie, Dougal; Kaplan, David L.; O'Brien, Andrew; Petitpas, Glen; Zic, Andrew</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 932, Issue 2, id.116, 21 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...932..116H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...932...58J</TD>
<TD>The Circumstellar Environments of Double-peaked, Calcium-strong Transients 2021gno and 2021inl</TD>
<TD>Jacobson-Galán, W. V.; Venkatraman, P.; Margutti, R.; Khatami, D.; Terreran, G.; Foley, R. J.; Angulo, R.; Angus, C. R.; Auchettl, K.; Blanchard, P. K.; Bobrick, A.; Bright, J. S.; Brout, D.; Chambers, K. C.; Couch, C. D.; Coulter, D. A.; Clever, K.; Davis, K. W.; de Boer, T. J. L.; DeMarchi, L.; Dodd, S. A.; Jones, D. O.; Johnson, J.; Kilpatrick, C. D.; Khetan, N.; Lai, Z.; Langeroodi, D.; Lin, C. -C.; Magnier, E. A.; Milisavljevic, D.; Perets, H. B.; Pierel, J. D. R.; Raymond, J.; Rest, S.; Rest, A.; Ridden-Harper, R.; Shen, K. J.; Siebert, M. R.; Smith, C.; Taggart, K.; Tinyanont, S.; Valdes, F.; Villar, V. A.; Wang, Q.; Yadavalli, S. K.; Zenati, Y.; Zenteno, A.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 932, Issue 1, id.58, 25 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...932...58J</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...932...45O</TD>
<TD>NICER Monitoring of Supersoft X-Ray Sources</TD>
<TD>Orio, M.; Gendreau, K.; Giese, M.; Luna, G. J. M.; Magdolen, J.; Pei, S.; Sun, B.; Behar, E.; Dobrotka, A.; Mikolajewska, J.; Pasham, Dheeraj R.; Strohmayer, T. E.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 932, Issue 1, id.45, 19 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...932...45O</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...932...40A</TD>
<TD>In Search of Short Gamma-Ray Burst Optical Counterparts with the Zwicky Transient Facility</TD>
<TD>Ahumada, Tomás; Anand, Shreya; Coughlin, Michael W.; Andreoni, Igor; Kool, Erik C.; Kumar, Harsh; Reusch, Simeon; Sagués-Carracedo, Ana; Stein, Robert; Cenko, S. Bradley; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Singer, Leo P.; Dunwoody, Rachel; Mangan, Joseph; Bhalerao, Varun; Bulla, Mattia; Burns, Eric; Graham, Matthew J.; Kaplan, David L.; Perley, Daniel; Almualla, Mouza; Bloom, Joshua S.; Cunningham, Virginia; De, Kishalay; Gatkine, Pradip; Ho, Anna Y. Q.; Karambelkar, Viraj; Kong, Albert K. H.; Yao, Yuhan; Anupama, G. C.; Barway, Sudhanshu; Ghosh, Shaon; Itoh, Ryosuke; McBreen, Sheila; Bellm, Eric C.; Fremling, Christoffer; Laher, Russ R.; Mahabal, Ashish A.; Riddle, Reed L.; Rosnet, Philippe; Rusholme, Ben; Smith, Roger; Sollerman, Jesper; Bissaldi, Elisabetta; Fletcher, Corinne; Hamburg, Rachel; Mailyan, Bagrat; Malacaria, Christian; Roberts, Oliver</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 932, Issue 1, id.40, 19 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...932...40A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...932....1R</TD>
<TD>The Peculiar Short-duration GRB 200826A and Its Supernova</TD>
<TD>Rossi, A.; Rothberg, B.; Palazzi, E.; Kann, D. A.; D'Avanzo, P.; Amati, L.; Klose, S.; Perego, A.; Pian, E.; Guidorzi, C.; Pozanenko, A. S.; Savaglio, S.; Stratta, G.; Agapito, G.; Covino, S.; Cusano, F.; D'Elia, V.; De Pasquale, M.; Della Valle, M.; Kuhn, O.; Izzo, L.; Loffredo, E.; Masetti, N.; Melandri, A.; Minaev, P. Y.; Guelbenzu, A. Nicuesa; Paris, D.; Paiano, S.; Plantet, C.; Rossi, F.; Salvaterra, R.; Schulze, S.; Veillet, C.; Volnova, A. A.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 932, Issue 1, id.1, 15 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...932....1R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022AJ....163..298M</TD>
<TD>TOI-1696: A Nearby M4 Dwarf with a 3 R &lt;SUB&gt;⊕&lt;/SUB&gt; Planet in the Neptunian Desert</TD>
<TD>Mori, Mayuko; Livingston, John H.; Leon, Jerome de; Narita, Norio; Hirano, Teruyuki; Fukui, Akihiko; Collins, Karen A.; Fujita, Naho; Hori, Yasunori; Ishikawa, Hiroyuki Tako; Kawauchi, Kiyoe; Stassun, Keivan G.; Watanabe, Noriharu; Giacalone, Steven; Gore, Rebecca; Schroeder, Ashley; Dressing, Courtney D.; Bieryla, Allyson; Jensen, Eric L. N.; Massey, Bob; Shporer, Avi; Kuzuhara, Masayuki; Charbonneau, David; Ciardi, David R.; Doty, John P.; Esparza-Borges, Emma; Harakawa, Hiroki; Hodapp, Klaus; Ikoma, Masahiro; Ikuta, Kai; Isogai, Keisuke; Jenkins, Jon M.; Kagetani, Taiki; Kimura, Tadahiro; Kodama, Takanori; Kotani, Takayuki; Krishnamurthy, Vigneshwaran; Kudo, Tomoyuki; Kurita, Seiya; Kurokawa, Takashi; Kusakabe, Nobuhiko; Latham, David W.; McLean, Brian; Murgas, Felipe; Nishikawa, Jun; Nishiumi, Taku; Omiya, Masashi; Osborn, Hugh P.; Palle, Enric; Parviainen, Hannu; Ricker, George R.; Seager, Sara; Serizawa, Takuma; Teng, Huan-Yu; Terada, Yuka; Twicken, Joseph D.; Ueda, Akitoshi; Vanderspek, Roland; Vievard, Sébastien; Winn, Joshua N.; Zou, Yujie; Tamura, Motohide</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 163, Issue 6, id.298, 19 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022AJ....163..298M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022AJ....163..286B</TD>
<TD>TOI-1696 and TOI-2136: Constraining the Masses of Two Mini-Neptunes with the Habitable-Zone Planet Finder</TD>
<TD>Beard, Corey; Robertson, Paul; Kanodia, Shubham; Libby-Roberts, Jessica; Cañas, Caleb I.; Gupta, Arvind F.; Holcomb, Rae; Jones, Sinclaire; Kobulnicky, Henry A.; Lin, Andrea S. J.; Lubin, Jack; Maney, Marissa; Parker, Brock A.; Stefánsson, Guðmundur; Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; Hebb, Leslie; Mahadevan, Suvrath; Wisniewski, John; Bender, Chad F.; Diddams, Scott A.; Everett, Mark; Fredrick, Connor; Halverson, Samuel; Hearty, Fred; Metcalf, Andrew J.; Monson, Andrew; Ninan, Joe P.; Roy, Arpita; Schutte, Maria; Schwab, Christian; Terrien, Ryan C.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 163, Issue 6, id.286, 20 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022AJ....163..286B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022AJ....163..275A</TD>
<TD>A Young, Low-density Stellar Stream in the Milky Way Disk: Theia 456</TD>
<TD>Andrews, Jeff J.; Curtis, Jason L.; Chanamé, Julio; Agüeros, Marcel A.; Schuler, Simon C.; Kounkel, Marina; Covey, Kevin R.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 163, Issue 6, id.275, 10 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022AJ....163..275A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022AJ....163..263H</TD>
<TD>A Zwicky Transient Facility Look at Optical Variability of Young Stellar Objects in the North America and Pelican Nebulae Complex</TD>
<TD>Hillenbrand, Lynne A.; Kiker, Thaddaeus J.; Gee, Miles; Lester, Owen; Braunfeld, Noah L.; Rebull, Luisa M.; Kuhn, Michael A.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 163, Issue 6, id.263, 18 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022AJ....163..263H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022AJ....163..257A</TD>
<TD>Activity and Rotation of Nearby Field M Dwarfs in the TESS Southern Continuous Viewing Zone</TD>
<TD>Anthony, Francys; Núñez, Alejandro; Agüeros, Marcel A.; Curtis, Jason L.; do Nascimento, J. -D., Jr.; Machado, João M.; Mann, Andrew W.; Newton, Elisabeth R.; Rampalli, Rayna; Thao, Pa Chia; Wood, Mackenna L.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 163, Issue 6, id.257, 12 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022AJ....163..257A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022AJ....163..250Y</TD>
<TD>Magnetic Activity on Four Short-period Contact Binaries: V0576 Peg, KW Psc, V0873 Per, and FY Boo</TD>
<TD>Yang, Yuangui; Yuan, Huiyu; Wang, Shuang; Dai, Haifeng</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 163, Issue 6, id.250, 16 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022AJ....163..250Y</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022AJ....163..246H</TD>
<TD>Hitting a New Low: The Unique 28 hr Cessation of Accretion in the TESS Light Curve of YY Dra (DO Dra)</TD>
<TD>Hill, Katherine L.; Littlefield, Colin; Garnavich, Peter; Scaringi, Simone; Szkody, Paula; Mason, Paul A.; Kennedy, Mark R.; Shaw, Aarran W.; Covington, Ava E.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 163, Issue 6, id.246, 9 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022AJ....163..246H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...662A.116O</TD>
<TD>XMM-Newton and TESS observations of the highly variable polar V496 UMa</TD>
<TD>Ok, Samet; Schwope, Axel</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 662, id.A116, 12 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...662A.116O</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...662A.109S</TD>
<TD>AutoSourceID-Light. Fast optical source localization via U-Net and Laplacian of Gaussian</TD>
<TD>Stoppa, F.; Vreeswijk, P.; Bloemen, S.; Bhattacharyya, S.; Caron, S.; Jóhannesson, G.; Ruiz de Austri, R.; van den Oetelaar, C.; Zaharijas, G.; Groot, P. J.; Cator, E.; Nelemans, G.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 662, id.A109, 8 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...662A.109S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022A&amp;A...662A..40C</TD>
<TD>The population of hot subdwarf stars studied with Gaia. IV. Catalogues of hot subluminous stars based on Gaia EDR3</TD>
<TD>Culpan, R.; Geier, S.; Reindl, N.; Pelisoli, I.; Gentile Fusillo, N.; Vorontseva, A.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 662, id.A40, 19 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022A&amp;A...662A..40C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022Univ....8..304L</TD>
<TD>Infrared Spectral Energy Distribution and Variability of Active Galactic Nuclei: Clues to the Structure of Circumnuclear Material</TD>
<TD>Lyu, Jianwei; Rieke, George</TD>
<TD>Universe, vol. 8, issue 6, p. 304</TD>
<TD>2022-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022Univ....8..304L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022Univ....8..303S</TD>
<TD>Antarctic Survey Telescope 3-3: Overview, System Performance and Preliminary Observations at Yaoan, Yunnan</TD>
<TD>Sun, Tianrui; Li, Xiaoyan; Hu, Lei; Meng, Kelai; Han, Zijian; Hu, Maokai; Li, Zhengyang; Wen, Haikun; Du, Fujia; Yang, Shihai; Gu, Bozhong; Yuan, Xiangyan; Li, Yun; Wang, Huihui; Liu, Lei; Zhu, Zhenxi; Huang, Xuehai; Lei, Chengming; Wang, Lifan; Wu, Xuefeng</TD>
<TD>Universe, vol. 8, issue 6, p. 303</TD>
<TD>2022-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022Univ....8..303S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022RAA....22e5005Y</TD>
<TD>Detecting and Monitoring Tidal Dissipation of Hot Jupiters in the Era of SiTian</TD>
<TD>Yang, Fan; Wang, Wei; Wei, Xing; Zhang, Hui; Zhou, Ji-Lin; Shan, Su-Su; Zheng, Jie; Zong, Wei-Kai; Yang, Ming; Bai, Yu; Wang, Song; Zheng, Jia-Chen; Xu, Yu-Ru; Li, Yu-Feng; Lu, You-Jun; Liu, Ji-Feng</TD>
<TD>Research in Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 22, Issue 5, id.055005, 11 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022RAA....22e5005Y</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022PSJ.....3..123R</TD>
<TD>Apophis Planetary Defense Campaign</TD>
<TD>Reddy, Vishnu; Kelley, Michael S.; Dotson, Jessie; Farnocchia, Davide; Erasmus, Nicolas; Polishook, David; Masiero, Joseph; Benner, Lance A. M.; Bauer, James; Alarcon, Miguel R.; Balam, David; Bamberger, Daniel; Bell, David; Barnardi, Fabrizio; Bressi, Terry H.; Brozovic, Marina; Brucker, Melissa J.; Buzzi, Luca; Cano, Juan; Cantillo, David; Cennamo, Ramona; Chastel, Serge; Chingis, Omarov; Choi, Young-Jun; Christensen, Eric; Denneau, Larry; Dróżdż, Marek; Elenin, Leonid; Erece, Orhan; Faggioli, Laura; Falco, Carmelo; Glamazda, Dmitry; Graziani, Filippo; Heinze, Aren N.; Holman, Matthew J.; Ivanov, Alexander; Jacques, Cristovao; Janse van Rensburg, Petro; Kaiser, Galina; Kamiński, Krzysztof; Kamińska, Monika K.; Kaplan, Murat; Kim, Dong-Heun; Kim, Myung-Jin; Kiss, Csaba; Kokina, Tatiana; Kuznetsov, Eduard; Larsen, Jeffrey A.; Lee, Hee-Jae; Lees, Robert C.; de León, Julia; Licandro, Javier; Mainzer, Amy; Marciniak, Anna; Marsset, Michael; Mastaler, Ron A.; Mathias, Donovan L.; McMillan, Robert S.; Medeiros, Hissa; Micheli, Marco; Mokhnatkin, Artem; Moon, Hong-Kyu; Morate, David; Naidu, Shantanu P.; Nastasi, Alessandro; Novichonok, Artem; Ogłoza, Waldemar; Pál, András; Pérez-Toledo, Fabricio; Perminov, Alexander; Petrescu, Elisabeta; Popescu, Marcel; Read, Mike T.; Reichart, Daniel E.; Reva, Inna; Roh, Dong-Goo; Rumpf, Clemens; Satpathy, Akash; Schmalz, Sergei; Scotti, James V.; Serebryanskiy, Aleksander; Serra-Ricart, Miquel; Sonbas, Eda; Szakáts, Robert; Taylor, Patrick A.; Tonry, John L.; Tubbiolo, Andrew F.; Veres, Peter; Wainscoat, Richard; Warner, Elizabeth; Weiland, Henry J.; Wells, Guy; Weryk, Robert; Wheeler, Lorien F.; Wiebe, Yulia; Yim, Hong-Suh; Żejmo, Michał; Zhornichenko, Anastasiya; Zoła, Stanisław; Michel, Patrick</TD>
<TD>The Planetary Science Journal, Volume 3, Issue 5, id.123, 16 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022PSJ.....3..123R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022OEJV..229....1C</TD>
<TD>New Semiregular Variable Star Near The Wizard Nebula - Evolution of the Red Giant MACOMP_V1</TD>
<TD>Conzo, G.; Moriconi, M.; Marotta, P. G.</TD>
<TD>Open European Journal on Variable stars, Vol. 229, p. 1-8.</TD>
<TD>2022-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022OEJV..229....1C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022Natur.606..236W</TD>
<TD>`Unsustainable': how satellite swarms pose a rising threat to astronomy</TD>
<TD>Witze, Alexandra</TD>
<TD>Nature, Volume 606, Issue 7913, p.236-237</TD>
<TD>2022-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022Natur.606..236W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022Natur.605...41B</TD>
<TD>A 62-minute orbital period black widow binary in a wide hierarchical triple</TD>
<TD>Burdge, Kevin B.; Marsh, Thomas R.; Fuller, Jim; Bellm, Eric C.; Caiazzo, Ilaria; Chakrabarty, Deepto; Coughlin, Michael W.; De, Kishalay; Dhillon, V. S.; Graham, Matthew J.; Rodríguez-Gil, Pablo; Jaodand, Amruta D.; Kaplan, David L.; Kara, Erin; Kong, Albert K. H.; Kulkarni, S. R.; Li, Kwan-Lok; Littlefair, S. P.; Majid, Walid A.; Mróz, Przemek; Pearlman, Aaron B.; Phinney, E. S.; Roestel, Jan van; Simcoe, Robert A.; Andreoni, Igor; Drake, Andrew J.; Dekany, Richard G.; Duev, Dmitry A.; Kool, Erik C.; Mahabal, Ashish A.; Medford, Michael S.; Riddle, Reed; Prince, Thomas A.</TD>
<TD>Nature, Volume 605, Issue 7908, p.41-45</TD>
<TD>2022-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022Natur.605...41B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.512.4484F</TD>
<TD>Close, bright, and boxy: the superluminous SN 2018hti</TD>
<TD>Fiore, A.; Benetti, S.; Nicholl, M.; Reguitti, A.; Cappellaro, E.; Campana, S.; Bose, S.; Paraskeva, E.; Berger, E.; Bravo, T. M.; Burke, J.; Cai, Y. -Z.; Chen, T. -W.; Chen, P.; Ciolfi, R.; Dong, S.; Gomez, S.; Gromadzki, M.; Gutiérrez, C. P.; Hiramatsu, D.; Hosseinzadeh, G.; Howell, D. A.; Jerkstrand, A.; Kankare, E.; Kozyreva, A.; Maguire, K.; McCully, C.; Ochner, P.; Pellegrino, C.; Pignata, G.; Post, R. S.; Elias-Rosa, N.; Shahbandeh, M.; Schuldt, S.; Thomas, B. P.; Tomasella, L.; Vinkó, J.; Vogl, C.; Wheeler, J. C.; Young, D. R.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 512, Issue 3, pp.4484-4502</TD>
<TD>2022-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.512.4484F</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.512.3602P</TD>
<TD>Formation and fate of low-metallicity stars in TNG50</TD>
<TD>Pakmor, Rüdiger; Simpson, Christine M.; van de Voort, Freeke; Hernquist, Lars; van Son, Lieke; Chruślińska, Martyna; Bieri, Rebekka; de Mink, Selma E.; Springel, Volker</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 512, Issue 3, pp.3602-3615</TD>
<TD>2022-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.512.3602P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.512.2841Q</TD>
<TD>The 6 × 2pt method: supernova velocities meet multiple tracers</TD>
<TD>Quartin, Miguel; Amendola, Luca; Moraes, Bruno</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 512, Issue 2, pp.2841-2853</TD>
<TD>2022-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.512.2841Q</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.512.2777T</TD>
<TD>Progenitor and close-in circumstellar medium of type II supernova 2020fqv from high-cadence photometry and ultra-rapid UV spectroscopy</TD>
<TD>Tinyanont, Samaporn; Ridden-Harper, R.; Foley, R. J.; Morozova, V.; Kilpatrick, C. D.; Dimitriadis, G.; DeMarchi, L.; Gagliano, A.; Jacobson-Galán, W. V.; Messick, A.; Pierel, J. D. R.; Piro, A. L.; Ramirez-Ruiz, E.; Siebert, M. R.; Chambers, K. C.; Clever, K. E.; Coulter, D. A.; De, K.; Hankins, M.; Hung, T.; Jha, S. W.; Jimenez Angel, C. E.; Jones, D. O.; Kasliwal, M. M.; Lin, C. -C.; Marques-Chaves, R.; Margutti, R.; Moore, A.; Pérez-Fournon, I.; Poidevin, F.; Rest, A.; Shirley, R.; Smith, C. S.; Strasburger, E.; Swift, J. J.; Wainscoat, R. J.; Wang, Q.; Zenati, Y.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 512, Issue 2, pp.2777-2797</TD>
<TD>2022-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.512.2777T</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.512.1924S</TD>
<TD>Discovery of extreme, roughly daily superflares on the recurrent nova V2487 Oph</TD>
<TD>Schaefer, Bradley E.; Pagnotta, Ashley; Zoppelt, Seth</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 512, Issue 2, pp.1924-1943</TD>
<TD>2022-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.512.1924S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.512.1391S</TD>
<TD>Low-efficiency long gamma-ray bursts: a case study with AT2020blt</TD>
<TD>Sarin, N.; Hamburg, R.; Burns, E.; Ashton, G.; Lasky, P. D.; Lamb, G. P.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 512, Issue 1, pp.1391-1399</TD>
<TD>2022-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.512.1391S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.512.1317D</TD>
<TD>Constraining Type Ia supernova explosions and early flux excesses with the Zwicky Transient Factory</TD>
<TD>Deckers, M.; Maguire, K.; Magee, M. R.; Dimitriadis, G.; Smith, M.; Sainz de Murieta, A.; Miller, A. A.; Goobar, A.; Nordin, J.; Rigault, M.; Bellm, E. C.; Coughlin, M.; Laher, R. R.; Shupe, D. L.; Graham, M.; Kasliwal, M.; Walters, R.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 512, Issue 1, pp.1317-1340</TD>
<TD>2022-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.512.1317D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022MNRAS.512..899W</TD>
<TD>Dust and the intrinsic spectral index of quasar variations: hints of finite stress at the innermost stable circular orbit</TD>
<TD>Weaver, John R.; Horne, Keith</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 512, Issue 1, pp.899-916</TD>
<TD>2022-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022MNRAS.512..899W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJS..260...18A</TD>
<TD>Target-of-opportunity Observations of Gravitational-wave Events with Vera C. Rubin Observatory</TD>
<TD>Andreoni, Igor; Margutti, Raffaella; Salafia, Om Sharan; Parazin, B.; Villar, V. Ashley; Coughlin, Michael W.; Yoachim, Peter; Mortensen, Kris; Brethauer, Daniel; Smartt, S. J.; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Alexander, Kate D.; Anand, Shreya; Berger, E.; Bernardini, Maria Grazia; Bianco, Federica B.; Blanchard, Peter K.; Bloom, Joshua S.; Brocato, Enzo; Bulla, Mattia; Cartier, Regis; Cenko, S. Bradley; Chornock, Ryan; Copperwheat, Christopher M.; Corsi, Alessandra; D'Ammando, Filippo; D'Avanzo, Paolo; Hélène Datrier, Laurence Élise; Foley, Ryan J.; Ghirlanda, Giancarlo; Goobar, Ariel; Grindlay, Jonathan; Hajela, Aprajita; Holz, Daniel E.; Karambelkar, Viraj; Kool, E. C.; Lamb, Gavin P.; Laskar, Tanmoy; Levan, Andrew; Maguire, Kate; May, Morgan; Melandri, Andrea; Milisavljevic, Dan; Miller, A. A.; Nicholl, Matt; Nissanke, Samaya M.; Palmese, Antonella; Piranomonte, Silvia; Rest, Armin; Sagués-Carracedo, Ana; Siellez, Karelle; Singer, Leo P.; Smith, Mathew; Steeghs, D.; Tanvir, Nial</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 260, Issue 1, id.18, 17 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJS..260...18A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...931...71G</TD>
<TD>The GALEX-PTF Experiment. II. Supernova Progenitor Radius and Energetics via Shock-cooling Modeling</TD>
<TD>Ganot, Noam; Ofek, Eran O.; Gal-Yam, Avishay; Schulze, Steve; Soumagnac, Maayane T.; Morag, Jonathan; Waxman, Eli; Kulkarni, Shrinivas R.; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Neill, James</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 931, Issue 1, id.71, 21 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...931...71G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...931...32Y</TD>
<TD>Optical Observations and Modeling of the Superluminous Supernova 2018lfe</TD>
<TD>Yin, Yao; Gomez, Sebastian; Berger, Edo; Hosseinzadeh, Griffin; Nicholl, Matt; Blanchard, Peter K.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 931, Issue 1, id.32, 9 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...931...32Y</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2022ApJ...931...13M</TD>
<TD>X-Ray Observation of the Roche-lobe-filling White Dwarf plus Hot Subdwarf System ZTF J213056.71+442046.5</TD>
<TD>Mereghetti, S.; La Palombara, N.; Kupfer, T.; Marsh, T. R.; Copperwheat, C. M.; Deshmukh, K.; Esposito, P.; Maccarone, T.; Pintore, F.; Rigoselli, M.; Rivera Sandoval, L.; Tiengo, A.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 931, Issue 1, id.13, 8 pp.</TD>
<TD>2022-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2022ApJ...931...13M</TD>
</TR>

</TABLEDATA>
</DATA>
</TABLE>
</RESOURCE>
</VOTABLE>

