<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf8'?>
<!DOCTYPE VOTABLE SYSTEM "http://cdsweb.u-strasbg.fr/xml/VOTable.dtd" >
<VOTABLE version="1.1">
<DESCRIPTION>
   Results generated from the NASA Astrophysics Data System: https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu
   For more information and support please contact ads@cfa.harvard.edu
</DESCRIPTION>
<RESOURCE type="results">
<TABLE>
<DESCRIPTION>
   ADS Search Results.
   Selected and retrieved 359 records.
</DESCRIPTION>
<FIELD ID="bibcode" datatype="char" arraysize="19">
<DESCRIPTION>The bibcode identifier for the record</DESCRIPTION>
</FIELD>
<FIELD ID="title" datatype="char" arraysize="*">
<DESCRIPTION>Title of the paper</DESCRIPTION>
</FIELD>
<FIELD ID="creator" datatype="char" arraysize="*">
<DESCRIPTION>List of authors</DESCRIPTION>
</FIELD>
<FIELD ID="source" datatype="char" arraysize="*">
<DESCRIPTION>Publication infromation</DESCRIPTION>
</FIELD>
<FIELD ID="date" datatype="char" arraysize="10">
<DESCRIPTION>Publication Date</DESCRIPTION>
</FIELD>
<FIELD ID="url" datatype="char" arraysize="*">
<DESCRIPTION>Resource URL</DESCRIPTION>
</FIELD>
<DATA>
<TABLEDATA>
<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.500.4307F</TD>
<TD>Calibrating the binary black hole population in nuclear star clusters through tidal disruption events</TD>
<TD>Fragione, Giacomo; Perna, Rosalba; Loeb, Abraham</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 500, Issue 4, pp.4307-4318</TD>
<TD>2021-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.500.4307F</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021JSSCh.29421896L</TD>
<TD>Flexible ligands-dependent formation of a new column layered MOF possess 1D channel and effective separation performance for CO&lt;SUB&gt;2&lt;/SUB&gt;</TD>
<TD>Li, Si-Yu; Zhang, Feng-Feng; Wang, Xiao; He, Meng-Hui; Ding, Zhu; Chen, Min; Hou, Xiang-Yang; Chen, Xiao-Li; Tang, Long; Yue, Er-Lin; Wang, Ji-Jiang; Fu, Feng</TD>
<TD>Journal of Solid State Chemistry, Volume 294, article id. 121896.</TD>
<TD>2021-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021JSSCh.29421896L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021JCAP...02..043M</TD>
<TD>Gravitational wave friction in light of GW170817 and GW190521</TD>
<TD>Mastrogiovanni, S.; Haegel, L.; Karathanasis, C.; Magaña Hernandez, I.; Steer, D. A.</TD>
<TD>Journal of Cosmology and Astroparticle Physics, Issue 02, article id. 043 (2021).</TD>
<TD>2021-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021JCAP...02..043M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021JCAP...02..024A</TD>
<TD>Electromagnetic bursts from mergers of oscillons in axion-like fields</TD>
<TD>Amin, Mustafa A.; Mou, Zong-Gang</TD>
<TD>Journal of Cosmology and Astroparticle Physics, Issue 02, article id. 024 (2021).</TD>
<TD>2021-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021JCAP...02..024A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJS..252...32J</TD>
<TD>Mid-infrared Outbursts in Nearby Galaxies (MIRONG). I. Sample Selection and Characterization</TD>
<TD>Jiang, Ning; Wang, Tinggui; Dou, Liming; Shu, Xinwen; Hu, Xueyang; Liu, Hui; Wang, Yibo; Yan, Lin; Sheng, Zhenfeng; Yang, Chenwei; Sun, Luming; Zhou, Hongyan</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 252, Issue 2, id.32, 27 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJS..252...32J</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...908L..34G</TD>
<TD>Measuring the Hubble Constant with GW190521 as an Eccentric black hole Merger and Its Potential Electromagnetic Counterpart</TD>
<TD>Gayathri, V.; Healy, J.; Lange, J.; O'Brien, B.; Szczepanczyk, M.; Bartos, I.; Campanelli, M.; Klimenko, S.; Lousto, C. O.; O'Shaughnessy, R.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 908, Issue 2, id.L34, 4 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...908L..34G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...908L..20H</TD>
<TD>Tidal Disruption Event Hosts Are Green and Centrally Concentrated: Signatures of a Post-merger System</TD>
<TD>Hammerstein, Erica; Gezari, Suvi; van Velzen, Sjoert; Cenko, S. Bradley; Roth, Nathaniel; Ward, Charlotte; Frederick, Sara; Hung, Tiara; Graham, Matthew; Foley, Ryan J.; Bellm, Eric C.; Cannella, Christopher; Drake, Andrew J.; Kupfer, Thomas; Laher, Russ R.; Mahabal, Ashish A.; Masci, Frank J.; Riddle, Reed; Rojas-Bravo, César; Smith, Roger</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 908, Issue 1, id.L20, 9 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...908L..20H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...908..249M</TD>
<TD>Constraints on the Rate of Supernovae Lasting for More Than a Year from Subaru/Hyper Suprime-Cam</TD>
<TD>Moriya, Takashi J.; Jiang, Ji-an; Yasuda, Naoki; Kokubo, Mitsuru; Kawana, Kojiro; Maeda, Keiichi; Pan, Yen-Chen; Quimby, Robert M.; Suzuki, Nao; Takahashi, Ichiro; Tanaka, Masaomi; Tominaga, Nozomu; Nomoto, Ken'ichi; Cooke, Jeff; Galbany, Lluís; González-Gaitán, Santiago; Lee, Chien-Hsiu; Pignata, Giuliano</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 908, Issue 2, id.249, 13 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...908..249M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...908..232R</TD>
<TD>Near-infrared and Optical Observations of Type Ic SN 2020oi and Broad-lined Type Ic SN 2020bvc: Carbon Monoxide, Dust, and High-velocity Supernova Ejecta</TD>
<TD>Rho, J.; Evans, A.; Geballe, T. R.; Banerjee, D. P. K.; Hoeflich, P.; Shahbandeh, M.; Valenti, S.; Yoon, S. -C.; Jin, H.; Williamson, M.; Modjaz, M.; Hiramatsu, D.; Howell, D. A.; Pellegrino, C.; Vinkó, J.; Cartier, R.; Burke, J.; McCully, C.; An, H.; Cha, H.; Pritchard, T.; Wang, X.; Andrews, J.; Galbany, L.; Van Dyk, S.; Graham, M. L.; Blinnikov, S.; Joshi, V.; Pál, A.; Kriskovics, L.; Ordasi, A.; Szakats, R.; Vida, K.; Chen, Z.; Li, X.; Zhang, J.; Yan, S.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 908, Issue 2, id.232, 21 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...908..232R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...908..180A</TD>
<TD>Identifying Candidate Optical Variables Using Gaia Data Release 2</TD>
<TD>Andrew, Shion; Swihart, Samuel J.; Strader, Jay</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 908, Issue 2, id.180, 10 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...908..180A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...908..170G</TD>
<TD>GHOST: Using Only Host Galaxy Information to Accurately Associate and Distinguish Supernovae</TD>
<TD>Gagliano, Alex; Narayan, Gautham; Engel, Andrew; Carrasco Kind, Matias; LSST Dark Energy Science Collaboration</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 908, Issue 2, id.170, 23 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...908..170G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...908..143J</TD>
<TD>The Young Supernova Experiment: Survey Goals, Overview, and Operations</TD>
<TD>Jones, D. O.; Foley, R. J.; Narayan, G.; Hjorth, J.; Huber, M. E.; Aleo, P. D.; Alexander, K. D.; Angus, C. R.; Auchettl, K.; Baldassare, V. F.; Bruun, S. H.; Chambers, K. C.; Chatterjee, D.; Coppejans, D. L.; Coulter, D. A.; DeMarchi, L.; Dimitriadis, G.; Drout, M. R.; Engel, A.; French, K. D.; Gagliano, A.; Gall, C.; Hung, T.; Izzo, L.; Jacobson-Galán, W. V.; Kilpatrick, C. D.; Korhonen, H.; Margutti, R.; Raimundo, S. I.; Ramirez-Ruiz, E.; Rest, A.; Rojas-Bravo, C.; Siebert, M. R.; Smartt, S. J.; Smith, K. W.; Terreran, G.; Wang, Q.; Wojtak, R.; Agnello, A.; Ansari, Z.; Arendse, N.; Baldeschi, A.; Blanchard, P. K.; Brethauer, D.; Bright, J. S.; Brown, J. S.; de Boer, T. J. L.; Dodd, S. A.; Fairlamb, J. R.; Grillo, C.; Hajela, A.; Hede, C.; Kolborg, A. N.; Law-Smith, J. A. P.; Lin, C. -C.; Magnier, E. A.; Malanchev, K.; Matthews, D.; Mockler, B.; Muthukrishna, D.; Pan, Y. -C.; Pfister, H.; Ramanah, D. K.; Rest, S.; Sarangi, A.; Schrøder, S. L.; Stauffer, C.; Stroh, M. C.; Taggart, K. L.; Tinyanont, S.; Wainscoat, R. J.; Young Supernova Experiment</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 908, Issue 2, id.143, 24 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...908..143J</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...908...99S</TD>
<TD>Extremely Energetic Supernova Explosions Embedded in a Massive Circumstellar Medium: The Case of SN 2016aps</TD>
<TD>Suzuki, Akihiro; Nicholl, Matt; Moriya, Takashi J.; Takiwaki, Tomoya</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 908, Issue 1, id.99, 13 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...908...99S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...908...51F</TD>
<TD>Early-time Light Curves of Type Ia Supernovae Observed with TESS</TD>
<TD>Fausnaugh, M. M.; Vallely, P. J.; Kochanek, C. S.; Shappee, B. J.; Stanek, K. Z.; Tucker, M. A.; Ricker, George R.; Vanderspek, Roland; Latham, David W.; Seager, S.; Winn, Joshua N.; Jenkins, Jon M.; Berta-Thompson, Zachory K.; Daylan, Tansu; Doty, John P.; Fűrész, Gábor; Levine, Alan M.; Morris, Robert; Pál, András; Sha, Lizhou; Ting, Eric B.; Wohler, Bill</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 908, Issue 1, id.51, 54 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...908...51F</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...908....4V</TD>
<TD>Seventeen Tidal Disruption Events from the First Half of ZTF Survey Observations: Entering a New Era of Population Studies</TD>
<TD>van Velzen, Sjoert; Gezari, Suvi; Hammerstein, Erica; Roth, Nathaniel; Frederick, Sara; Ward, Charlotte; Hung, Tiara; Cenko, S. Bradley; Stein, Robert; Perley, Daniel A.; Taggart, Kirsty; Foley, Ryan J.; Sollerman, Jesper; Blagorodnova, Nadejda; Andreoni, Igor; Bellm, Eric C.; Brinnel, Valery; De, Kishalay; Dekany, Richard; Feeney, Michael; Fremling, Christoffer; Giomi, Matteo; Golkhou, V. Zach; Graham, Matthew J.; Ho, Anna. Y. Q.; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Kilpatrick, Charles D.; Kulkarni, Shrinivas R.; Kupfer, Thomas; Laher, Russ R.; Mahabal, Ashish; Masci, Frank J.; Miller, Adam A.; Nordin, Jakob; Riddle, Reed; Rusholme, Ben; van Santen, Jakob; Sharma, Yashvi; Shupe, David L.; Soumagnac, Maayane T.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 908, Issue 1, id.4, 26 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...908....4V</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...907L..48V</TD>
<TD>Search for Black Hole Merger Families</TD>
<TD>Veske, Doğa; Sullivan, Andrew G.; Márka, Zsuzsa; Bartos, Imre; Corley, K. Rainer; Samsing, Johan; Buscicchio, Riccardo; Márka, Szabolcs</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 907, Issue 2, id.L48, 7 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...907L..48V</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...907L..29H</TD>
<TD>An Extraordinary Response of Iron Emission to the Central Outburst in a Tidal Disruption Event Candidate</TD>
<TD>He, Zhicheng; Jiang, Ning; Wang, Tinggui; Liu, Guilin; Sun, Mouyuan; Guo, Hengxiao; Shen, Lu; Cai, Zhenyi; Shu, Xinwen; Sheng, Zhenfeng; Liang, Zhixiong; Xu, Youhua</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 907, Issue 2, id.L29, 5 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...907L..29H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...907...99S</TD>
<TD>Bright, Months-long Stellar Outbursts Announce the Explosion of Interaction-powered Supernovae</TD>
<TD>Strotjohann, Nora L.; Ofek, Eran O.; Gal-Yam, Avishay; Bruch, Rachel; Schulze, Steve; Shaviv, Nir; Sollerman, Jesper; Filippenko, Alexei V.; Yaron, Ofer; Fremling, Christoffer; Nordin, Jakob; Kool, Erik C.; Perley, Dan A.; Ho, Anna Y. Q.; Yang, Yi; Yao, Yuhan; Soumagnac, Maayane T.; Graham, Melissa L.; Barbarino, Cristina; Tartaglia, Leonardo; De, Kishalay; Goldstein, Daniel A.; Cook, David O.; Brink, Thomas G.; Taggart, Kirsty; Yan, Lin; Lunnan, Ragnhild; Kasliwal, Mansi; Kulkarni, Shri R.; Nugent, Peter E.; Masci, Frank J.; Rosnet, Philippe; Adams, Scott M.; Andreoni, Igor; Bagdasaryan, Ashot; Bellm, Eric C.; Burdge, Kevin; Duev, Dmitry A.; Dugas, Alison; Frederick, Sara; Goldwasser, Samantha; Hankins, Matthew; Irani, Ido; Karambelkar, Viraj; Kupfer, Thomas; Liang, Jingyi; Neill, James D.; Porter, Michael; Riddle, Reed L.; Sharma, Yashvi; Short, Phil; Taddia, Francesco; Tzanidakis, Anastasios; van Roestel, Jan; Walters, Richard; Zhuang, Zhuyun</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 907, Issue 2, id.99, 31 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...907...99S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...907...96S</TD>
<TD>Improving Damped Random Walk Parameters for SDSS Stripe 82 Quasars with Pan-STARRS1</TD>
<TD>Suberlak, Krzysztof L.; Ivezić, Željko; MacLeod, Chelsea</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 907, Issue 2, id.96, 26 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...907...96S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021AJ....161...73C</TD>
<TD>Dust Production from Mini Outbursts of Comet 29P/Schwassmann-Wachmann 1</TD>
<TD>Clements, Tiffany D.; Fernandez, Yanga</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 161, Issue 2, id.73, 10 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021AJ....161...73C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021A&amp;A...646A.181S</TD>
<TD>X-ray and ultraviolet observations of the eclipsing cataclysmic variables OV Bootis and SDSS J103533.02+055158.3 with degenerate donors</TD>
<TD>Schwope, Axel; Worpel, Hauke; Traulsen, Iris</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 646, id.A181, 12 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021A&amp;A...646A.181S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021A&amp;A...646A.119P</TD>
<TD>Forbidden hugs in pandemic times. I. Luminous red nova AT 2019zhd, a new merger in M 31</TD>
<TD>Pastorello, A.; Fraser, M.; Valerin, G.; Reguitti, A.; Itagaki, K.; Ochner, P.; Williams, S. C.; Jones, D.; Munday, J.; Smartt, S. J.; Smith, K. W.; Srivastav, S.; Elias-Rosa, N.; Kankare, E.; Karamehmetoglu, E.; Lundqvist, P.; Mazzali, P. A.; Munari, U.; Stritzinger, M. D.; Tomasella, L.; Anderson, J. P.; Chambers, K. C.; Rest, A.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 646, id.A119, 12 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021A&amp;A...646A.119P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021A&amp;A...646A..22Y</TD>
<TD>Is supernova SN 2020faa an iPTF14hls look-alike?</TD>
<TD>Yang, S.; Sollerman, J.; Chen, T. -W.; Kool, E. C.; Lunnan, R.; Schulze, S.; Strotjohann, N.; Horesh, A.; Kasliwal, M.; Kupfer, T.; Mahabal, A. A.; Masci, F. J.; Nugent, P.; Perley, D. A.; Riddle, R.; Rusholme, B.; Sharma, Y.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 646, id.A22, 10 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021A&amp;A...646A..22Y</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021RAA....21...13D</TD>
<TD>Research on the readout noise suppression method for digital correlated double sampling</TD>
<TD>Duan, Wei; Song, Qian; Wei, Ming-Zhi; Zhao, Zhao-Wang; Wang, Wei; Zhang, Yu-Heng; Feng, Zhi-Wei</TD>
<TD>Research in Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 21, Issue 1, id.013, 9 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021RAA....21...13D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021PhRvL.126b1101Y</TD>
<TD>Direct Determination of Supermassive Black Hole Properties with Gravitational-Wave Radiation from Surrounding Stellar-Mass Black Hole Binaries</TD>
<TD>Yu, Hang; Chen, Yanbei</TD>
<TD>Physical Review Letters, Volume 126, Issue 2, article id.021101</TD>
<TD>2021-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021PhRvL.126b1101Y</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021PhRvD.103b3524M</TD>
<TD>Cosmology requirements on supernova photometric redshift systematics for the Rubin LSST and Roman Space Telescope</TD>
<TD>Mitra, Ayan; Linder, Eric V.</TD>
<TD>Physical Review D, Volume 103, Issue 2, article id.023524</TD>
<TD>2021-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021PhRvD.103b3524M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021PASA...38....4M</TD>
<TD>Processing GOTO data with the Rubin Observatory LSST Science Pipelines I: Production of coadded frames</TD>
<TD>Mullaney, J. R.; Makrygianni, L.; Dhillon, V.; Littlefair, S.; Ackley, K.; Dyer, M.; Lyman, J.; Ulaczyk, K.; Cutter, R.; Mong, Y. -L.; Steeghs, D.; Galloway, D. K.; O'Brien, P.; Ramsay, G.; Poshyachinda, S.; Kotak, R.; Nuttall, L.; Pallé, E.; Pollacco, D.; Thrane, E.; Aukkaravittayapun, S.; Awiphan, S.; Breton, R.; Burhanudin, U.; Chote, P.; Chrimes, A.; Daw, E.; Duffy, C.; Eyles-Ferris, R.; Gompertz, B.; Heikkilä, T.; Irawati, P.; Kennedy, M.; Killestein, T.; Levan, A.; Marsh, T.; Mata-Sanchez, D.; Mattila, S.; Maund, J.; McCormac, J.; Mkrtichian, D.; Rol, E.; Sawangwit, U.; Stanway, E.; Starling, R.; Tooke, S.; Wiersema, K.</TD>
<TD>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Australia, Volume 38, article id. e004</TD>
<TD>2021-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021PASA...38....4M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021PASA...38....1T</TD>
<TD>High cadence optical transient searches using drift scan imaging II: Event rate upper limits on optical transients of duration &lt;21 ms and magnitude &lt;6.6</TD>
<TD>Tingay, Steven; Joubert, Wynand</TD>
<TD>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Australia, Volume 38, article id. e001</TD>
<TD>2021-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021PASA...38....1T</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021P&amp;SS..19505120H</TD>
<TD>Photometric study for near-Earth asteroid (155140) 2005 UD</TD>
<TD>Huang, J. -N.; Muinonen, K.; Chen, T.; Wang, X. -B.</TD>
<TD>Planetary and Space Science, Volume 195, article id. 105120.</TD>
<TD>2021-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021P&amp;SS..19505120H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021NatRP...3..344B</TD>
<TD>Gravitational-wave physics and astronomy in the 2020s and 2030s</TD>
<TD>Bailes, M.; Berger, B. K.; Brady, P. R.; Branchesi, M.; Danzmann, K.; Evans, M.; Holley-Bockelmann, K.; Iyer, B. R.; Kajita, T.; Katsanevas, S.; Kramer, M.; Lazzarini, A.; Lehner, L.; Losurdo, G.; Lück, H.; McClelland, D. E.; McLaughlin, M. A.; Punturo, M.; Ransom, S.; Raychaudhury, S.; Reitze, D. H.; Ricci, F.; Rowan, S.; Saito, Y.; Sanders, G. H.; Sathyaprakash, B. S.; Schutz, B. F.; Sesana, A.; Shinkai, H.; Siemens, X.; Shoemaker, D. H.; Thorpe, J.; van den Brand, J. F. J.; Vitale, S.</TD>
<TD>Nature Reviews Physics, Volume 3, Issue 5, p.344-366</TD>
<TD>2021-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021NatRP...3..344B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021NatAs...5...46A</TD>
<TD>Optical follow-up of the neutron star-black hole mergers S200105ae and S200115j</TD>
<TD>Anand, Shreya; Coughlin, Michael W.; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Bulla, Mattia; Ahumada, Tomás; Sagués Carracedo, Ana; Almualla, Mouza; Andreoni, Igor; Stein, Robert; Foucart, Francois; Singer, Leo P.; Sollerman, Jesper; Bellm, Eric C.; Bolin, Bryce; Caballero-García, M. D.; Castro-Tirado, Alberto J.; Cenko, S. Bradley; De, Kishalay; Dekany, Richard G.; Duev, Dmitry A.; Feeney, Michael; Fremling, Christoffer; Goldstein, Daniel A.; Golkhou, V. Zach; Graham, Matthew J.; Guessoum, Nidhal; Hankins, Matthew J.; Hu, Youdong; Kong, Albert K. H.; Kool, Erik C.; Kulkarni, S. R.; Kumar, Harsh; Laher, Russ R.; Masci, Frank J.; Mróz, Przemek; Nissanke, Samaya; Porter, Michael; Reusch, Simeon; Riddle, Reed; Rosnet, Philippe; Rusholme, Ben; Serabyn, Eugene; Sánchez-Ramírez, R.; Rigault, Mickael; Shupe, David L.; Smith, Roger; Soumagnac, Maayane T.; Walters, Richard; Valeev, Azamat F.</TD>
<TD>Nature Astronomy, Volume 5, p. 46-53</TD>
<TD>2021-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021NatAs...5...46A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.501..229W</TD>
<TD>ZZ Piscis Austrinus (ZZ PsA): a bright red nova progenitor and the instability mass ratio of contact binary stars</TD>
<TD>Wadhwa, Surjit S.; De Horta, Ain; Filipović, Miroslav D.; Tothill, N. F. H.; Arbutina, Bojan; Petrović, Jelena; Djurašević, Gojko</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 501, Issue 1, pp.229-235</TD>
<TD>2021-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.501..229W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.500.4213M</TD>
<TD>PS15cey and PS17cke: prospective candidates from the Pan-STARRS Search for kilonovae</TD>
<TD>McBrien, O. R.; Smartt, S. J.; Huber, M. E.; Rest, A.; Chambers, K. C.; Barbieri, C.; Bulla, M.; Jha, S.; Gromadzki, M.; Srivastav, S.; Smith, K. W.; Young, D. R.; McLaughlin, S.; Inserra, C.; Nicholl, M.; Fraser, M.; Maguire, K.; Chen, T. -W.; Wevers, T.; Anderson, J. P.; Müller-Bravo, T. E.; Olivares E., F.; Kankare, E.; Gal-Yam, A.; Waters, C.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 500, Issue 3, pp.4213-4228</TD>
<TD>2021-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.500.4213M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.500.4025L</TD>
<TD>Discovery of a candidate binary supermassive black hole in a periodic quasar from circumbinary accretion variability</TD>
<TD>Liao, Wei-Ting; Chen, Yu-Ching; Liu, Xin; Holgado, A. Miguel; Guo, Hengxiao; Gruendl, Robert; Morganson, Eric; Shen, Yue; Davis, Tamara; Kessler, Richard; Martini, Paul; McMahon, Richard G.; Allam, Sahar; Annis, James; Avila, Santiago; Banerji, Manda; Bechtol, Keith; Bertin, Emmanuel; Brooks, David; Buckley-Geer, Elizabeth; Carnero Rosell, Aurelio; Carrasco Kind, Matias; Carretero, Jorge; Javier Castander, Francisco; Cunha, Carlos; D'Andrea, Chris; da Costa, Luiz; Davis, Christopher; De Vicente, Juan; Desai, Shantanu; Thomas Diehl, H.; Doel, Peter; Eifler, Tim; Evrard, August; Flaugher, Brenna; Fosalba, Pablo; Frieman, Josh; Garcia-Bellido, Juan; Gaztanaga, Enrique; Glazebrook, Karl; Gruen, Daniel; Gschwend, Julia; Gutierrez, Gaston; Hartley, Will; Hollowood, Devon L.; Honscheid, Klaus; Hoyle, Ben; James, David; Krause, Elisabeth; Kuehn, Kyler; Lima, Marcos; Maia, Marcio; Marshall, Jennifer; Menanteau, Felipe; Miquel, Ramon; Plazas Malagón, Andrés; Roodman, Aaron; Sanchez, Eusebio; Scarpine, Vic; Schubnell, Michael; Serrano, Santiago; Smith, Mathew; Smith, R. Chris; Soares-Santos, Marcelle; Sobreira, Flavia; Suchyta, Eric; Swanson, Molly; Tarle, Gregory; Vikram, Vinu; Walker, Alistair</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 500, Issue 3, pp.4025-4041</TD>
<TD>2021-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.500.4025L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.500.2986H</TD>
<TD>The effect of a magnetic field on the dynamics of debris discs around white dwarfs</TD>
<TD>Hogg, M. A.; Cutter, R.; Wynn, G. A.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 500, Issue 3, pp.2986-3001</TD>
<TD>2021-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.500.2986H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021MNRAS.500.1673H</TD>
<TD>Discovery and follow-up of ASASSN-19dj: an X-ray and UV luminous TDE in an extreme post-starburst galaxy</TD>
<TD>Hinkle, Jason T.; Holoien, T. W. -S.; Auchettl, K.; Shappee, B. J.; Neustadt, J. M. M.; Payne, A. V.; Brown, J. S.; Kochanek, C. S.; Stanek, K. Z.; Graham, M. J.; Tucker, M. A.; Do, A.; Anderson, J. P.; Bose, S.; Chen, P.; Coulter, D. A.; Dimitriadis, G.; Dong, Subo; Foley, R. J.; Huber, M. E.; Hung, T.; Kilpatrick, C. D.; Pignata, G.; Piro, A. L.; Rojas-Bravo, C.; Siebert, M. R.; Stalder, B.; Thompson, Todd A.; Tonry, J. L.; Vallely, P. J.; Wisniewski, J. P.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 500, Issue 2, pp.1673-1696</TD>
<TD>2021-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021MNRAS.500.1673H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021JChPh.154b4303D</TD>
<TD>In silico design of a new Zn-triazole based metal-organic framework for CO&lt;SUB&gt;2&lt;/SUB&gt; and H&lt;SUB&gt;2&lt;/SUB&gt;O adsorption</TD>
<TD>Dahmani, R.; Grubišić, S.; Djordjević, I.; Ben Yaghlane, S.; Boughdiri, S.; Chambaud, G.; Hochlaf, M.</TD>
<TD>The Journal of Chemical Physics, Volume 154, Issue 2, article id.024303</TD>
<TD>2021-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021JChPh.154b4303D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021FrASS...7..108P</TD>
<TD>Binary neutron star mergers: a multi-messenger revolution</TD>
<TD>Pian, Elena</TD>
<TD>Frontiers in Astronomy and Space Sciences, Volume 7, id.108 (2020)</TD>
<TD>2021-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021FrASS...7..108P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ChEnS.22916073S</TD>
<TD>Molecular-level behavior of imidazolium-based ionic liquid mixtures</TD>
<TD>Sappidi, Praveenkumar; Bara, Jason E.; Turner, C. Heath</TD>
<TD>Chemical Engineering Science, Volume 229, article id. 116073.</TD>
<TD>2021-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ChEnS.22916073S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...907L...9N</TD>
<TD>GW190521 May Be an Intermediate-mass Ratio Inspiral</TD>
<TD>Nitz, Alexander H.; Capano, Collin D.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 907, Issue 1, id.L9, 7 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...907L...9N</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...907L...3K</TD>
<TD>Deep Optical Observations Contemporaneous with Emission from the Periodic FRB 180916.J0158+65</TD>
<TD>Kilpatrick, Charles D.; Burchett, Joseph N.; Jones, David O.; Margalit, Ben; McMillan, Russet; Fong, Wen-fai; Heintz, Kasper E.; Tejos, Nicolas; Escorial, Alicia Rouco</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 907, Issue 1, id.L3, 8 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...907L...3K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...907...52T</TD>
<TD>The Early Discovery of SN 2017ahn: Signatures of Persistent Interaction in a Fast-declining Type II Supernova</TD>
<TD>Tartaglia, L.; Sand, D. J.; Groh, J. H.; Valenti, S.; Wyatt, S. D.; Bostroem, K. A.; Brown, P. J.; Yang, S.; Burke, J.; Chen, T. -W.; Davis, S.; Förster, F.; Galbany, L.; Haislip, J.; Hiramatsu, D.; Hosseinzadeh, G.; Howell, D. A.; Hsiao, E. Y.; Jha, S. W.; Kouprianov, V.; Kuncarayakti, H.; Lyman, J. D.; McCully, C.; Phillips, M. M.; Rau, A.; Reichart, D. E.; Shahbandeh, M.; Strader, J.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 907, Issue 1, id.52, 19 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...907...52T</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...906L..11Z</TD>
<TD>Neutron Star Mergers in Active Galactic Nucleus Accretion Disks: Cocoon and Ejecta Shock Breakouts</TD>
<TD>Zhu, Jin-Ping; Zhang, Bing; Yu, Yun-Wei; Gao, He</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 906, Issue 2, id.L11, 7 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...906L..11Z</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...906...99L</TD>
<TD>Can the Helium-detonation Model Explain the Observed Diversity of Type Ia Supernovae?</TD>
<TD>Li, Wenxiong; Wang, Xiaofeng; Bulla, Mattia; Pan, Yen-Chen; Wang, Lifan; Mo, Jun; Zhang, Jujia; Wu, Chengyuan; Zhang, Jicheng; Zhang, Tianmeng; Xiang, Danfeng; Lin, Han; Sai, Hanna; Zhang, Xinghan; Chen, Zhihao; Yan, Shengyu</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 906, Issue 2, id.99, 12 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...906...99L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021ApJ...906...56D</TD>
<TD>Supernova 2018cuf: A Type IIP Supernova with a Slow Fall from Plateau</TD>
<TD>Dong, Yize; Valenti, S.; Bostroem, K. A.; Sand, D. J.; Andrews, Jennifer E.; Galbany, L.; Jha, Saurabh W.; Eweis, Youssef; Kwok, Lindsey; Hsiao, E. Y.; Davis, Scott; Brown, Peter J.; Kuncarayakti, H.; Maeda, Keiichi; Rho, Jeonghee; Amaro, R. C.; Anderson, J. P.; Arcavi, Iair; Burke, Jamison; Dastidar, Raya; Folatelli, Gastón; Haislip, Joshua; Hiramatsu, Daichi; Hosseinzadeh, Griffin; Howell, D. Andrew; Jencson, J.; Kouprianov, Vladimir; Lundquist, M.; Lyman, J. D.; McCully, Curtis; Misra, Kuntal; Reichart, Daniel E.; Sánchez, S. F.; Smith, Nathan; Wang, Xiaofeng; Wang, Lingzhi; Wyatt, S.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 906, Issue 1, id.56, 15 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021ApJ...906...56D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021AJ....161...15S</TD>
<TD>AT 2020iko: A WZ Sge-type Dwarf Nova Candidate with an Anomalous Precursor Event</TD>
<TD>Soraisam, Monika D.; DeSantis, Sarah R.; Lee, Chien-Hsiu; Matheson, Thomas; Narayan, Gautham; Saha, Abhijit; Sand, David J.; Stubens, Carl; Szkody, Paula; Wolf, Nicholas; Wyatt, Samuel D.; Hosokawa, Ryohei; Kawai, Nobuyuki; Murata, Katsuhiro L.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 161, Issue 1, id.15, 8 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021AJ....161...15S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2021A&amp;A...645A.137A</TD>
<TD>Multi-band behaviour of the TeV blazar PG 1553+113 in optical range on diverse timescales. Flux and spectral variations</TD>
<TD>Agarwal, A.; Mihov, B.; Andruchow, I.; Cellone, S. A.; Anupama, G. C.; Agrawal, V.; Zola, S.; Slavcheva-Mihova, L.; Özdönmez, A.; Ege, Ergün; Raj, A.; Mammana, L.; Zibecchi, L.; Fernández-Lajús, E.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 645, id.A137, 20 pp.</TD>
<TD>2021-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2021A&amp;A...645A.137A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020Sci...370.1450D</TD>
<TD>Multimessenger constraints on the neutron-star equation of state and the Hubble constant</TD>
<TD>Dietrich, Tim; Coughlin, Michael W.; Pang, Peter T. H.; Bulla, Mattia; Heinzel, Jack; Issa, Lina; Tews, Ingo; Antier, Sarah</TD>
<TD>Science, Volume 370, Issue 6523, pp. 1450-1453 (2020).</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020Sci...370.1450D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ResPh..1903579P</TD>
<TD>Search for high energy γ-rays from the direction of the candidate electromagnetic counterpart to the binary black hole merger gravitational-wave event S190521g</TD>
<TD>Podlesnyi, Egor; Dzhatdoev, Timur</TD>
<TD>Results in Physics, Volume 19, article id. 103579.</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ResPh..1903579P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020PhRvD.102l4077R</TD>
<TD>Black hole-neutron star coalescence: Effects of the neutron star spin on jet launching and dynamical ejecta mass</TD>
<TD>Ruiz, Milton; Paschalidis, Vasileios; Tsokaros, Antonios; Shapiro, Stuart L.</TD>
<TD>Physical Review D, Volume 102, Issue 12, article id.124077</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020PhRvD.102l4077R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020PhRvD.102l4018S</TD>
<TD>Modified gravity and the black hole mass gap</TD>
<TD>Straight, Maria C.; Sakstein, Jeremy; Baxter, Eric J.</TD>
<TD>Physical Review D, Volume 102, Issue 12, article id.124018</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020PhRvD.102l4018S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020PhRvD.102l3015B</TD>
<TD>Impact of neutrino pair-production rates in core-collapse supernovae</TD>
<TD>Betranhandy, Aurore; O'Connor, Evan</TD>
<TD>Physical Review D, Volume 102, Issue 12, article id.123015</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020PhRvD.102l3015B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020PhRvD.102l3009Y</TD>
<TD>Spin and eccentricity evolution in triple systems: From the Lidov-Kozai interaction to the final merger of the inner binary</TD>
<TD>Yu, Hang; Ma, Sizheng; Giesler, Matthew; Chen, Yanbei</TD>
<TD>Physical Review D, Volume 102, Issue 12, article id.123009</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020PhRvD.102l3009Y</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020PSJ.....1...73M</TD>
<TD>Convex Shape and Rotation Model of Lucy Target (11351) Leucus from Lightcurves and Occultations</TD>
<TD>Mottola, Stefano; Hellmich, Stephan; Buie, Marc W.; Zangari, Amanda M.; Marchi, Simone; Brown, Michael E.; Levison, Harold F.</TD>
<TD>The Planetary Science Journal, Volume 1, Issue 3, id.73, 14 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020PSJ.....1...73M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020PASP..132l5004O</TD>
<TD>Seeing-limited Imaging Sky Surveys—Small versus Large Telescopes</TD>
<TD>Ofek, E. O.; Ben-Ami, S.</TD>
<TD>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 132, Issue 1018, id.125004, 7 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020PASP..132l5004O</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020PASP..132l5001Z</TD>
<TD>The Tsinghua University-Ma Huateng Telescopes for Survey: Overview and Performance of the System</TD>
<TD>Zhang, Ji-Cheng; Wang, Xiao-Feng; Mo, Jun; Xi, Gao-Bo; Lin, Jie; Jiang, Xiao-Jun; Zhang, Xiao-Ming; Li, Wen-Xiong; Yan, Sheng-Yu; Chen, Zhi-Hao; Hu, Lei; Li, Xue; Lin, Wei-Li; Lin, Han; Miao, Cheng; Rui, Li-Ming; Sai, Han-Na; Xiang, Dan-Feng; Zhang, Xing-Han</TD>
<TD>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 132, Issue 1018, id.125001, 17 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020PASP..132l5001Z</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020PASJ...72...98K</TD>
<TD>BC Cassiopeiae: First detection of IW Andromedae-type phenomenon among post-eruption novae</TD>
<TD>Kato, Taichi; Kojiguchi, Naoto</TD>
<TD>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Volume 72, Issue 6, id.98, 4 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020PASJ...72...98K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.499L..87D</TD>
<TD>A quasar microlensing event towards J1249+3449?</TD>
<TD>De Paolis, F.; Nucita, A. A.; Strafella, F.; Licchelli, D.; Ingrosso, G.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 499, Issue 1, pp.L87-L90</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.499L..87D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.499L..26W</TD>
<TD>CO observations towards H-=I-rich Ultradiffuse Galaxies</TD>
<TD>Wang, Junzhi; Yang, Kai; Zhang, Zhi-Yu; Fang, Min; Shi, Yong; Liu, Shu; Li, Juan; Li, Fei</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 499, Issue 1, pp.L26-L30</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.499L..26W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.499.6009M</TD>
<TD>Machine learning for transient recognition in difference imaging with minimum sampling effort</TD>
<TD>Mong, Y. -L.; Ackley, K.; Galloway, D. K.; Killestein, T.; Lyman, J.; Steeghs, D.; Dhillon, V.; O'Brien, P. T.; Ramsay, G.; Poshyachinda, S.; Kotak, R.; Nuttall, L.; Pallé, E.; Pollacco, D.; Thrane, E.; Dyer, M. J.; Ulaczyk, K.; Cutter, R.; McCormac, J.; Chote, P.; Levan, A. J.; Marsh, T.; Stanway, E.; Gompertz, B.; Wiersema, K.; Chrimes, A.; Obradovic, A.; Mullaney, J.; Daw, E.; Littlefair, S.; Maund, J.; Makrygianni, L.; Burhanudin, U.; Starling, R. L. C.; Eyles-Ferris, R. A. J.; Tooke, S.; Duffy, C.; Aukkaravittayapun, S.; Sawangwit, U.; Awiphan, S.; Mkrtichian, D.; Irawati, P.; Mattila, S.; Heikkilä, T.; Breton, R.; Kennedy, M.; Mata Sánchez, D.; Rol, E.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 499, Issue 4, pp.6009-6017</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.499.6009M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.499.5941D</TD>
<TD>Cosmic rates of black hole mergers and pair-instability supernovae from chemically homogeneous binary evolution</TD>
<TD>du Buisson, L.; Marchant, P.; Podsiadlowski, Ph; Kobayashi, C.; Abdalla, F. B.; Taylor, P.; Mandel, I.; de Mink, S. E.; Moriya, T. J.; Langer, N.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 499, Issue 4, pp.5941-5959</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.499.5941D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.499.5782O</TD>
<TD>A catalogue of over 10 million variable source candidates in ZTF Data Release 1</TD>
<TD>Ofek, Eran O.; Soumagnac, Maayane; Nir, Guy; Gal-Yam, Avishay; Nugent, Peter; Masci, Frank; Kulkarni, Shri R.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 499, Issue 4, pp.5782-5790</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.499.5782O</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.499.3459P</TD>
<TD>Swift-XRT follow-up of gravitational wave triggers during the third aLIGO/Virgo observing run</TD>
<TD>Page, K. L.; Evans, P. A.; Tohuvavohu, A.; Kennea, J. A.; Klingler, N. J.; Cenko, S. B.; Oates, S. R.; Ambrosi, E.; Barthelmy, S. D.; Beardmore, A. P.; Bernardini, M. G.; Breeveld, A. A.; Brown, P. J.; Burrows, D. N.; Campana, S.; Caputo, R.; Cusumano, G.; D'Aì, A.; D'Avanzo, P.; D'Elia, V.; De Pasquale, M.; Emery, S. W. K.; Giommi, P.; Gronwall, C.; Hartmann, D. H.; Krimm, H. A.; Kuin, N. P. M.; Malesani, D. B.; Marshall, F. E.; Melandri, A.; Nousek, J. A.; O'Brien, P. T.; Osborne, J. P.; Pagani, C.; Page, M. J.; Palmer, D. M.; Perri, M.; Racusin, J. L.; Sakamoto, T.; Sbarufatti, B.; Schlieder, J. E.; Siegel, M. H.; Tagliaferri, G.; Troja, E.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 499, Issue 3, pp.3459-3480</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.499.3459P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.499.3130G</TD>
<TD>Classifying image sequences of astronomical transients with deep neural networks</TD>
<TD>Gómez, Catalina; Neira, Mauricio; Hernández Hoyos, Marcela; Arbeláez, Pablo; Forero-Romero, Jaime E.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 499, Issue 3, pp.3130-3138</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.499.3130G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.499.2564G</TD>
<TD>Single magnetic white dwarfs with Balmer emission lines: a small class with consistent physical characteristics as possible signposts for close-in planetary companions</TD>
<TD>Gänsicke, Boris T.; Rodríguez-Gil, Pablo; Gentile Fusillo, Nicola P.; Inight, Keith; Schreiber, Matthias R.; Pala, Anna F.; Tremblay, Pier-Emmanuel</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 499, Issue 2, pp.2564-2574</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.499.2564G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.499.2245C</TD>
<TD>Candidate periodically variable quasars from the Dark Energy Survey and the Sloan Digital Sky Survey</TD>
<TD>Chen, Yu-Ching; Liu, Xin; Liao, Wei-Ting; Holgado, A. Miguel; Guo, Hengxiao; Gruendl, Robert A.; Morganson, Eric; Shen, Yue; Zhang, Kaiwen; Abbott, Tim M. C.; Aguena, Michel; Allam, Sahar; Avila, Santiago; Bertin, Emmanuel; Bhargava, Sunayana; Brooks, David; Burke, David L.; Carnero Rosell, Aurelio; Carollo, Daniela; Carrasco Kind, Matias; Carretero, Jorge; Costanzi, Matteo; da Costa, Luiz N.; Davis, Tamara M.; De Vicente, Juan; Desai, Shantanu; Diehl, H. Thomas; Doel, Peter; Everett, Spencer; Flaugher, Brenna; Friedel, Douglas; Frieman, Joshua; García-Bellido, Juan; Gaztanaga, Enrique; Glazebrook, Karl; Gruen, Daniel; Gutierrez, Gaston; Hinton, Samuel R.; Hollowood, Devon L.; James, David J.; Kim, Alex G.; Kuehn, Kyler; Kuropatkin, Nikolay; Lewis, Geraint F.; Lidman, Christopher; Lima, Marcos; Maia, Marcio A. G.; March, Marisa; Marshall, Jennifer L.; Menanteau, Felipe; Miquel, Ramon; Palmese, Antonella; Paz-Chinchón, Francisco; Plazas, Andrés A.; Sanchez, Eusebio; Schubnell, Michael; Serrano, Santiago; Sevilla-Noarbe, Ignacio; Smith, Mathew; Suchyta, Eric; Swanson, Molly E. C.; Tarle, Gregory; Tucker, Brad E.; Norbert Varga, Tamas; Walker, Alistair R.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 499, Issue 2, pp.2245-2264</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.499.2245C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.499.2116M</TD>
<TD>The nature of the symbiotic candidate 2MASS J07363415+6538548 in the field of NGC 2403</TD>
<TD>Merc, J.; Gális, R.; Kára, J.; Wolf, M.; Vrašťák, M.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 499, Issue 2, pp.2116-2123</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.499.2116M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.499.1854M</TD>
<TD>Understanding the origin of white dwarf atmospheric pollution by dynamical simulations based on detected three-planet systems</TD>
<TD>Maldonado, R. F.; Villaver, E.; Mustill, A. J.; Chavez, M.; Bertone, E.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 499, Issue 2, pp.1854-1869</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.499.1854M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020LRR....23....4B</TD>
<TD>Neutron star mergers and how to study them</TD>
<TD>Burns, Eric</TD>
<TD>Living Reviews in Relativity, Volume 23, Issue 1, article id.4</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020LRR....23....4B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020JSSCh.29221656W</TD>
<TD>Preparation of egg white@zeolitic imidazolate framework-8@polyacrylic acid aerogel and its adsorption properties for organic dyes</TD>
<TD>Wang, Qingqing; Lei, Liling; Wang, Fangcao; Chen, Congtao; Kang, Xiyang; Wang, Cong; Zhao, Junhong; Yang, Qingxiang; Chen, Zhijun</TD>
<TD>Journal of Solid State Chemistry, Volume 292, article id. 121656.</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020JSSCh.29221656W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020JApA...41...48J</TD>
<TD>Merged white dwarfs and nucleosynthesis</TD>
<TD>Jeffery, C. Simon; Zhang, X.</TD>
<TD>Journal of Astrophysics and Astronomy, Volume 41, Issue 1, article id.48</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020JApA...41...48J</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020EPJC...80.1172G</TD>
<TD>Generalized absurdly benign traversable wormholes powered by Casimir energy</TD>
<TD>Garattini, Remo</TD>
<TD>The European Physical Journal C, Volume 80, Issue 12, article id.1172</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020EPJC...80.1172G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020CoBAO..67..181D</TD>
<TD>Detecting shock waves in non-fundamental mode RR Lyrae using large sample of spectra in SDSS and LAMOST</TD>
<TD>Duan, Xiao-Wei; Chen, Xiao-Dian; Deng, Li-Cai; Yang, Fan; Liu, Chao; Bhardwaj, Anupam; Zhang, Hua-Wei</TD>
<TD>Communications of the Byurakan Astrophysical Observatory (ComBAO), Volume 67, pp.181-186</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020CoBAO..67..181D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...905L..25S</TD>
<TD>An Early-warning System for Electromagnetic Follow-up of Gravitational-wave Events</TD>
<TD>Sachdev, Surabhi; Magee, Ryan; Hanna, Chad; Cannon, Kipp; Singer, Leo; SK, Javed Rana; Mukherjee, Debnandini; Caudill, Sarah; Chan, Chiwai; Creighton, Jolien D. E.; Ewing, Becca; Fong, Heather; Godwin, Patrick; Huxford, Rachael; Kapadia, Shasvath; Li, Alvin K. Y.; Lok Lo, Rico Ka; Meacher, Duncan; Messick, Cody; Mohite, Siddharth R.; Nishizawa, Atsushi; Ohta, Hiroaki; Pace, Alexander; Reza, Amit; Sathyaprakash, B. S.; Shikauchi, Minori; Singh, Divya; Tsukada, Leo; Tsuna, Daichi; Tsutsui, Takuya; Ueno, Koh</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 905, Issue 2, id.L25, 6 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...905L..25S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...905L...7B</TD>
<TD>An 8.8 Minute Orbital Period Eclipsing Detached Double White Dwarf Binary</TD>
<TD>Burdge, Kevin B.; Coughlin, Michael W.; Fuller, Jim; Kaplan, David L.; Kulkarni, S. R.; Marsh, Thomas R.; Bellm, Eric C.; Dekany, Richard G.; Duev, Dmitry A.; Graham, Matthew J.; Mahabal, Ashish A.; Masci, Frank J.; Laher, Russ R.; Riddle, Reed; Soumagnac, Maayane T.; Prince, Thomas A.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 905, Issue 1, id.L7, 11 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...905L...7B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...905L...5U</TD>
<TD>Application of The Wind-driven Model to a Sample of Tidal Disruption Events</TD>
<TD>Uno, Kohki; Maeda, Keiichi</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 905, Issue 1, id.L5, 6 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...905L...5U</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...905..145K</TD>
<TD>Kilonova Luminosity Function Constraints Based on Zwicky Transient Facility Searches for 13 Neutron Star Merger Triggers during O3</TD>
<TD>Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Anand, Shreya; Ahumada, Tomás; Stein, Robert; Carracedo, Ana Sagués; Andreoni, Igor; Coughlin, Michael W.; Singer, Leo P.; Kool, Erik C.; De, Kishalay; Kumar, Harsh; AlMualla, Mouza; Yao, Yuhan; Bulla, Mattia; Dobie, Dougal; Reusch, Simeon; Perley, Daniel A.; Cenko, S. Bradley; Bhalerao, Varun; Kaplan, David L.; Sollerman, Jesper; Goobar, Ariel; Copperwheat, Christopher M.; Bellm, Eric C.; Anupama, G. C.; Corsi, Alessandra; Nissanke, Samaya; Agudo, Iván; Bagdasaryan, Ashot; Barway, Sudhanshu; Belicki, Justin; Bloom, Joshua S.; Bolin, Bryce; Buckley, David A. H.; Burdge, Kevin B.; Burruss, Rick; Caballero-García, Maria D.; Cannella, Chris; Castro-Tirado, Alberto J.; Cook, David O.; Cooke, Jeff; Cunningham, Virginia; Dahiwale, Aishwarya; Deshmukh, Kunal; Dichiara, Simone; Duev, Dmitry A.; Dutta, Anirban; Feeney, Michael; Franckowiak, Anna; Frederick, Sara; Fremling, Christoffer; Gal-Yam, Avishay; Gatkine, Pradip; Ghosh, Shaon; Goldstein, Daniel A.; Golkhou, V. Zach; Graham, Matthew J.; Graham, Melissa L.; Hankins, Matthew J.; Helou, George; Hu, Youdong; Ip, Wing-Huen; Jaodand, Amruta; Karambelkar, Viraj; Kong, Albert K. H.; Kowalski, Marek; Khandagale, Maitreya; Kulkarni, S. R.; Kumar, Brajesh; Laher, Russ R.; Li, K. L.; Mahabal, Ashish; Masci, Frank J.; Miller, Adam A.; Mogotsi, Moses; Mohite, Siddharth; Mooley, Kunal; Mroz, Przemek; Newman, Jeffrey A.; Ngeow, Chow-Choong; Oates, Samantha R.; Patil, Atharva Sunil; Pandey, Shashi B.; Pavana, M.; Pian, Elena; Riddle, Reed; Sánchez-Ramírez, Rubén; Sharma, Yashvi; Singh, Avinash; Smith, Roger; Soumagnac, Maayane T.; Taggart, Kirsty; Tan, Hanjie; Tzanidakis, Anastasios; Troja, Eleonora; Valeev, Azamat F.; Walters, Richard; Waratkar, Gaurav; Webb, Sara; Yu, Po-Chieh; Zhang, Bin-Bin; Zhou, Rongpu; Zolkower, Jeffry</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 905, Issue 2, id.145, 31 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...905..145K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...905...98H</TD>
<TD>ZTF20aajnksq (AT 2020blt): A Fast Optical Transient at z ≈ 2.9 with No Detected Gamma-Ray Burst Counterpart</TD>
<TD>Ho, Anna Y. Q.; Perley, Daniel A.; Beniamini, Paz; Cenko, S. Bradley; Kulkarni, S. R.; Andreoni, Igor; Singer, Leo P.; De, Kishalay; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Fremling, Christoffer; Bellm, Eric C.; Dekany, Richard; Delacroix, Alexandre; Duev, Dmitry A.; Goldstein, Daniel A.; Golkhou, V. Zach; Goobar, Ariel; Graham, Matthew J.; Hale, David; Kupfer, Thomas; Laher, Russ R.; Masci, Frank J.; Miller, Adam A.; Neill, James D.; Riddle, Reed; Rusholme, Ben; Shupe, David L.; Smith, Roger; Sollerman, Jesper; van Roestel, Jan</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 905, Issue 2, id.98, 11 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...905...98H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...905...94V</TD>
<TD>SuperRAENN: A Semisupervised Supernova Photometric Classification Pipeline Trained on Pan-STARRS1 Medium-Deep Survey Supernovae</TD>
<TD>Villar, V. Ashley; Hosseinzadeh, Griffin; Berger, Edo; Ntampaka, Michelle; Jones, David O.; Challis, Peter; Chornock, Ryan; Drout, Maria R.; Foley, Ryan J.; Kirshner, Robert P.; Lunnan, Ragnhild; Margutti, Raffaella; Milisavljevic, Dan; Sanders, Nathan; Pan, Yen-Chen; Rest, Armin; Scolnic, Daniel M.; Magnier, Eugene; Metcalfe, Nigel; Wainscoat, Richard; Waters, Christopher</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 905, Issue 2, id.94, 21 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...905...94V</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...905...93H</TD>
<TD>Photometric Classification of 2315 Pan-STARRS1 Supernovae with Superphot</TD>
<TD>Hosseinzadeh, Griffin; Dauphin, Frederick; Villar, V. Ashley; Berger, Edo; Jones, David O.; Challis, Peter; Chornock, Ryan; Drout, Maria R.; Foley, Ryan J.; Kirshner, Robert P.; Lunnan, Ragnhild; Margutti, Raffaella; Milisavljevic, Dan; Pan, Yen-Chen; Rest, Armin; Scolnic, Daniel M.; Magnier, Eugene; Metcalfe, Nigel; Wainscoat, Richard; Waters, Christopher</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 905, Issue 2, id.93, 20 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...905...93H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...905...74N</TD>
<TD>Quasars That Have Transitioned from Radio-quiet to Radio-loud on Decadal Timescales Revealed by VLASS and FIRST</TD>
<TD>Nyland, Kristina; Dong, Dillon Z.; Patil, Pallavi; Lacy, Mark; van Velzen, Sjoert; Kimball, Amy E.; Sarbadhicary, Sumit K.; Hallinan, Gregg; Baldassare, Vivienne; Clarke, Tracy E.; Goulding, Andy D.; Greene, Jenny; Hughes, Andrew; Kassim, Namir; Kunert-Bajraszewska, Magdalena; Maccarone, Thomas J.; Mooley, Kunal; Mukherjee, Dipanjan; Peters, Wendy; Petrov, Leonid; Polisensky, Emil; Rujopakarn, Wiphu; Whittle, Mark; Vaccari, Mattia</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 905, Issue 1, id.74, 22 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...905...74N</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...905...58D</TD>
<TD>The Zwicky Transient Facility Census of the Local Universe. I. Systematic Search for Calcium-rich Gap Transients Reveals Three Related Spectroscopic Subclasses</TD>
<TD>De, Kishalay; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Tzanidakis, Anastasios; Fremling, U. Christoffer; Adams, Scott; Aloisi, Robert; Andreoni, Igor; Bagdasaryan, Ashot; Bellm, Eric C.; Bildsten, Lars; Cannella, Christopher; Cook, David O.; Delacroix, Alexandre; Drake, Andrew; Duev, Dmitry; Dugas, Alison; Frederick, Sara; Gal-Yam, Avishay; Goldstein, Daniel; Golkhou, V. Zach; Graham, Matthew J.; Hale, David; Hankins, Matthew; Helou, George; Ho, Anna Y. Q.; Irani, Ido; Jencson, Jacob E.; Kaplan, David L.; Kaye, Stephen; Kulkarni, S. R.; Kupfer, Thomas; Laher, Russ R.; Leadbeater, Robin; Lunnan, Ragnhild; Masci, Frank J.; Miller, Adam A.; Neill, James D.; Ofek, Eran O.; Perley, Daniel A.; Polin, Abigail; Prince, Thomas A.; Quataert, Eliot; Reiley, Dan; Riddle, Reed L.; Rusholme, Ben; Sharma, Yashvi; Shupe, David L.; Sollerman, Jesper; Tartaglia, Leonardo; Walters, Richard; Yan, Lin; Yao, Yuhan</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 905, Issue 1, id.58, 53 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...905...58D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...905...52G</TD>
<TD>High-redshift Extreme Variability Quasars from Sloan Digital Sky Survey Multiepoch Spectroscopy</TD>
<TD>Guo, Hengxiao; Peng, Jiacheng; Zhang, Kaiwen; Burke, Colin J.; Liu, Xin; Sun, Mouyuan; Wang, Shu; Kong, Minzhi; Sheng, Zhenfeng; Wang, Tinggui; He, Zhicheng; Gu, Minfeng</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 905, Issue 1, id.52, 19 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...905...52G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...905...32B</TD>
<TD>A Systematic Search of Zwicky Transient Facility Data for Ultracompact Binary LISA-detectable Gravitational-wave Sources</TD>
<TD>Burdge, Kevin B.; Prince, Thomas A.; Fuller, Jim; Kaplan, David L.; Marsh, Thomas R.; Tremblay, Pier-Emmanuel; Zhuang, Zhuyun; Bellm, Eric C.; Caiazzo, Ilaria; Coughlin, Michael W.; Dhillon, Vik S.; Gaensicke, Boris; Rodríguez-Gil, Pablo; Graham, Matthew J.; Hermes, JJ; Kupfer, Thomas; Littlefair, S. P.; Mróz, Przemek; Phinney, E. S.; van Roestel, Jan; Yao, Yuhan; Dekany, Richard G.; Drake, Andrew J.; Duev, Dmitry A.; Hale, David; Feeney, Michael; Helou, George; Kaye, Stephen; Mahabal, Ashish. A.; Masci, Frank J.; Riddle, Reed; Smith, Roger; Soumagnac, Maayane T.; Kulkarni, S. R.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 905, Issue 1, id.32, 26 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...905...32B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...904..169A</TD>
<TD>Standard Candles and Sirens Rescue H&lt;SUB&gt;0&lt;/SUB&gt;</TD>
<TD>Agrawal, Aniket; Okumura, Teppei; Futamase, Toshifumi</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 904, Issue 2, id.169, 5 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...904..169A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...904..155A</TD>
<TD>Constraining the Kilonova Rate with Zwicky Transient Facility Searches Independent of Gravitational Wave and Short Gamma-Ray Burst Triggers</TD>
<TD>Andreoni, Igor; Kool, Erik C.; Sagués Carracedo, Ana; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Bulla, Mattia; Ahumada, Tomás; Coughlin, Michael W.; Anand, Shreya; Sollerman, Jesper; Goobar, Ariel; Kaplan, David L.; Loveridge, Tegan T.; Karambelkar, Viraj; Cooke, Jeff; Bagdasaryan, Ashot; Bellm, Eric C.; Cenko, S. Bradley; Cook, David O.; De, Kishalay; Dekany, Richard; Delacroix, Alexandre; Drake, Andrew; Duev, Dmitry A.; Fremling, Christoffer; Golkhou, V. Zach; Graham, Matthew J.; Hale, David; Kulkarni, S. R.; Kupfer, Thomas; Laher, Russ R.; Mahabal, Ashish A.; Masci, Frank J.; Rusholme, Ben; Smith, Roger M.; Tzanidakis, Anastasios; Van Sistine, Angela; Yao, Yuhan</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 904, Issue 2, id.155, 19 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...904..155A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...904..146F</TD>
<TD>The First Extensive Spectroscopic Study of Young Stars in the North America and Pelican Nebulae</TD>
<TD>Fang, Min; Hillenbrand, Lynne A.; Kim, Jinyoung Serena; Findeisen, Krzysztof; Herczeg, Gregory J.; Carpenter, John M.; Rebull, Luisa M.; Wang, Hongchi</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 904, Issue 2, id.146, 26 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...904..146F</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...904...99R</TD>
<TD>Tidal Disruptions of Main-sequence Stars. II. Simulation Methodology and Stellar Mass Dependence of the Character of Full Tidal Disruptions</TD>
<TD>Ryu, Taeho; Krolik, Julian; Piran, Tsvi; Noble, Scott C.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 904, Issue 2, id.99, 15 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...904...99R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...904...98R</TD>
<TD>Tidal Disruptions of Main-sequence Stars. I. Observable Quantities and Their Dependence on Stellar and Black Hole Mass</TD>
<TD>Ryu, Taeho; Krolik, Julian; Piran, Tsvi; Noble, Scott C.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 904, Issue 2, id.98, 11 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...904...98R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020AcA....70..241P</TD>
<TD>Over 10000 δ Scuti Stars toward the Galactic Bulge from OGLE-IV</TD>
<TD>Pietrukowicz, P.; Soszyński, I.; Netzel, H.; Wrona, M.; Udalski, A.; Szymański, M. K.; Poleski, R.; Kozłowski, S.; Skowron, J.; Ulaczyk, DK.; Skowron, D. M.; Mróz, P.; Rybicki, K.; Iwanek, P.; Gromadzki, M.</TD>
<TD>Acta Astronomica, vol 70, no 4, p. 241-263</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020AcA....70..241P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020AJ....160..285V</TD>
<TD>An Asymmetric Eclipse Seen toward the Pre-main-sequence Binary System V928 Tau</TD>
<TD>van Dam, Dirk M.; Kenworthy, Matthew A.; David, Trevor J.; Mamajek, Eric E.; Hillenbrand, Lynne A.; Cody, Ann Marie; Howard, Andrew W.; Isaacson, Howard; Ciardi, David R.; Rebull, Luisa M.; Stauffer, John R.; Patel, Rahul; Cameron + WASP Collaborators, Andrew Collier; Rodriguez, Joseph E.; Pojmański, Grzegorz; Gonzales, Erica J.; Schlieder, Joshua E.; Hambsch, Franz-Josef; Dufoer, Sjoerd; Vanmunster, Tonny; Dubois, Franky; Vanaverbeke, Siegfried; Logie, Ludwig; Rau, Steve</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 160, Issue 6, id.285, 16 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020AJ....160..285V</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020AJ....160..278D</TD>
<TD>Periodic Eruptive Variability of the Isolated Pre-main-sequence Star V347 Aurigae</TD>
<TD>Dahm, S. E.; Hillenbrand, L. A.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 160, Issue 6, id.278, 16 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020AJ....160..278D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020AJ....160..277F</TD>
<TD>Establishing Earth's Minimoon Population through Characterization of Asteroid 2020 CD&lt;SUB&gt;3&lt;/SUB&gt;</TD>
<TD>Fedorets, Grigori; Micheli, Marco; Jedicke, Robert; Naidu, Shantanu P.; Farnocchia, Davide; Granvik, Mikael; Moskovitz, Nicholas; Schwamb, Megan E.; Weryk, Robert; Wierzchoś, Kacper; Christensen, Eric; Pruyne, Theodore; Bottke, William F.; Ye, Quanzhi; Wainscoat, Richard; Devogèle, Maxime; Buchanan, Laura E.; Djupvik, Anlaug Amanda; Faes, Daniel M.; Föhring, Dora; Roediger, Joel; Seccull, Tom; Smith, Adam B.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 160, Issue 6, id.277, 14 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020AJ....160..277F</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020AJ....160..259S</TD>
<TD>A Mini-Neptune and a Radius Valley Planet Orbiting the Nearby M2 Dwarf TOI-1266 in Its Venus Zone: Validation with the Habitable-zone Planet Finder</TD>
<TD>Stefánsson, Guðmundur; Kopparapu, Ravi; Lin, Andrea; Mahadevan, Suvrath; Cañas, Caleb I.; Kanodia, Shubham; Ninan, Joe P.; Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; Hebb, Leslie; Wisniewski, John; Gupta, Arvind; Everett, Mark; Bender, Chad F.; Diddams, Scott A.; Ford, Eric B.; Fredrick, Connor; Halverson, Samuel; Hearty, Fred; Levi, Eric; Maney, Marissa; Metcalf, Andrew J.; Monson, Andrew; Ramsey, Lawrence W.; Robertson, Paul; Roy, Arpita; Schwab, Christian; Terrien, Ryan C.; Wright, Jason T.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 160, Issue 6, id.259, 19 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020AJ....160..259S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020AJ....160..250R</TD>
<TD>Recoverability of Known Near-Earth Asteroids</TD>
<TD>Roa, Javier; Farnocchia, Davide; Chodas, Paul W.; Chesley, Steven R.; Park, Ryan S.; Naidu, Shantanu P.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 160, Issue 6, id.250, 12 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020AJ....160..250R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020A&amp;A...644A.176R</TD>
<TD>Strong dependence of Type Ia supernova standardization on the local specific star formation rate</TD>
<TD>Rigault, M.; Brinnel, V.; Aldering, G.; Antilogus, P.; Aragon, C.; Bailey, S.; Baltay, C.; Barbary, K.; Bongard, S.; Boone, K.; Buton, C.; Childress, M.; Chotard, N.; Copin, Y.; Dixon, S.; Fagrelius, P.; Feindt, U.; Fouchez, D.; Gangler, E.; Hayden, B.; Hillebrandt, W.; Howell, D. A.; Kim, A.; Kowalski, M.; Kuesters, D.; Leget, P. -F.; Lombardo, S.; Lin, Q.; Nordin, J.; Pain, R.; Pecontal, E.; Pereira, R.; Perlmutter, S.; Rabinowitz, D.; Runge, K.; Rubin, D.; Saunders, C.; Smadja, G.; Sofiatti, C.; Suzuki, N.; Taubenberger, S.; Tao, C.; Thomas, R. C.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 644, id.A176, 20 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020A&amp;A...644A.176R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020A&amp;A...644A.163C</TD>
<TD>HOLISMOKES. II. Identifying galaxy-scale strong gravitational lenses in Pan-STARRS using convolutional neural networks</TD>
<TD>Cañameras, R.; Schuldt, S.; Suyu, S. H.; Taubenberger, S.; Meinhardt, T.; Leal-Taixé, L.; Lemon, C.; Rojas, K.; Savary, E.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 644, id.A163, 27 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020A&amp;A...644A.163C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020A&amp;A...644A.162S</TD>
<TD>HOLISMOKES. I. Highly Optimised Lensing Investigations of Supernovae, Microlensing Objects, and Kinematics of Ellipticals and Spirals</TD>
<TD>Suyu, S. H.; Huber, S.; Cañameras, R.; Kromer, M.; Schuldt, S.; Taubenberger, S.; Yıldırım, A.; Bonvin, V.; Chan, J. H. H.; Courbin, F.; Nöbauer, U.; Sim, S. A.; Sluse, D.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 644, id.A162, 15 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020A&amp;A...644A.162S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020A&amp;A...644A..35P</TD>
<TD>Euclid: Identification of asteroid streaks in simulated images using StreakDet software</TD>
<TD>Pöntinen, M.; Granvik, M.; Nucita, A. A.; Conversi, L.; Altieri, B.; Auricchio, N.; Bodendorf, C.; Bonino, D.; Brescia, M.; Capobianco, V.; Carretero, J.; Carry, B.; Castellano, M.; Cledassou, R.; Congedo, G.; Corcione, L.; Cropper, M.; Dusini, S.; Frailis, M.; Franceschi, E.; Fumana, M.; Garilli, B.; Grupp, F.; Hormuth, F.; Israel, H.; Jahnke, K.; Kermiche, S.; Kitching, T.; Kohley, R.; Kubik, B.; Kunz, M.; Laureijs, R.; Lilje, P. B.; Lloro, I.; Maiorano, E.; Marggraf, O.; Massey, R.; Meneghetti, M.; Meylan, G.; Moscardini, L.; Padilla, C.; Paltani, S.; Pasian, F.; Pires, S.; Polenta, G.; Raison, F.; Roncarelli, M.; Rossetti, E.; Saglia, R.; Schneider, P.; Secroun, A.; Serrano, S.; Sirri, G.; Taylor, A. N.; Tereno, I.; Toledo-Moreo, R.; Valenziano, L.; Wang, Y.; Wetzstein, M.; Zoubian, J.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 644, id.A35, 12 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-12-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020A&amp;A...644A..35P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020Symm...12.1966P</TD>
<TD>Strongly Lensed Supernovae in Well-Studied Galaxy Clusters with the Vera C. Rubin Observatory</TD>
<TD>Petrushevska, Tanja</TD>
<TD>Symmetry, vol. 12, issue 12, p. 1966</TD>
<TD>2020-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020Symm...12.1966P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020PhR...886....1N</TD>
<TD>The electromagnetic counterparts of compact binary mergers</TD>
<TD>Nakar, Ehud</TD>
<TD>Physics Reports, Volume 886, p. 1-84.</TD>
<TD>2020-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020PhR...886....1N</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020PASP..132k4202G</TD>
<TD>Evryscope-South Survey of Upper- and Pre-main Sequence Solar Neighborhood Stars</TD>
<TD>Galliher, Nathan W.; Ratzloff, Jeffrey K.; Corbett, Hank; Law, Nicholas M.; Howard, Ward S.; Glazier, Amy L.; Vasquez Soto, Alan; Gonzalez, Ramses</TD>
<TD>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 132, Issue 1017, id.114202, 17 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020PASP..132k4202G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.499.1450P</TD>
<TD>SN 2018gjx reveals that some SNe Ibn are SNe IIb exploding in dense circumstellar material</TD>
<TD>Prentice, S. J.; Maguire, K.; Boian, I.; Groh, J.; Anderson, J.; Barbarino, C.; Bostroem, K. A.; Burke, J.; Clark, P.; Dong, Y.; Fraser, M.; Galbany, L.; Gromadzki, M.; Gutiérrez, C. P.; Howell, D. A.; Hiramatsu, D.; Inserra, C.; James, P. A.; Kankare, E.; Kuncarayakti, H.; Mazzali, P. A.; McCully, C.; Müller-Bravo, T. E.; Nichol, M.; Pellegrino, C.; Smartt, S. J.; Sollerman, J.; Tartaglia, L.; Valenti, S.; Young, D. R.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 499, Issue 1, pp.1450-1467</TD>
<TD>2020-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.499.1450P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.499..524G</TD>
<TD>Density-based outlier scoring on Kepler data</TD>
<TD>Giles, Daniel K.; Walkowicz, Lucianne</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 499, Issue 1, pp.524-542</TD>
<TD>2020-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.499..524G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.499..482N</TD>
<TD>An outflow powers the optical rise of the nearby, fast-evolving tidal disruption event AT2019qiz</TD>
<TD>Nicholl, M.; Wevers, T.; Oates, S. R.; Alexander, K. D.; Leloudas, G.; Onori, F.; Jerkstrand, A.; Gomez, S.; Campana, S.; Arcavi, I.; Charalampopoulos, P.; Gromadzki, M.; Ihanec, N.; Jonker, P. G.; Lawrence, A.; Mandel, I.; Schulze, S.; Short, P.; Burke, J.; McCully, C.; Hiramatsu, D.; Howell, D. A.; Pellegrino, C.; Abbot, H.; Anderson, J. P.; Berger, E.; Blanchard, P. K.; Cannizzaro, G.; Chen, T. -W.; Dennefeld, M.; Galbany, L.; González-Gaitán, S.; Hosseinzadeh, G.; Inserra, C.; Irani, I.; Kuin, P.; Müller-Bravo, T.; Pineda, J.; Ross, N. P.; Roy, R.; Smartt, S. J.; Smith, K. W.; Tucker, B.; Wyrzykowski, Ł.; Young, D. R.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 499, Issue 1, pp.482-504</TD>
<TD>2020-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.499..482N</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.498.4119S</TD>
<TD>The tidal disruption event AT 2018hyz - I. Double-peaked emission lines and a flat Balmer decrement</TD>
<TD>Short, P.; Nicholl, M.; Lawrence, A.; Gomez, S.; Arcavi, I.; Wevers, T.; Leloudas, G.; Schulze, S.; Anderson, J. P.; Berger, E.; Blanchard, P. K.; Burke, J.; Castro Segura, N.; Charalampopoulos, P.; Chornock, R.; Galbany, L.; Gromadzki, M.; Herzog, L. J.; Hiramatsu, D.; Horne, Keith; Hosseinzadeh, G.; Howell, D. Andrew; Ihanec, N.; Inserra, C.; Kankare, E.; Maguire, K.; McCully, C.; Müller Bravo, T. E.; Onori, F.; Sollerman, J.; Young, D. R.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 498, Issue 3, pp.4119-4133</TD>
<TD>2020-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.498.4119S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.498.3077W</TD>
<TD>Unsupervised machine learning for transient discovery in deeper, wider, faster light curves</TD>
<TD>Webb, Sara; Lochner, Michelle; Muthukrishna, Daniel; Cooke, Jeff; Flynn, Chris; Mahabal, Ashish; Goode, Simon; Andreoni, Igor; Pritchard, Tyler; Abbott, Timothy M. C.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 498, Issue 3, pp.3077-3094</TD>
<TD>2020-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.498.3077W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020JCAP...11..055P</TD>
<TD>Constraining the host galaxy halos of massive black holes from LISA event rates</TD>
<TD>Padmanabhan, Hamsa; Loeb, Abraham</TD>
<TD>Journal of Cosmology and Astroparticle Physics, Issue 11, article id. 055 (2020).</TD>
<TD>2020-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020JCAP...11..055P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...904...74G</TD>
<TD>FLEET: A Redshift-agnostic Machine Learning Pipeline to Rapidly Identify Hydrogen-poor Superluminous Supernovae</TD>
<TD>Gomez, Sebastian; Berger, Edo; Blanchard, Peter K.; Hosseinzadeh, Griffin; Nicholl, Matt; Villar, V. Ashley; Yin, Yao</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 904, Issue 1, id.74, 12 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...904...74G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...904...56G</TD>
<TD>Stars Stripped in Binaries: The Living Gravitational-wave Sources</TD>
<TD>Götberg, Y.; Korol, V.; Lamberts, A.; Kupfer, T.; Breivik, K.; Ludwig, B.; Drout, M. R.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 904, Issue 1, id.56, 14 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...904...56G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...904...35P</TD>
<TD>The Zwicky Transient Facility Bright Transient Survey. II. A Public Statistical Sample for Exploring Supernova Demographics</TD>
<TD>Perley, Daniel A.; Fremling, Christoffer; Sollerman, Jesper; Miller, Adam A.; Dahiwale, Aishwarya S.; Sharma, Yashvi; Bellm, Eric C.; Biswas, Rahul; Brink, Thomas G.; Bruch, Rachel J.; De, Kishalay; Dekany, Richard; Drake, Andrew J.; Duev, Dmitry A.; Filippenko, Alexei V.; Gal-Yam, Avishay; Goobar, Ariel; Graham, Matthew J.; Graham, Melissa L.; Ho, Anna Y. Q.; Irani, Ido; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Kim, Young-Lo; Kulkarni, S. R.; Mahabal, Ashish; Masci, Frank J.; Modak, Shaunak; Neill, James D.; Nordin, Jakob; Riddle, Reed L.; Soumagnac, Maayane T.; Strotjohann, Nora L.; Schulze, Steve; Taggart, Kirsty; Tzanidakis, Anastasios; Walters, Richard S.; Yan, Lin</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 904, Issue 1, id.35, 24 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...904...35P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...904....4F</TD>
<TD>High-energy Neutrinos and Gamma Rays from Nonrelativistic Shock-powered Transients</TD>
<TD>Fang, Ke; Metzger, Brian D.; Vurm, Indrek; Aydi, Elias; Chomiuk, Laura</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 904, Issue 1, id.4, 17 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...904....4F</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...903L..27C</TD>
<TD>Orbital Foregrounds for Ultra-short Duration Transients</TD>
<TD>Corbett, Hank; Law, Nicholas M.; Soto, Alan Vasquez; Howard, Ward S.; Glazier, Amy; Gonzalez, Ramses; Ratzloff, Jeffrey K.; Galliher, Nathan; Fors, Octavi; Quimby, Robert</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 903, Issue 2, id.L27, 7 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...903L..27C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...903..132H</TD>
<TD>A Non-equipartition Shock Wave Traveling in a Dense Circumstellar Environment around SN 2020oi</TD>
<TD>Horesh, Assaf; Sfaradi, Itai; Ergon, Mattias; Barbarino, Cristina; Sollerman, Jesper; Moldon, Javier; Dobie, Dougal; Schulze, Steve; Pérez-Torres, Miguel; Williams, David R. A.; Fremling, Christoffer; Gal-Yam, Avishay; Kulkarni, Shrinivas R.; O'Brien, Andrew; Lundqvist, Peter; Murphy, Tara; Fender, Rob; Anand, Shreya; Belicki, Justin; Bellm, Eric C.; Coughlin, Michael W.; De, Kishalay; Golkhou, V. Zach; Graham, Matthew J.; Green, Dave A.; Hankins, Matt; Kasliwal, Mansi; Kupfer, Thomas; Laher, Russ R.; Masci, Frank J.; Miller, A. A.; Neill, James D.; Ofek, Eran O.; Perrott, Yvette; Porter, Michael; Reiley, Daniel J.; Rigault, Mickael; Rodriguez, Hector; Rusholme, Ben; Shupe, David L.; Titterington, David</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 903, Issue 2, id.132, 15 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...903..132H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...903..116A</TD>
<TD>Caltech-NRAO Stripe 82 Survey (CNSS). III. The First Radio-discovered Tidal Disruption Event, CNSS J0019+00</TD>
<TD>Anderson, M. M.; Mooley, K. P.; Hallinan, G.; Dong, D.; Phinney, E. S.; Horesh, A.; Bourke, S.; Cenko, S. B.; Frail, D.; Kulkarni, S. R.; Myers, S.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 903, Issue 2, id.116, 12 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...903..116A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...903...54T</TD>
<TD>Deep Modeling of Quasar Variability</TD>
<TD>Tachibana, Yutaro; Graham, Matthew J.; Kawai, Nobuyuki; Djorgovski, S. G.; Drake, Andrew J.; Mahabal, Ashish A.; Stern, Daniel</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 903, Issue 1, id.54, 17 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...903...54T</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020A&amp;A...643A.130Z</TD>
<TD>Light-time effect detected in fourteen eclipsing binaries</TD>
<TD>Zasche, P.; Uhlař, R.; Svoboda, P.; Cagaš, P.; Mašek, M.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 643, id.A130, 10 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020A&amp;A...643A.130Z</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020A&amp;A...643A.113A</TD>
<TD>Observational constraints on the optical and near-infrared emission from the neutron star-black hole binary merger candidate S190814bv</TD>
<TD>Ackley, K.; Amati, L.; Barbieri, C.; Bauer, F. E.; Benetti, S.; Bernardini, M. G.; Bhirombhakdi, K.; Botticella, M. T.; Branchesi, M.; Brocato, E.; Bruun, S. H.; Bulla, M.; Campana, S.; Cappellaro, E.; Castro-Tirado, A. J.; Chambers, K. C.; Chaty, S.; Chen, T. -W.; Ciolfi, R.; Coleiro, A.; Copperwheat, C. M.; Covino, S.; Cutter, R.; D'Ammando, F.; D'Avanzo, P.; De Cesare, G.; D'Elia, V.; Della Valle, M.; Denneau, L.; De Pasquale, M.; Dhillon, V. S.; Dyer, M. J.; Elias-Rosa, N.; Evans, P. A.; Eyles-Ferris, R. A. J.; Fiore, A.; Fraser, M.; Fruchter, A. S.; Fynbo, J. P. U.; Galbany, L.; Gall, C.; Galloway, D. K.; Getman, F. I.; Ghirlanda, G.; Gillanders, J. H.; Gomboc, A.; Gompertz, B. P.; González-Fernández, C.; González-Gaitán, S.; Grado, A.; Greco, G.; Gromadzki, M.; Groot, P. J.; Gutiérrez, C. P.; Heikkilä, T.; Heintz, K. E.; Hjorth, J.; Hu, Y. -D.; Huber, M. E.; Inserra, C.; Izzo, L.; Japelj, J.; Jerkstrand, A.; Jin, Z. P.; Jonker, P. G.; Kankare, E.; Kann, D. A.; Kennedy, M.; Kim, S.; Klose, S.; Kool, E. C.; Kotak, R.; Kuncarayakti, H.; Lamb, G. P.; Leloudas, G.; Levan, A. J.; Longo, F.; Lowe, T. B.; Lyman, J. D.; Magnier, E.; Maguire, K.; Maiorano, E.; Mandel, I.; Mapelli, M.; Mattila, S.; McBrien, O. R.; Melandri, A.; Michałowski, M. J.; Milvang-Jensen, B.; Moran, S.; Nicastro, L.; Nicholl, M.; Nicuesa Guelbenzu, A.; Nuttal, L.; Oates, S. R.; O'Brien, P. T.; Onori, F.; Palazzi, E.; Patricelli, B.; Perego, A.; Torres, M. A. P.; Perley, D. A.; Pian, E.; Pignata, G.; Piranomonte, S.; Poshyachinda, S.; Possenti, A.; Pumo, M. L.; Quirola-Vásquez, J.; Ragosta, F.; Ramsay, G.; Rau, A.; Rest, A.; Reynolds, T. M.; Rosetti, S. S.; Rossi, A.; Rosswog, S.; Sabha, N. B.; Sagués Carracedo, A.; Salafia, O. S.; Salmon, L.; Salvaterra, R.; Savaglio, S.; Sbordone, L.; Schady, P.; Schipani, P.; Schultz, A. S. B.; Schweyer, T.; Smartt, S. J.; Smith, K. W.; Smith, M.; Sollerman, J.; Srivastav, S.; Stanway, E. R.; Starling, R. L. C.; Steeghs, D.; Stratta, G.; Stubbs, C. W.; Tanvir, N. R.; Testa, V.; Thrane, E.; Tonry, J. L.; Turatto, M.; Ulaczyk, K.; van der Horst, A. J.; Vergani, S. D.; Walton, N. A.; Watson, D.; Wiersema, K.; Wiik, K.; Wyrzykowski, Ł.; Yang, S.; Yi, S. -X.; Young, D. R.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 643, id.A113, 48 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020A&amp;A...643A.113A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020A&amp;A...643A..99B</TD>
<TD>Investigating the magnetospheric accretion process in the young pre-transitional disk system DoAr 44 (V2062 Oph). A multiwavelength interferometric, spectropolarimetric, and photometric observing campaign</TD>
<TD>Bouvier, J.; Alecian, E.; Alencar, S. H. P.; Sousa, A.; Donati, J. -F.; Perraut, K.; Bayo, A.; Rebull, L. M.; Dougados, C.; Duvert, G.; Berger, J. -P.; Benisty, M.; Pouilly, K.; Folsom, C.; Moutou, C.; SPIRou Consortium</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 643, id.A99, 18 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020A&amp;A...643A..99B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020A&amp;A...643A..79S</TD>
<TD>Two stripped envelope supernovae with circumstellar interaction. But only one really shows it</TD>
<TD>Sollerman, J.; Fransson, C.; Barbarino, C.; Fremling, C.; Horesh, A.; Kool, E.; Schulze, S.; Sfaradi, I.; Yang, S.; Bellm, E. C.; Burruss, R.; Cunningham, V.; De, K.; Drake, A. J.; Golkhou, V. Z.; Green, D. A.; Kasliwal, M.; Kulkarni, S.; Kupfer, T.; Laher, R. R.; Masci, F. J.; Rodriguez, H.; Rusholme, B.; Williams, D. R. A.; Yan, L.; Zolkower, J.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 643, id.A79, 13 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020A&amp;A...643A..79S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020A&amp;A...643A..35P</TD>
<TD>First systematic high-precision survey of bright supernovae. I. Methodology for identifying early bumps</TD>
<TD>Paraskeva, E.; Bonanos, A. Z.; Liakos, A.; Spetsieri, Z. T.; Maund, J. R.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 643, id.A35, 22 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-11-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020A&amp;A...643A..35P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020SSRv..216..124V</TD>
<TD>Optical-Ultraviolet Tidal Disruption Events</TD>
<TD>van Velzen, Sjoert; Holoien, Thomas W. -S.; Onori, Francesca; Hung, Tiara; Arcavi, Iair</TD>
<TD>Space Science Reviews, Volume 216, Issue 8, article id.124</TD>
<TD>2020-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020SSRv..216..124V</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020RAA....20..160W</TD>
<TD>Observational signatures of close binaries of supermassive black holes in active galactic nuclei</TD>
<TD>Wang, Jian-Min; Li, Yan-Rong</TD>
<TD>Research in Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 20, Issue 10, id.160, 16 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020RAA....20..160W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020PhRvD.102h3028L</TD>
<TD>Neutrino emission from an off-axis jet driven by the tidal disruption event AT2019dsg</TD>
<TD>Liu, Ruo-Yu; Xi, Shao-Qiang; Wang, Xiang-Yu</TD>
<TD>Physical Review D, Volume 102, Issue 8, article id.083028</TD>
<TD>2020-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020PhRvD.102h3028L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020PASP..132j4501X</TD>
<TD>GWOPS: A VO-technology Driven Tool to Search for the Electromagnetic Counterpart of Gravitational Wave Event</TD>
<TD>Xu, Yunfei; Xu, Dong; Cui, Chenzhou; Fan, Dongwei; Zhu, Zipei; Yu, Bangyao; Li, Changhua; Han, Jun; Mi, Linying; Li, Shanshan; He, Boliang; Tao, Yihan; Yang, Hanxi; Yang, Sisi</TD>
<TD>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 132, Issue 1016, id.104501, 12 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020PASP..132j4501X</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020PASP..132j1001S</TD>
<TD>Exocomets from a Solar System Perspective</TD>
<TD>Strøm, Paul A.; Bodewits, Dennis; Knight, Matthew M.; Kiefer, Flavien; Jones, Geraint H.; Kral, Quentin; Matrà, Luca; Bodman, Eva; Capria, Maria Teresa; Cleeves, Ilsedore; Fitzsimmons, Alan; Haghighipour, Nader; Harrison, John H. D.; Iglesias, Daniela; Kama, Mihkel; Linnartz, Harold; Majumdar, Liton; de Mooij, Ernst J. W.; Milam, Stefanie N.; Opitom, Cyrielle; Rebollido, Isabel; Rogers, Laura K.; Snodgrass, Colin; Sousa-Silva, Clara; Xu, Siyi; Lin, Zhong-Yi; Zieba, Sebastian</TD>
<TD>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 132, Issue 1016, id.101001, 19 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020PASP..132j1001S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020PASJ...72...89T</TD>
<TD>Photometric classification of Hyper Suprime-Cam transients using machine learning</TD>
<TD>Takahashi, Ichiro; Suzuki, Nao; Yasuda, Naoki; Kimura, Akisato; Ueda, Naonori; Tanaka, Masaomi; Tominaga, Nozomu; Yoshida, Naoki</TD>
<TD>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Volume 72, Issue 5, id.89, 22 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020PASJ...72...89T</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.498.2575W</TD>
<TD>The host galaxies of 106 rapidly evolving transients discovered by the Dark Energy Survey</TD>
<TD>Wiseman, P.; Pursiainen, M.; Childress, M.; Swann, E.; Smith, M.; Galbany, L.; Lidman, C.; Davis, T. M.; Gutiérrez, C. P.; Möller, A.; Thomas, B. P.; Frohmaier, C.; Foley, R. J.; Hinton, S. R.; Kelsey, L.; Kessler, R.; Lewis, G. F.; Sako, M.; Scolnic, D.; Sullivan, M.; Vincenzi, M.; Abbott, T. M. C.; Aguena, M.; Allam, S.; Annis, J.; Bertin, E.; Bhargava, S.; Brooks, D.; Burke, D. L.; Carnero Rosell, A.; Carollo, D.; Carrasco Kind, M.; Carretero, J.; Costanzi, M.; da Costa, L. N.; Diehl, H. T.; Doel, P.; Everett, S.; Fosalba, P.; Frieman, J.; García-Bellido, J.; Gaztanaga, E.; Glazebrook, K.; Gruen, D.; Gruendl, R. A.; Gschwend, J.; Gutierrez, G.; Hollowood, D. L.; Honscheid, K.; James, D. J.; Kuehn, K.; Kuropatkin, N.; Lima, M.; Maia, M. A. G.; Marshall, J. L.; Martini, P.; Menanteau, F.; Miquel, R.; Palmese, A.; Paz-Chinchón, F.; Plazas, A. A.; Romer, A. K.; Sanchez, E.; Scarpine, V.; Schubnell, M.; Serrano, S.; Sevilla-Noarbe, I.; Sommer, N. E.; Suchyta, E.; Swanson, M. E. C.; Tarle, G.; Tucker, B. E.; Tucker, D. L.; Varga, T. N.; Walker, A. R.; Walker, A. R.; (DES Collaboration)</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 498, Issue 2, pp.2575-2593</TD>
<TD>2020-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.498.2575W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.498.2339R</TD>
<TD>The first high-redshift changing-look quasars</TD>
<TD>Ross, Nicholas P.; Graham, Matthew J.; Calderone, Giorgio; Ford, K. E. Saavik; McKernan, Barry; Stern, Daniel</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 498, Issue 2, pp.2339-2353</TD>
<TD>2020-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.498.2339R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.498...33R</TD>
<TD>K2: Background Survey - the search for undiscovered transients in Kepler/K2 data</TD>
<TD>Ridden-Harper, R.; Tucker, B. E.; Gully-Santiago, M.; Barentsen, G.; Rest, A.; Garnavich, P.; Shaya, E.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 498, Issue 1, pp.33-43</TD>
<TD>2020-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.498...33R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.497.5518A</TD>
<TD>GRANDMA observations of advanced LIGO's and advanced Virgo's third observational campaign</TD>
<TD>Antier, S.; Agayeva, S.; Almualla, M.; Awiphan, S.; Baransky, A.; Barynova, K.; Beradze, S.; Blažek, M.; Boër, M.; Burkhonov, O.; Christensen, N.; Coleiro, A.; Corre, D.; Coughlin, M. W.; Crisp, H.; Dietrich, T.; Ducoin, J. -G.; Duverne, P. -A.; Marchal-Duval, G.; Gendre, B.; Gokuldass, P.; Eggenstein, H. B.; Eymar, L.; Hello, P.; Howell, E. J.; Ismailov, N.; Kann, D. A.; Karpov, S.; Klotz, A.; Kochiashvili, N.; Lachaud, C.; Leroy, N.; Lin, W. L.; Li, W. X.; Mašek, M.; Mo, J.; Menard, R.; Morris, D.; Noysena, K.; Orange, N. B.; Prouza, M.; Rattanamala, R.; Sadibekova, T.; Saint-Gelais, D.; Serrau, M.; Simon, A.; Stachie, C.; Thöne, C. C.; Tillayev, Y.; Turpin, D.; Postigo, A. de Ugarte; Vasylenko, V.; Vidadi, Z.; Was, M.; Wang, X. F.; Zhang, J. J.; Zhang, T. M.; Zhang, X. H.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 497, Issue 4, pp.5518-5539</TD>
<TD>2020-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.497.5518A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.497.5364B</TD>
<TD>A multiwavelength search for black widow and redback counterparts of candidate γ-ray millisecond pulsars</TD>
<TD>Braglia, C.; Mignani, R. P.; Belfiore, A.; Marelli, M.; Israel, G. L.; Novara, G.; De Luca, A.; Tiengo, A.; Saz Parkinson, P. M.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 497, Issue 4, pp.5364-5382</TD>
<TD>2020-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.497.5364B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.497.4602F</TD>
<TD>A survey for variable young stars with small telescopes - III. Warm spots on the active star V1598 Cyg</TD>
<TD>Froebrich, Dirk; Scholz, Aleks; Eislöffel, Jochen; Stecklum, Bringfried</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 497, Issue 4, pp.4602-4613</TD>
<TD>2020-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.497.4602F</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.497.4091M</TD>
<TD>Dynamical evolution of two-planet systems and its connection with white dwarf atmospheric pollution</TD>
<TD>Maldonado, R. F.; Villaver, E.; Mustill, A. J.; Chavez, M.; Bertone, E.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 497, Issue 4, pp.4091-4106</TD>
<TD>2020-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.497.4091M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...902L..29N</TD>
<TD>Gravitational-wave Merger Forecasting: Scenarios for the Early Detection and Localization of Compact-binary Mergers with Ground-based Observatories</TD>
<TD>Nitz, Alexander H.; Schäfer, Marlin; Dal Canton, Tito</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 902, Issue 2, id.L29, 7 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...902L..29N</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...902L...8Y</TD>
<TD>Helium-rich Superluminous Supernovae from the Zwicky Transient Facility</TD>
<TD>Yan, Lin; Perley, D. A.; Schulze, S.; Lunnan, R.; Sollerman, J.; De, K.; Chen, Z. H.; Fremling, C.; Gal-Yam, A.; Taggart, K.; Chen, T. -W.; Andreoni, I.; Bellm, E. C.; Cunningham, V.; Dekany, R.; Duev, D. A.; Fransson, C.; Laher, R. R.; Hankins, M.; Ho, A. Y. Q.; Jencson, J. E.; Kaye, S.; Kulkarni, S. R.; Kasliwal, M. M.; Golkhou, V. Z.; Graham, M.; Masci, F. J.; Miller, A. A.; Neill, J. D.; Ofek, E.; Porter, M.; Mróz, P.; Reiley, D.; Riddle, R.; Rigault, M.; Rusholme, B.; Shupe, D. L.; Soumagnac, M. T.; Smith, R.; Tartaglia, L.; Yao, Y.; Yaron, O.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 902, Issue 1, id.L8, 8 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...902L...8Y</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...902..108M</TD>
<TD>High-energy Neutrino and Gamma-Ray Emission from Tidal Disruption Events</TD>
<TD>Murase, Kohta; Kimura, Shigeo S.; Zhang, B. Theodore; Oikonomou, Foteini; Petropoulou, Maria</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 902, Issue 2, id.108, 13 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...902..108M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...902...92R</TD>
<TD>EVR-CB-004: An Inflated Hot Subdwarf O Star + Unseen WD Companion in a Compact Binary Discovered with the Evryscope</TD>
<TD>Ratzloff, Jeffrey K.; Kupfer, Thomas; Barlow, Brad N.; Schneider, David; Marsh, Thomas R.; Heber, Ulrich; Corcoran, Kyle A.; Bauer, Evan; Hämmerich, Steven; Corbett, Henry T.; Glazier, Amy; Howard, Ward S.; Law, Nicholas M.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 902, Issue 2, id.92, 18 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...902...92R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...902...86H</TD>
<TD>SN 2020bvc: A Broad-line Type Ic Supernova with a Double-peaked Optical Light Curve and a Luminous X-Ray and Radio Counterpart</TD>
<TD>Ho, Anna Y. Q.; Kulkarni, S. R.; Perley, Daniel A.; Cenko, S. Bradley; Corsi, Alessandra; Schulze, Steve; Lunnan, Ragnhild; Sollerman, Jesper; Gal-Yam, Avishay; Anand, Shreya; Barbarino, Cristina; Bellm, Eric C.; Bruch, Rachel J.; Burns, Eric; De, Kishalay; Dekany, Richard; Delacroix, Alexandre; Duev, Dmitry A.; Frederiks, Dmitry D.; Fremling, Christoffer; Goldstein, Daniel A.; Golkhou, V. Zach; Graham, Matthew J.; Hale, David; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Kupfer, Thomas; Laher, Russ R.; Martikainen, Julia; Masci, Frank J.; Neill, James D.; Ridnaia, Anna; Rusholme, Ben; Savchenko, Volodymyr; Shupe, David L.; Soumagnac, Maayane T.; Strotjohann, Nora L.; Svinkin, Dmitry S.; Taggart, Kirsty; Tartaglia, Leonardo; Yan, Lin; Zolkower, Jeffry</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 902, Issue 1, id.86, 22 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...902...86H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...902...71P</TD>
<TD>Localization of Compact Binary Sources with Second-generation Gravitational-wave Interferometer Networks</TD>
<TD>Pankow, Chris; Rizzo, Monica; Rao, Kaushik; Berry, Christopher P. L.; Kalogera, Vassiliki</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 902, Issue 1, id.71, 14 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...902...71P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...902...60B</TD>
<TD>Star Formation and Morphological Properties of Galaxies in the Pan-STARRS 3π Survey. I. A Machine-learning Approach to Galaxy and Supernova Classification</TD>
<TD>Baldeschi, A.; Miller, A.; Stroh, M.; Margutti, R.; Coppejans, D. L.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 902, Issue 1, id.60, 17 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...902...60B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...902...48B</TD>
<TD>ZTF Early Observations of Type Ia Supernovae. III. Early-time Colors As a Test for Explosion Models and Multiple Populations</TD>
<TD>Bulla, Mattia; Miller, Adam A.; Yao, Yuhan; Dessart, Luc; Dhawan, Suhail; Papadogiannakis, Semeli; Biswas, Rahul; Goobar, Ariel; Kulkarni, S. R.; Nordin, Jakob; Nugent, Peter; Polin, Abigail; Sollerman, Jesper; Bellm, Eric C.; Coughlin, Michael W.; Dekany, Richard; Golkhou, V. Zach; Graham, Matthew J.; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Kupfer, Thomas; Laher, Russ R.; Masci, Frank J.; Porter, Michael; Rusholme, Ben; Shupe, David L.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 902, Issue 1, id.48, 14 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...902...48B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...902...47M</TD>
<TD>ZTF Early Observations of Type Ia Supernovae. II. First Light, the Initial Rise, and Time to Reach Maximum Brightness</TD>
<TD>Miller, A. A.; Yao, Y.; Bulla, M.; Pankow, C.; Bellm, E. C.; Cenko, S. B.; Dekany, R.; Fremling, C.; Graham, M. J.; Kupfer, T.; Laher, R. R.; Mahabal, A. A.; Masci, F. J.; Nugent, P. E.; Riddle, R.; Rusholme, B.; Smith, R. M.; Shupe, D. L.; van Roestel, J.; Kulkarni, S. R.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 902, Issue 1, id.47, 25 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...902...47M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...902...46Y</TD>
<TD>The Young and Nearby Normal Type Ia Supernova 2018gv: UV-optical Observations and the Earliest Spectropolarimetry</TD>
<TD>Yang, Yi; Hoeflich, Peter; Baade, Dietrich; Maund, Justyn R.; Wang, Lifan; Brown, Peter. J.; Stevance, Heloise F.; Arcavi, Iair; Burke, Jamison; Cikota, Aleksandar; Clocchiatti, Alejandro; Gal-Yam, Avishay; Graham, Melissa. L.; Hiramatsu, Daichi; Hosseinzadeh, Griffin; Howell, D. Andrew; Jha, Saurabh W.; McCully, Curtis; Patat, Ferdinando; Sand, David. J.; Schulze, Steve; Spyromilio, Jason; Valenti, Stefano; Vinkó, József; Wang, Xiaofeng; Wheeler, J. Craig; Yaron, Ofer; Zhang, Jujia</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 902, Issue 1, id.46, 35 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...902...46Y</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...902....6S</TD>
<TD>SN 2018fif: The Explosion of a Large Red Supergiant Discovered in Its Infancy by the Zwicky Transient Facility</TD>
<TD>Soumagnac, Maayane T.; Ganot, Noam; Irani, Ido; Gal-yam, Avishay; Ofek, Eran O.; Waxman, Eli; Morag, Jonathan; Yaron, Ofer; Schulze, Steve; Yang, Yi; Rubin, Adam; Cenko, S. Bradley; Sollerman, Jesper; Perley, Daniel A.; Fremling, Christoffer; Nugent, Peter; Neill, James D.; Karamehmetoglu, Emir; Bellm, Eric C.; Bruch, Rachel J.; Burruss, Rick; Cunningham, Virginia; Dekany, Richard; Golkhou, V. Zach; Graham, Matthew J.; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Konidaris, Nicholas P.; Kulkarni, Shrinivas R.; Kupfer, Thomas; Laher, Russ R.; Masci, Frank J.; Riddle, Reed; Rigault, Mickael; Rusholme, Ben; van Roestel, Jan; Zackay, Barak</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 902, Issue 1, id.6, 15 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...902....6S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020AJ....160..164H</TD>
<TD>The Outburst of the Young Star Gaia19bey</TD>
<TD>Hodapp, Klaus W.; Denneau, Larry; Tucker, Michael; Shappee, Benjamin J.; Huber, Mark E.; Payne, Anna V.; Do, Aaron; Lin, Chien-Cheng; Connelley, Michael S.; Varricatt, Watson P.; Tonry, John; Chambers, Kenneth; Magnier, Eugene</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 160, Issue 4, id.164, 13 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020AJ....160..164H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020A&amp;C....3300411N</TD>
<TD>Data Lab-A community science platform</TD>
<TD>Nikutta, R.; Fitzpatrick, M.; Scott, A.; Weaver, B. A.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy and Computing, Volume 33, article id. 100411.</TD>
<TD>2020-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020A&amp;C....3300411N</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020A&amp;A...642A.160G</TD>
<TD>Constraining the transient high-energy activity of &lt;ASTROBJ&gt;FRB 180916.J0158+65&lt;/ASTROBJ&gt; with Insight-HXMT follow-up observations</TD>
<TD>Guidorzi, C.; Orlandini, M.; Frontera, F.; Nicastro, L.; Xiong, S. L.; Liao, J. Y.; Li, G.; Zhang, S. N.; Amati, L.; Virgilli, E.; Zhang, S.; Bu, Q. C.; Cai, C.; Cao, X. L.; Chang, Z.; Chen, L.; Chen, T. X.; Chen, Y.; Chen, Y. P.; Cui, W. W.; Du, Y. Y.; Gao, G. H.; Gao, H.; Gao, M.; Ge, M. Y.; Gu, Y. D.; Guan, J.; Guo, C. C.; Han, D. W.; Huang, Y.; Huo, J.; Jia, S. M.; Jiang, W. C.; Jin, J.; Kong, L. D.; Li, B.; Li, C. K.; Li, T. P.; Li, W.; Li, X.; Li, X. B.; Li, X. F.; Li, Z. W.; Liang, X. H.; Liu, B. S.; Liu, C. Z.; Liu, H. X.; Liu, H. W.; Liu, X. J.; Lu, F. J.; Lu, X. F.; Luo, Q.; Luo, T.; Ma, R. C.; Ma, X.; Meng, B.; Nang, Y.; Nie, J. Y.; Ou, G.; Qu, J. L.; Ren, X. Q.; Sai, N.; Song, L. M.; Song, X. Y.; Sun, L.; Tan, Y.; Tao, L.; Tuo, Y. L.; Wang, C.; Wang, L. J.; Wang, P. J.; Wang, W. S.; Wang, Y. S.; Wen, X. Y.; Wu, B. Y.; Wu, B. B.; Wu, M.; Xiao, G. C.; Xiao, S.; Xu, Y. P.; Yang, R.; Yang, S.; Yang, Y. J.; Yi, Q. B.; Yin, Q. Q.; You, Y.; Zhang, F.; Zhang, H. M.; Zhang, J.; Zhang, P.; Zhang, W. C.; Zhang, W.; Zhang, Y. F.; Zhang, Y. H.; Zhao, H. S.; Zhao, X. F.; Zheng, S. J.; Zheng, Y. G.; Zhou, D. K.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 642, id.A160, 9 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-10-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020A&amp;A...642A.160G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020RAA....20..135W</TD>
<TD>The formation of neutron star systems through accretion-induced collapse in white-dwarf binaries</TD>
<TD>Wang, Bo; Liu, Dongdong</TD>
<TD>Research in Astronomy and Astrophysics, Volume 20, Issue 9, id.135, 24 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020RAA....20..135W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020PhyOJ..13..111P</TD>
<TD>A Heavyweight Merger</TD>
<TD>Perna, Rosalba</TD>
<TD>Physics, Volume 13, article id. 111</TD>
<TD>2020-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020PhyOJ..13..111P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020PhRvD.102f3021H</TD>
<TD>Science with the TianQin Observatory: Preliminary results on Galactic double white dwarf binaries</TD>
<TD>Huang, Shun-Jia; Hu, Yi-Ming; Korol, Valeriya; Li, Peng-Cheng; Liang, Zheng-Cheng; Lu, Yang; Wang, Hai-Tian; Yu, Shenghua; Mei, Jianwei</TD>
<TD>Physical Review D, Volume 102, Issue 6, article id.063021</TD>
<TD>2020-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020PhRvD.102f3021H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020PSJ.....1...47P</TD>
<TD>A Deep Search for Stable Venus Co-orbital Asteroids: Limits on the Population</TD>
<TD>Pokorný, Petr; Kuchner, Marc J.; Sheppard, Scott S.</TD>
<TD>The Planetary Science Journal, Volume 1, Issue 2, id.47, 10 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020PSJ.....1...47P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020PDU....2900519G</TD>
<TD>On the amount of peculiar velocity field information in supernovae from LSST and beyond</TD>
<TD>Garcia, Karolina; Quartin, Miguel; Siffert, Beatriz B.</TD>
<TD>Physics of the Dark Universe, Volume 29, article id. 100519.</TD>
<TD>2020-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020PDU....2900519G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020NewSc.247...19C</TD>
<TD>Gravitational wave detectors find their biggest black hole yet</TD>
<TD>Crane, Leah</TD>
<TD>New Scientist, vol. 247, issue 3299, p. 19</TD>
<TD>2020-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020NewSc.247...19C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020NewAR..8901538D</TD>
<TD>Jets from Tidal Disruption Events</TD>
<TD>De Colle, Fabio; Lu, Wenbin</TD>
<TD>New Astronomy Reviews, Volume 89, article id. 101538.</TD>
<TD>2020-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020NewAR..8901538D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.497.2974V</TD>
<TD>On the cosmological performance of photometrically classified supernovae with machine learning</TD>
<TD>Vargas dos Santos, Marcelo; Quartin, Miguel; Reis, Ribamar R. R.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 497, Issue 3, pp.2974-2991</TD>
<TD>2020-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.497.2974V</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.497.2641T</TD>
<TD>Vetting the optical transient candidates detected by the GWAC network using convolutional neural networks</TD>
<TD>Turpin, Damien; Ganet, M.; Antier, S.; Bertin, E.; Xin, L. P.; Leroy, N.; Wu, C.; Xu, Y.; Han, X. H.; Cai, H. B.; Li, H. L.; Lu, X. M.; Feng, Q. C.; Wei, J. Y.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 497, Issue 3, pp.2641-2650</TD>
<TD>2020-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.497.2641T</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.497.1320S</TD>
<TD>Using machine learning for transient classification in searches for gravitational-wave counterparts</TD>
<TD>Stachie, Cosmin; Coughlin, Michael W.; Christensen, Nelson; Muthukrishna, Daniel</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 497, Issue 2, pp.1320-1331</TD>
<TD>2020-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.497.1320S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.497.1181C</TD>
<TD>Implications of the search for optical counterparts during the second part of the Advanced LIGO's and Advanced Virgo's third observing run: lessons learned for future follow-up observations</TD>
<TD>Coughlin, Michael W.; Dietrich, Tim; Antier, Sarah; Almualla, Mouza; Anand, Shreya; Bulla, Mattia; Foucart, Francois; Guessoum, Nidhal; Hotokezaka, Kenta; Kumar, Vishwesh; Raaijmakers, Geert; Nissanke, Samaya</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 497, Issue 1, pp.1181-1196</TD>
<TD>2020-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.497.1181C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.497..726G</TD>
<TD>Searching for electromagnetic counterparts to gravitational-wave merger events with the prototype Gravitational-Wave Optical Transient Observer (GOTO-4)</TD>
<TD>Gompertz, B. P.; Cutter, R.; Steeghs, D.; Galloway, D. K.; Lyman, J.; Ulaczyk, K.; Dyer, M. J.; Ackley, K.; Dhillon, V. S.; O'Brien, P. T.; Ramsay, G.; Poshyachinda, S.; Kotak, R.; Nuttall, L.; Breton, R. P.; Pallé, E.; Pollacco, D.; Thrane, E.; Aukkaravittayapun, S.; Awiphan, S.; Brown, M. J. I.; Burhanudin, U.; Chote, P.; Chrimes, A. A.; Daw, E.; Duffy, C.; Eyles-Ferris, R. A. J.; Heikkilä, T.; Irawati, P.; Kennedy, M. R.; Killestein, T.; Levan, A. J.; Littlefair, S.; Makrygianni, L.; Marsh, T.; Mata Sánchez, D.; Mattila, S.; Maund, J.; McCormac, J.; Mkrtichian, D.; Mong, Y. -L.; Mullaney, J.; Müller, B.; Obradovic, A.; Rol, E.; Sawangwit, U.; Stanway, E. R.; Starling, R. L. C.; Strøm, P. A.; Tooke, S.; West, R.; Wiersema, K.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 497, Issue 1, pp.726-738</TD>
<TD>2020-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.497..726G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.497..318L</TD>
<TD>SN 2018hti: a nearby superluminous supernova discovered in a metal-poor galaxy</TD>
<TD>Lin, W. L.; Wang, X. F.; Li, W. X.; Zhang, J. J.; Mo, J.; Sai, H. N.; Zhang, X. H.; Filippenko, A. V.; Zheng, W. K.; Brink, T. G.; Baron, E.; DerKacy, J. M.; Ehgamberdiev, S. A.; Mirzaqulov, D.; Li, X.; Zhang, J. C.; Yan, S. Y.; Xi, G. B.; Hsiao, Y.; Zhang, T. M.; Wang, L. J.; Liu, L. D.; Xiang, D. F.; Wu, C. Y.; Rui, L. M.; Chen, Z. H.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 497, Issue 1, pp.318-335</TD>
<TD>2020-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.497..318L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.497..246G</TD>
<TD>AT2018kzr: the merger of an oxygen-neon white dwarf and a neutron star or black hole</TD>
<TD>Gillanders, J. H.; Sim, S. A.; Smartt, S. J.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 497, Issue 1, pp.246-262</TD>
<TD>2020-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.497..246G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJS..250....6W</TD>
<TD>Comprehensive Analysis of the Tidal Effect in Gravitational Waves and Implication for Cosmology</TD>
<TD>Wang, Bo; Zhu, Zhenyu; Li, Ang; Zhao, Wen</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 250, Issue 1, id.6, 22 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJS..250....6W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...901...61L</TD>
<TD>Four (Super)luminous Supernovae from the First Months of the ZTF Survey</TD>
<TD>Lunnan, R.; Yan, Lin; Perley, D. A.; Schulze, S.; Taggart, K.; Gal-Yam, A.; Fremling, C.; Soumagnac, M. T.; Ofek, E.; Adams, S. M.; Barbarino, C.; Bellm, E. C.; De, K.; Fransson, C.; Frederick, S.; Golkhou, V. Z.; Graham, M. J.; Hallakoun, N.; Ho, A. Y. Q.; Kasliwal, M. M.; Kaspi, S.; Kulkarni, S. R.; Laher, R. R.; Masci, F. J.; Nuñez, F. Pozo; Rusholme, B.; Quimby, R. M.; Shupe, D. L.; Sollerman, J.; Taddia, F.; Roestel, J. van; Yang, Y.; Yao, Yuhan</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 901, Issue 1, id.61, 19 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...901...61L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...900L..45B</TD>
<TD>Characterization of Temporarily Captured Minimoon 2020 CD&lt;SUB&gt;3&lt;/SUB&gt; by Keck Time-resolved Spectrophotometry</TD>
<TD>Bolin, Bryce T.; Fremling, Christoffer; Holt, Timothy R.; Hankins, Matthew J.; Ahumada, Tomás; Anand, Shreya; Bhalerao, Varun; Burdge, Kevin B.; Copperwheat, Chris M.; Coughlin, Michael; Deshmukh, Kunal P.; De, Kishalay; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Morbidelli, Alessandro; Purdum, Josiah N.; Quimby, Robert; Bodewits, Dennis; Chang, Chan-Kao; Ip, Wing-Huen; Hsu, Chen-Yen; Laher, Russ R.; Lin, Zhong-Yi; Lisse, Carey M.; Masci, Frank J.; Ngeow, Chow-Choong; Tan, Hanjie; Zhai, Chengxing; Burruss, Rick; Dekany, Richard; Delacroix, Alexandre; Duev, Dmitry A.; Graham, Matthew; Hale, David; Kulkarni, Shrinivas R.; Kupfer, Thomas; Mahabal, Ashish; Mróz, Przemyslaw J.; Neill, James D.; Riddle, Reed; Rodriguez, Hector; Smith, Roger M.; Soumagnac, Maayane T.; Walters, Richard; Yan, Lin; Zolkower, Jeffry</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 900, Issue 2, id.L45, 14 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...900L..45B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...900L..37R</TD>
<TD>A Year-long Superoutburst from an Ultracompact White Dwarf Binary Reveals the Importance of Donor Star Irradiation</TD>
<TD>Rivera Sandoval, L. E.; Maccarone, T. J.; Pichardo Marcano, M.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 900, Issue 2, id.L37, 6 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...900L..37R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...900L..27S</TD>
<TD>Strong Calcium Emission Indicates that the Ultraviolet-flashing SN Ia 2019yvq Was the Result of a Sub-Chandrasekar-mass Double-detonation Explosion</TD>
<TD>Siebert, Matthew R.; Dimitriadis, Georgios; Polin, Abigail; Foley, Ryan J.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 900, Issue 2, id.L27, 11 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...900L..27S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...900...73K</TD>
<TD>Comparative Spectral Analysis of the Superluminous Supernova 2019neq</TD>
<TD>Könyves-Tóth, Réka; Thomas, Benjamin P.; Vinkó, József; Wheeler, J. Craig</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 900, Issue 1, id.73, 13 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...900...73K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...900...58Y</TD>
<TD>Dust Reverberation Mapping in Distant Quasars from Optical and Mid-infrared Imaging Surveys</TD>
<TD>Yang, Qian; Shen, Yue; Liu, Xin; Aguena, Michel; Annis, James; Avila, Santiago; Banerji, Manda; Bertin, Emmanuel; Brooks, David; Burke, David; Carnero Rosell, Aurelio; Carrasco Kind, Matias; da Costa, Luiz; De Vicente, Juan; Desai, Shantanu; Diehl, H. Thomas; Doel, Peter; Flaugher, Brenna; Fosalba, Pablo; Frieman, Josh; Garcia-Bellido, Juan; Gerdes, David; Gruen, Daniel; Gruendl, Robert; Gschwend, Julia; Gutierrez, Gaston; Hinton, Samuel; Hollowood, Devon L.; Honscheid, Klaus; Kuropatkin, Nikolay; Maia, Marcio; March, Marisa; Marshall, Jennifer; Martini, Paul; Melchior, Peter; Menanteau, Felipe; Miquel, Ramon; Paz-Chinchon, Francisco; Malagón, Andrés Plazas; Romer, Kathy; Sanchez, Eusebio; Scarpine, Vic; Schubnell, Michael; Serrano, Santiago; Sevilla, Ignacio; Smith, Mathew; Suchyta, Eric; Tarle, Gregory; Varga, Tamas Norbert; Wilkinson, Reese</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 900, Issue 1, id.58, 17 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...900...58Y</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...900...46Y</TD>
<TD>SN2019dge: A Helium-rich Ultra-stripped Envelope Supernova</TD>
<TD>Yao, Yuhan; De, Kishalay; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Ho, Anna Y. Q.; Schulze, Steve; Li, Zhihui; Kulkarni, S. R.; Fruchter, Andrew; Rubin, David; Perley, Daniel A.; Fuller, Jim; Piro, Anthony L.; Fremling, C.; Bellm, Eric C.; Burruss, Rick; Duev, Dmitry A.; Feeney, Michael; Gal-Yam, Avishay; Golkhou, V. Zach; Graham, Matthew J.; Helou, George; Kupfer, Thomas; Laher, Russ R.; Masci, Frank J.; Miller, Adam A.; Rusholme, Ben; Shupe, David L.; Smith, Roger; Sollerman, Jesper; Soumagnac, Maayane T.; Zolkower, Jeffry</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 900, Issue 1, id.46, 24 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...900...46Y</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020AdSpR..66.1147D</TD>
<TD>On a century of extragalactic novae and the rise of the rapid recurrent novae</TD>
<TD>Darnley, Matthew J.; Henze, Martin</TD>
<TD>Advances in Space Research, Volume 66, Issue 5, p. 1147-1168.</TD>
<TD>2020-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020AdSpR..66.1147D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020AdSpR..66.1090S</TD>
<TD>Insights from multi-wavelength observations during high and low states of non-magnetic CVs</TD>
<TD>Szkody, Paula</TD>
<TD>Advances in Space Research, Volume 66, Issue 5, p. 1090-1096.</TD>
<TD>2020-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020AdSpR..66.1090S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020AcA....70..169M</TD>
<TD>Identifying Microlensing Events Using Neural Networks</TD>
<TD>Mróz, P.</TD>
<TD>Acta Astronomica, vol 70, no 3, p. 169-180</TD>
<TD>2020-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020AcA....70..169M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020AJ....160..147C</TD>
<TD>A Warm Jupiter Transiting an M Dwarf: A TESS Single-transit Event Confirmed with the Habitable-zone Planet Finder</TD>
<TD>Cañas, Caleb I.; Stefansson, Gudmundur; Kanodia, Shubham; Mahadevan, Suvrath; Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; Robertson, Paul; Bender, Chad F.; Ninan, Joe P.; Beard, Corey; Lubin, Jack; Gupta, Arvind F.; Everett, Mark E.; Monson, Andrew; Wilson, Robert F.; Lewis, Hannah M.; Brewer, Mary; Majewski, Steven R.; Hebb, Leslie; Dawson, Rebekah I.; Diddams, Scott A.; Ford, Eric B.; Fredrick, Connor; Halverson, Samuel; Hearty, Fred; Lin, Andrea S. J.; Metcalf, Andrew J.; Rajagopal, Jayadev; Ramsey, Lawrence W.; Roy, Arpita; Schwab, Christian; Terrien, Ryan C.; Wright, Jason T.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 160, Issue 3, id.147, 14 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-09-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020AJ....160..147C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020PASP..132h5002S</TD>
<TD>Design and Operation of the ATLAS Transient Science Server</TD>
<TD>Smith, K. W.; Smartt, S. J.; Young, D. R.; Tonry, J. L.; Denneau, L.; Flewelling, H.; Heinze, A. N.; Weiland, H. J.; Stalder, B.; Rest, A.; Stubbs, C. W.; Anderson, J. P.; Chen, T. -W.; Clark, P.; Do, A.; Förster, F.; Fulton, M.; Gillanders, J.; McBrien, O. R.; O'Neill, D.; Srivastav, S.; Wright, D. E.</TD>
<TD>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 132, Issue 1014, id.085002, 22 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020PASP..132h5002S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020PASJ...72...67T</TD>
<TD>A numerical light curve model for interaction-powered supernovae</TD>
<TD>Takei, Yuki; Shigeyama, Toshikazu</TD>
<TD>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Volume 72, Issue 4, id.67</TD>
<TD>2020-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020PASJ...72...67T</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020Natur.584..159C</TD>
<TD>Migrating big astronomy data to the cloud</TD>
<TD>Choi, Charles Q.</TD>
<TD>Nature, Volume 584, Issue 7819, p.159-160</TD>
<TD>2020-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020Natur.584..159C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020NatRP...2..452K</TD>
<TD>The future is now</TD>
<TD>Kasliwal, Mansi M.</TD>
<TD>Nature Reviews Physics, Volume 2, Issue 9, p.452-454</TD>
<TD>2020-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020NatRP...2..452K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.496.5503B</TD>
<TD>Progenitor, precursor, and evolution of the dusty remnant of the stellar merger M31-LRN-2015</TD>
<TD>Blagorodnova, N.; Karambelkar, V.; Adams, S. M.; Kasliwal, M. M.; Kochanek, C. S.; Dong, S.; Campbell, H.; Hodgkin, S.; Jencson, J. E.; Johansson, J.; Kozłowski, S.; Laher, R. R.; Masci, F.; Nugent, P.; Rebbapragada, U.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 496, Issue 4, pp.5503-5517</TD>
<TD>2020-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.496.5503B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.496.5482Y</TD>
<TD>Non-linear dynamical tides in white dwarf binaries</TD>
<TD>Yu, Hang; Weinberg, Nevin N.; Fuller, Jim</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 496, Issue 4, pp.5482-5502</TD>
<TD>2020-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.496.5482Y</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.496.5233S</TD>
<TD>The dust never settles: collisional production of gas and dust in evolved planetary systems</TD>
<TD>Swan, Andrew; Farihi, Jay; Wilson, Thomas G.; Parsons, Steven G.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 496, Issue 4, pp.5233-5242</TD>
<TD>2020-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.496.5233S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.496.3572P</TD>
<TD>Physical characterization of 2020 AV&lt;SUB&gt;2&lt;/SUB&gt;, the first known asteroid orbiting inside Venus orbit</TD>
<TD>Popescu, M.; de León, J.; de la Fuente Marcos, C.; Vaduvescu, O.; de la Fuente Marcos, R.; Licandro, J.; Pinter, V.; Tatsumi, E.; Zamora, O.; Fariña, C.; Curelaru, L.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 496, Issue 3, pp.3572-3581</TD>
<TD>2020-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.496.3572P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.496.2292V</TD>
<TD>The lifetimes of planetary debris discs around white dwarfs</TD>
<TD>Veras, Dimitri; Heng, Kevin</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 496, Issue 2, pp.2292-2308</TD>
<TD>2020-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.496.2292V</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.496.1902A</TD>
<TD>The possible disappearance of a massive star in the low-metallicity galaxy PHL 293B</TD>
<TD>Allan, Andrew P.; Groh, Jose H.; Mehner, Andrea; Smith, Nathan; Boian, Ioana; Farrell, Eoin J.; Andrews, Jennifer E.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 496, Issue 2, pp.1902-1908</TD>
<TD>2020-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.496.1902A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.496.1730F</TD>
<TD>The VISTA Variables in the Vía Láctea infrared variability catalogue (VIVA-I)</TD>
<TD>Ferreira Lopes, C. E.; Cross, N. J. G.; Catelan, M.; Minniti, D.; Hempel, M.; Lucas, P. W.; Angeloni, R.; Jablonsky, F.; Braga, V. F.; Leão, I. C.; Herpich, F. R.; Alonso-García, J.; Papageorgiou, A.; Pichara, K.; Saito, R. K.; Bradley, A. J.; Beamin, J. C.; Cortés, C.; De Medeiros, J. R.; Russell, Christopher M. P.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 496, Issue 2, pp.1730-1756</TD>
<TD>2020-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.496.1730F</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.496.1325B</TD>
<TD>Progenitors of early-time interacting supernovae</TD>
<TD>Boian, Ioana; Groh, Jose H.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 496, Issue 2, pp.1325-1342</TD>
<TD>2020-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.496.1325B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.496.1243G</TD>
<TD>Spectroscopic and photometric periods of six ultracompact accreting binaries</TD>
<TD>Green, Matthew J.; Marsh, Thomas R.; Carter, Philip J.; Steeghs, Danny; Breedt, Elmé; Dhillon, V. S.; Littlefair, S. P.; Parsons, Steven G.; Kerry, Paul; Gentile Fusillo, Nicola P.; Ashley, R. P.; Bours, Madelon C. P.; Cunningham, Tim; Dyer, Martin J.; Gänsicke, Boris T.; Izquierdo, Paula; Pala, Anna F.; Pattama, Chuangwit; Outmani, Sabrina; Sahman, David I.; Sukaum, Boonchoo; Wild, James</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 496, Issue 2, pp.1243-1261</TD>
<TD>2020-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.496.1243G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.496.1132T</TD>
<TD>Observations of the low-luminosity Type Iax supernova 2019gsc: a fainter clone of SN 2008ha?</TD>
<TD>Tomasella, Lina; Stritzinger, Maximilian; Benetti, Stefano; Elias-Rosa, Nancy; Cappellaro, Enrico; Kankare, Erkki; Lundqvist, Peter; Magee, Mark; Maguire, Kate; Pastorello, Andrea; Prentice, Simon; Reguitti, Andrea</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 496, Issue 2, pp.1132-1143</TD>
<TD>2020-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.496.1132T</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.496.1105M</TD>
<TD>Confirmation of monoperiodicity above 20 s for two blue large-amplitude pulsators</TD>
<TD>McWhirter, Paul Ross; Lam, Marco C.; Steele, Iain A.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 496, Issue 2, pp.1105-1114</TD>
<TD>2020-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.496.1105M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJS..249...34R</TD>
<TD>Classifying Single Stars and Spectroscopic Binaries Using Optical Stellar Templates</TD>
<TD>Roulston, Benjamin R.; Green, Paul J.; Kesseli, Aurora Y.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 249, Issue 2, id.34</TD>
<TD>2020-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJS..249...34R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...899..130S</TD>
<TD>Gaia 18dvy: A New FUor in the Cygnus OB3 Association</TD>
<TD>Szegedi-Elek, E.; Ábrahám, P.; Wyrzykowski, Ł.; Kun, M.; Kóspál, Á.; Chen, L.; Marton, G.; Moór, A.; Kiss, C.; Pál, A.; Szabados, L.; Varga, J.; Varga-Verebélyi, E.; Andreas, C.; Bachelet, E.; Bischoff, R.; Bódi, A.; Breedt, E.; Burgaz, U.; Butterley, T.; Carrasco, J. M.; Čepas, V.; Damljanovic, G.; Gezer, I.; Godunova, V.; Gromadzki, M.; Gurgul, A.; Hardy, L.; Hildebrandt, F.; Hoffmann, S.; Hundertmark, M.; Ihanec, N.; Janulis, R.; Kalup, Cs.; Kaczmarek, Z.; Könyves-Tóth, R.; Krezinger, M.; Kruszyńska, K.; Littlefair, S.; Maskoliūnas, M.; Mészáros, L.; Mikołajczyk, P.; Mugrauer, M.; Netzel, H.; Ordasi, A.; Pakštienė, E.; Rybicki, K. A.; Sárneczky, K.; Seli, B.; Simon, A.; Šiškauskaitė, K.; Sódor, Á.; Sokolovsky, K. V.; Stenglein, W.; Street, R.; Szakáts, R.; Tomasella, L.; Tsapras, Y.; Vida, K.; Zdanavičius, J.; Zieliński, M.; Zieliński, P.; Ziółkowska, O.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 899, Issue 2, id.130</TD>
<TD>2020-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...899..130S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...899..127S</TD>
<TD>X-Ray Properties of Young Radio Quasars at z &gt; 4.5</TD>
<TD>Snios, Bradford; Siemiginowska, Aneta; Sobolewska, Małgosia; Cheung, C. C.; Kashyap, Vinay; Migliori, Giulia; Schwartz, Daniel A.; Stawarz, Łukasz; Worrall, Diana M.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 899, Issue 2, id.127</TD>
<TD>2020-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...899..127S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...899..103M</TD>
<TD>Gigayear-timescale Destruction of High-eccentricity Asteroids by Spin and Why 2006 HY51 Has Been Spared</TD>
<TD>Makarov, Valeri V.; Goldin, Alexey; Veras, Dimitri</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 899, Issue 2, id.103</TD>
<TD>2020-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...899..103M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...899...56S</TD>
<TD>A Systematic Study on the Rise Time-Peak Luminosity Relation for Bright Optical Transients Powered by Wind Shock Breakout</TD>
<TD>Suzuki, Akihiro; Moriya, Takashi J.; Takiwaki, Tomoya</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 899, Issue 1, id.56</TD>
<TD>2020-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...899...56S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...899...51S</TD>
<TD>Early Ultraviolet Observations of Type IIn Supernovae Constrain the Asphericity of Their Circumstellar Material</TD>
<TD>Soumagnac, Maayane T.; Ofek, Eran O.; Liang, Jingyi; Gal-yam, Avishay; Nugent, Peter; Yang, Yi; Cenko, S. Bradley; Sollerman, Jesper; Perley, Daniel A.; Andreoni, Igor; Barbarino, Cristina; Burdge, Kevin B.; Bruch, Rachel J.; De, Kishalay; Dugas, Alison; Fremling, Christoffer; Graham, Melissa L.; Hankins, Matthew J.; Strotjohann, Nora Linn; Moran, Shane; Neill, James D.; Schulze, Steve; Shupe, David L.; Sipőcz, Brigitta M.; Taggart, Kirsty; Tartaglia, Leonardo; Walters, Richard; Yan, Lin; Yao, Yuhan; Yaron, Ofer; Bellm, Eric C.; Cannella, Chris; Dekany, Richard; Duev, Dmitry A.; Feeney, Michael; Frederick, Sara; Graham, Matthew J.; Laher, Russ R.; Masci, Frank J.; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Kowalski, Marek; Kupfer, Thomas; Miller, Adam A.; Rigault, Mickael; Rusholme, Ben</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 899, Issue 1, id.51</TD>
<TD>2020-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...899...51S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...899...29K</TD>
<TD>TOI-1728b: The Habitable-zone Planet Finder Confirms a Warm Super-Neptune Orbiting an M-dwarf Host</TD>
<TD>Kanodia, Shubham; Cañas, Caleb I.; Stefansson, Gudmundur; Ninan, Joe P.; Hebb, Leslie; Lin, Andrea S. J.; Baran, Helen; Maney, Marissa; Terrien, Ryan C.; Mahadevan, Suvrath; Cochran, William D.; Endl, Michael; Dong, Jiayin; Bender, Chad F.; Diddams, Scott A.; Ford, Eric B.; Fredrick, Connor; Halverson, Samuel; Hearty, Fred; Metcalf, Andrew J.; Monson, Andrew; Ramsey, Lawrence W.; Robertson, Paul; Roy, Arpita; Schwab, Christian; Wright, Jason T.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 899, Issue 1, id.29</TD>
<TD>2020-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...899...29K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...898L..56L</TD>
<TD>Detections of Simultaneous Brightening of γ-Ray and Optical Emissions of a Distant Blazar GB 1508+5714 at Redshift 4.3</TD>
<TD>Liao, Neng-Hui; Li, Shang; Sheng, Zhen-Feng; Fan, Yi-Zhong</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 898, Issue 2, id.L56</TD>
<TD>2020-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...898L..56L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...898L..39K</TD>
<TD>Of Harbingers and Higher Modes: Improved Gravitational-wave Early Warning of Compact Binary Mergers</TD>
<TD>Kapadia, Shasvath J.; Singh, Mukesh Kumar; Shaikh, Md Arif; Chatterjee, Deep; Ajith, Parameswaran</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 898, Issue 2, id.L39</TD>
<TD>2020-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...898L..39K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...898..166J</TD>
<TD>SN 2019ehk: A Double-peaked Ca-rich Transient with Luminous X-Ray Emission and Shock-ionized Spectral Features</TD>
<TD>Jacobson-Galán, Wynn V.; Margutti, Raffaella; Kilpatrick, Charles D.; Hiramatsu, Daichi; Perets, Hagai; Khatami, David; Foley, Ryan J.; Raymond, John; Yoon, Sung-Chul; Bobrick, Alexey; Zenati, Yossef; Galbany, Lluís; Andrews, Jennifer; Brown, Peter J.; Cartier, Régis; Coppejans, Deanne L.; Dimitriadis, Georgios; Dobson, Matthew; Hajela, Aprajita; Howell, D. Andrew; Kuncarayakti, Hanindyo; Milisavljevic, Danny; Rahman, Mohammed; Rojas-Bravo, César; Sand, David J.; Shepherd, Joel; Smartt, Stephen J.; Stacey, Holland; Stroh, Michael; Swift, Jonathan J.; Terreran, Giacomo; Vinko, Jozsef; Wang, Xiaofeng; Anderson, Joseph P.; Baron, Edward A.; Berger, Edo; Blanchard, Peter K.; Burke, Jamison; Coulter, David A.; DeMarchi, Lindsay; DerKacy, James M.; Fremling, Christoffer; Gomez, Sebastian; Gromadzki, Mariusz; Hosseinzadeh, Griffin; Kasen, Daniel; Kriskovics, Levente; McCully, Curtis; Müller-Bravo, Tomás E.; Nicholl, Matt; Ordasi, András; Pellegrino, Craig; Piro, Anthony L.; Pál, András; Ren, Juanjuan; Rest, Armin; Rich, R. Michael; Sai, Hanna; Sárneczky, Krisztián; Shen, Ken J.; Short, Philip; Siebert, Matthew R.; Stauffer, Candice; Szakáts, Róbert; Zhang, Xinhan; Zhang, Jujia; Zhang, Kaicheng</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 898, Issue 2, id.166</TD>
<TD>2020-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...898..166J</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020AdSpR..66..490Y</TD>
<TD>Ground deformation and fissure activity of the Yuncheng Basin (China) revealed by multiband time series InSAR</TD>
<TD>Yang, Chengsheng; Zhang, Fan; Liu, Ruichun; Hou, Jianguo; Zhang, Qin; Zhao, Chaoying</TD>
<TD>Advances in Space Research, Volume 66, Issue 3, p. 490-504.</TD>
<TD>2020-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020AdSpR..66..490Y</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020AJ....160...92H</TD>
<TD>Physical Characterization of Interstellar Comet 2I/2019 Q4 (Borisov)</TD>
<TD>Hui, Man-To; Ye, Quan-Zhi; Föhring, Dora; Hung, Denise; Tholen, David J.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 160, Issue 2, id.92</TD>
<TD>2020-08-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020AJ....160...92H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.496L..59Y</TD>
<TD>Galaxy optical variability of Virgo cluster: new tracer for environmental influences on galaxies</TD>
<TD>Yang, Fan; Long, Richard J.; Shan, Su-Su; Ge, Jun-Qiang; Guo, Rui; Zhang, Bo; Gao, Jing-Hua; Ji, Xiang; Liu, Ji-Feng</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 496, Issue 1, pp.L59-L63</TD>
<TD>2020-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.496L..59Y</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.495.4622F</TD>
<TD>Observing the earliest moments of supernovae using strong gravitational lenses</TD>
<TD>Foxley-Marrable, Max; Collett, Thomas E.; Frohmaier, Chris; Goldstein, Daniel A.; Kasen, Daniel; Swann, Elizabeth; Bacon, David</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 495, Issue 4, pp.4622-4637</TD>
<TD>2020-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.495.4622F</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.495.4419V</TD>
<TD>Examining supernova events in Type 1 active galactic nuclei</TD>
<TD>Villarroel, Beatriz; Imaz, Iñigo; Lusso, Elisabeta; Comerón, Sébastien; Prieto, M. Almudena; Marziani, Paola; Mattsson, Lars</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 495, Issue 4, pp.4419-4429</TD>
<TD>2020-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.495.4419V</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.495.4366A</TD>
<TD>Dynamic scheduling: target of opportunity observations of gravitational wave events</TD>
<TD>Almualla, Mouza; Coughlin, Michael W.; Anand, Shreya; Alqassimi, Khalid; Guessoum, Nidhal; Singer, Leo P.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 495, Issue 4, pp.4366-4371</TD>
<TD>2020-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.495.4366A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.495.4061H</TD>
<TD>Spikey: self-lensing flares from eccentric SMBH binaries</TD>
<TD>Hu, Betty X.; D'Orazio, Daniel J.; Haiman, Zoltán; Smith, Krista Lynne; Snios, Bradford; Charisi, Maria; Di Stefano, Rosanne</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 495, Issue 4, pp.4061-4070</TD>
<TD>2020-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.495.4061H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.495.4040W</TD>
<TD>Supernova host galaxies in the dark energy survey: I. Deep coadds, photometry, and stellar masses</TD>
<TD>Wiseman, P.; Smith, M.; Childress, M.; Kelsey, L.; Möller, A.; Gupta, R. R.; Swann, E.; Angus, C. R.; Brout, D.; Davis, T. M.; Foley, R. J.; Frohmaier, C.; Galbany, L.; Gutiérrez, C. P.; Inserra, C.; Kessler, R.; Lewis, G. F.; Lidman, C.; Macaulay, E.; Nichol, R. C.; Pursiainen, M.; Sako, M.; Scolnic, D.; Sommer, N. E.; Sullivan, M.; Tucker, B. E.; Abbott, T. M. C.; Aguena, M.; Allam, S.; Avila, S.; Bertin, E.; Brooks, D.; Buckley-Geer, E.; Burke, D. L.; Carnero Rosell, A.; Carollo, D.; Carrasco Kind, M.; da Costa, L. N.; De Vicente, J.; Desai, S.; Diehl, H. T.; Doel, P.; Eifler, T. F.; Everett, S.; Fosalba, P.; Frieman, J.; García-Bellido, J.; Gaztanaga, E.; Gerdes, D. W.; Gill, M. S. S.; Glazebrook, K.; Gruendl, R. A.; Gschwend, J.; Hartley, W. G.; Hinton, S. R.; Hollowood, D. L.; Honscheid, K.; James, D. J.; Kuehn, K.; Kuropatkin, N.; Lima, M.; Maia, M. A. G.; March, M.; Martini, P.; Melchior, P.; Menanteau, F.; Miquel, R.; Ogando, R. L. C.; Paz-Chinchón, F.; Plazas, A. A.; Romer, A. K.; Roodman, A.; Sanchez, E.; Scarpine, V.; Serrano, S.; Suchyta, E.; Swanson, M. E. C.; Tarle, G.; Thomas, D.; Tucker, D. L.; Varga, T. N.; Walker, A. R.; Wilkinson, R. D.; (DES Collaboration)</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 495, Issue 4, pp.4040-4060</TD>
<TD>2020-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.495.4040W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020CoSka..50..672A</TD>
<TD>LAMOST J202629.80+423652.0 is not a symbiotic star</TD>
<TD>Andreoli, V.; Munari, U.</TD>
<TD>Contributions of the Astronomical Observatory Skalnaté Pleso, vol. 50, no. 3, p. 672-680.</TD>
<TD>2020-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020CoSka..50..672A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJS..249...18C</TD>
<TD>The Zwicky Transient Facility Catalog of Periodic Variable Stars</TD>
<TD>Chen, Xiaodian; Wang, Shu; Deng, Licai; de Grijs, Richard; Yang, Ming; Tian, Hao</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 249, Issue 1, id.18</TD>
<TD>2020-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJS..249...18C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJS..249...16M</TD>
<TD>Microlensing Optical Depth and Event Rate in the OGLE-IV Galactic Plane Fields</TD>
<TD>Mróz, Przemek; Udalski, Andrzej; Szymański, Michał K.; Soszyński, Igor; Pietrukowicz, Paweł; Kozłowski, Szymon; Skowron, Jan; Poleski, Radosław; Ulaczyk, Krzysztof; Gromadzki, Mariusz; Rybicki, Krzysztof; Iwanek, Patryk; Wrona, Marcin</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 249, Issue 1, id.16</TD>
<TD>2020-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJS..249...16M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...898L..25K</TD>
<TD>A New Class of Roche Lobe-filling Hot Subdwarf Binaries</TD>
<TD>Kupfer, Thomas; Bauer, Evan B.; Burdge, Kevin B.; Roestel, Jan van; Bellm, Eric C.; Fuller, Jim; Hermes, JJ; Marsh, Thomas R.; Bildsten, Lars; Kulkarni, Shrinivas R.; Phinney, E. S.; Prince, Thomas A.; Szkody, Paula; Yao, Yuhan; Irrgang, Andreas; Heber, Ulrich; Schneider, David; Dhillon, Vik S.; Murawski, Gabriel; Drake, Andrew J.; Duev, Dmitry A.; Feeney, Michael; Graham, Matthew J.; Laher, Russ R.; Littlefair, S. P.; Mahabal, A. A.; Masci, Frank J.; Porter, Michael; Reiley, Dan; Rodriguez, Hector; Rusholme, Ben; Shupe, David L.; Soumagnac, Maayane T.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 898, Issue 1, id.L25</TD>
<TD>2020-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...898L..25K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...898...56M</TD>
<TD>The Spectacular Ultraviolet Flash from the Peculiar Type Ia Supernova 2019yvq</TD>
<TD>Miller, A. A.; Magee, M. R.; Polin, A.; Maguire, K.; Zimmerman, E.; Yao, Y.; Sollerman, J.; Schulze, S.; Perley, D. A.; Kromer, M.; Dhawan, S.; Bulla, M.; Andreoni, I.; Bellm, E. C.; De, K.; Dekany, R.; Delacroix, A.; Fremling, C.; Gal-Yam, A.; Goldstein, D. A.; Golkhou, V. Z.; Goobar, A.; Graham, M. J.; Irani, I.; Kasliwal, M. M.; Kaye, S.; Kim, Y. -L.; Laher, R. R.; Mahabal, A. A.; Masci, F. J.; Nugent, P. E.; Ofek, E.; Phinney, E. S.; Prentice, S. J.; Riddle, R.; Rigault, M.; Rusholme, B.; Schweyer, T.; Shupe, D. L.; Soumagnac, M. T.; Terreran, G.; Walters, R.; Yan, L.; Zolkower, J.; Kulkarni, S. R.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 898, Issue 1, id.56</TD>
<TD>2020-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...898...56M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...898...29T</TD>
<TD>Comparing Moment-based and Monte Carlo Methods of Radiation Transport Modeling for Type II-Plateau Supernova Light Curves</TD>
<TD>Tsang, Benny T. -H.; Goldberg, Jared A.; Bildsten, Lars; Kasen, Daniel</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 898, Issue 1, id.29</TD>
<TD>2020-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...898...29T</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...897L..44T</TD>
<TD>Intermediate Luminosity Red Transients by Black Holes Born from Erupting Massive Stars</TD>
<TD>Tsuna, Daichi; Ishii, Ayako; Kuriyama, Naoto; Kashiyama, Kazumi; Shigeyama, Toshikazu</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 897, Issue 2, id.L44</TD>
<TD>2020-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...897L..44T</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...897L..12S</TD>
<TD>Image-based Classification of Variable Stars: First Results from Optical Gravitational Lensing Experiment Data</TD>
<TD>Szklenár, T.; Bódi, A.; Tarczay-Nehéz, D.; Vida, K.; Marton, G.; Mező, Gy.; Forró, A.; Szabó, R.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 897, Issue 1, id.L12, 8 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...897L..12S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...897..171V</TD>
<TD>A White Dwarf with Transiting Circumstellar Material Far outside the Roche Limit</TD>
<TD>Vanderbosch, Z.; Hermes, J. J.; Dennihy, E.; Dunlap, B. H.; Izquierdo, P.; Tremblay, P. -E.; Cho, P. B.; Gänsicke, B. T.; Toloza, O.; Bell, K. J.; Montgomery, M. H.; Winget, D. E.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 897, Issue 2, id.171</TD>
<TD>2020-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...897..171V</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...897..159P</TD>
<TD>Constraining the Source of the High-velocity Ejecta in Type Ia SN 2019ein</TD>
<TD>Pellegrino, C.; Howell, D. A.; Sarbadhicary, S. K.; Burke, J.; Hiramatsu, D.; McCully, C.; Milne, P. A.; Andrews, J. E.; Brown, P.; Chomiuk, L.; Hsiao, E. Y.; Sand, D. J.; Shahbandeh, M.; Smith, N.; Valenti, S.; Vinkó, J.; Wheeler, J. C.; Wyatt, S.; Yang, Y.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 897, Issue 2, id.159</TD>
<TD>2020-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...897..159P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...897..156U</TD>
<TD>A Wind-driven Model: Application to Peculiar Transients AT2018cow and iPTF14hls</TD>
<TD>Uno, Kohki; Maeda, Keiichi</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 897, Issue 2, id.156</TD>
<TD>2020-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...897..156U</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...897..144M</TD>
<TD>Gravitational Microlensing Event Statistics for the Zwicky Transient Facility</TD>
<TD>Medford, Michael S.; Lu, Jessica R.; Dawson, William A.; Lam, Casey Y.; Golovich, Nathan R.; Schlafly, Edward F.; Nugent, Peter</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 897, Issue 2, id.144</TD>
<TD>2020-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...897..144M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...897..114B</TD>
<TD>The Pre-explosion Mass Distribution of Hydrogen-poor Superluminous Supernova Progenitors and New Evidence for a Mass-Spin Correlation</TD>
<TD>Blanchard, Peter K.; Berger, Edo; Nicholl, Matt; Villar, V. Ashley</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 897, Issue 2, id.114</TD>
<TD>2020-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...897..114B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...897...80W</TD>
<TD>Continuum-fitting the X-Ray Spectra of Tidal Disruption Events</TD>
<TD>Wen, Sixiang; Jonker, Peter G.; Stone, Nicholas C.; Zabludoff, Ann I.; Psaltis, Dimitrios</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 897, Issue 1, id.80</TD>
<TD>2020-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...897...80W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020Ap&amp;SS.365..118K</TD>
<TD>WALLABY - an SKA Pathfinder HI survey</TD>
<TD>Koribalski, Bärbel S.; Staveley-Smith, L.; Westmeier, T.; Serra, P.; Spekkens, K.; Wong, O. I.; Lee-Waddell, K.; Lagos, C. D. P.; Obreschkow, D.; Ryan-Weber, E. V.; Zwaan, M.; Kilborn, V.; Bekiaris, G.; Bekki, K.; Bigiel, F.; Boselli, A.; Bosma, A.; Catinella, B.; Chauhan, G.; Cluver, M. E.; Colless, M.; Courtois, H. M.; Crain, R. A.; de Blok, W. J. G.; Dénes, H.; Duffy, A. R.; Elagali, A.; Fluke, C. J.; For, B. -Q.; Heald, G.; Henning, P. A.; Hess, K. M.; Holwerda, B. W.; Howlett, C.; Jarrett, T.; Jones, D. H.; Jones, M. G.; Józsa, G. I. G.; Jurek, R.; Jütte, E.; Kamphuis, P.; Karachentsev, I.; Kerp, J.; Kleiner, D.; Kraan-Korteweg, R. C.; López-Sánchez, Á. R.; Madrid, J.; Meyer, M.; Mould, J.; Murugeshan, C.; Norris, R. P.; Oh, S. -H.; Oosterloo, T. A.; Popping, A.; Putman, M.; Reynolds, T. N.; Rhee, J.; Robotham, A. S. G.; Ryder, S.; Schröder, A. C.; Shao, Li; Stevens, A. R. H.; Taylor, E. N.; vanÂ der Hulst, J. M.; Verdes-Montenegro, L.; Wakker, B. P.; Wang, J.; Whiting, M.; Winkel, B.; Wolf, C.</TD>
<TD>Astrophysics and Space Science, Volume 365, Issue 7, article id.118</TD>
<TD>2020-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020Ap&amp;SS.365..118K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020AJ....160...31N</TD>
<TD>A Search for Extra-tidal RR Lyrae in Globular Clusters NGC 5024 and NGC 5053</TD>
<TD>Ngeow, Chow-Choong; Belecki, Justin; Burruss, Rick; Drake, Andrew J.; Graham, Matthew J.; Kaplan, David L.; Kupfer, Thomas; Mahabal, Ashish; Masci, Frank J.; Riddle, Reed; Rodriguez, Hector; Rusholme, Ben</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 160, Issue 1, id.31, 15 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020AJ....160...31N</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020AJ....160...26B</TD>
<TD>Characterization of the Nucleus, Morphology, and Activity of Interstellar Comet 2I/Borisov by Optical and Near-infrared GROWTH, Apache Point, IRTF, ZTF, and Keck Observations</TD>
<TD>Bolin, Bryce T.; Lisse, Carey M.; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Quimby, Robert; Tan, Hanjie; Copperwheat, Chris M.; Lin, Zhong-Yi; Morbidelli, Alessandro; Abe, Lyu; Bendjoya, Philippe; Burdge, Kevin B.; Coughlin, Michael; Fremling, Christoffer; Itoh, Ryosuke; Koss, Michael; Masci, Frank J.; Maeno, Syota; Mamajek, Eric E.; Marocco, Federico; Murata, Katsuhiro; Rivet, Jean-Pierre; Sitko, Michael L.; Stern, Daniel; Vernet, David; Walters, Richard; Yan, Lin; Andreoni, Igor; Bhalerao, Varun; Bodewits, Dennis; De, Kishalay; Deshmukh, Kunal P.; Bellm, Eric C.; Blagorodnova, Nadejda; Buzasi, Derek; Cenko, S. Bradley; Chang, Chan-Kao; Chojnowski, Drew; Dekany, Richard; Duev, Dmitry A.; Graham, Matthew; Jurić, Mario; Kulkarni, Shrinivas R.; Kupfer, Thomas; Mahabal, Ashish; Neill, James D.; Ngeow, Chow-Choong; Penprase, Bryan; Riddle, Reed; Rodriguez, Hector; Smith, Roger M.; Rosnet, Philippe; Sollerman, Jesper; Soumagnac, Maayane T.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 160, Issue 1, id.26, 16 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020AJ....160...26B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020AJ....160...18A</TD>
<TD>Beyond Gaia: Asteroseismic Distances of M Giants Using Ground-based Transient Surveys</TD>
<TD>Auge, Connor; Huber, Daniel; Heinze, Aren; Shappee, B. J.; Tonry, John; Chakrabarti, Sukanya; Sanderson, Robyn E.; Denneau, Larry; Flewelling, Heather; Holoien, Thomas W. -S.; Kochanek, C. S.; Pignata, Giuliano; Sickafoose, Amanda; Stalder, Brian; Stanek, K. Z.; Stello, Dennis; Thompson, Todd A.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 160, Issue 1, id.18, 11 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020AJ....160...18A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020A&amp;A...639L..11I</TD>
<TD>Broad-line type Ic SN 2020bvc. Signatures of an off-axis gamma-ray burst afterglow</TD>
<TD>Izzo, L.; Auchettl, K.; Hjorth, J.; De Colle, F.; Gall, C.; Angus, C. R.; Raimundo, S. I.; Ramirez-Ruiz, E.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 639, id.L11, 8 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020A&amp;A...639L..11I</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020A&amp;A...639L..10M</TD>
<TD>The sustained post-outburst brightness of Nova Per 2018, the evolved companion, and the long orbital period</TD>
<TD>Munari, U.; Moretti, S.; Maitan, A.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 639, id.L10, 6 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020A&amp;A...639L..10M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020A&amp;A...639A..15D</TD>
<TD>Probing binary neutron star mergers in dense environments using afterglow counterparts</TD>
<TD>Duque, Raphaël; Beniamini, Paz; Daigne, Frédéric; Mochkovitch, Robert</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 639, id.A15, 8 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-07-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020A&amp;A...639A..15D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020rfma.book...45B</TD>
<TD>Extrasolar Enigmas: From Disintegrating Exoplanets to Exoasteroids</TD>
<TD>Budaj, Jan; Kabáth, Petr; Palle, Enric</TD>
<TD>Reviews in Frontiers of Modern Astrophysics; From Space Debris to Cosmology, edited by Kabáth, Petr; Jones, David; Skarka, Marek. ISBN: 978-3-030-38509-5. Cham: Springer International Publishing, 2020, pp. 45-88</TD>
<TD>2020-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020rfma.book...45B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020SSRv..216...81A</TD>
<TD>Radio Properties of Tidal Disruption Events</TD>
<TD>Alexander, Kate D.; van Velzen, Sjoert; Horesh, Assaf; Zauderer, B. Ashley</TD>
<TD>Space Science Reviews, Volume 216, Issue 5, article id.81</TD>
<TD>2020-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020SSRv..216...81A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020PhyOJ..13..101S</TD>
<TD>Possible Flare from Black Hole Merger</TD>
<TD>Schirber, Michael</TD>
<TD>Physics, Volume 13, article id. 101</TD>
<TD>2020-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020PhyOJ..13..101S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020PhRvL.124y1102G</TD>
<TD>Candidate Electromagnetic Counterpart to the Binary Black Hole Merger Gravitational-Wave Event S190521g&lt;SUP&gt;*&lt;/SUP&gt;</TD>
<TD>Graham, M. J.; Ford, K. E. S.; McKernan, B.; Ross, N. P.; Stern, D.; Burdge, K.; Coughlin, M.; Djorgovski, S. G.; Drake, A. J.; Duev, D.; Kasliwal, M.; Mahabal, A. A.; van Velzen, S.; Belecki, J.; Bellm, E. C.; Burruss, R.; Cenko, S. B.; Cunningham, V.; Helou, G.; Kulkarni, S. R.; Masci, F. J.; Prince, T.; Reiley, D.; Rodriguez, H.; Rusholme, B.; Smith, R. M.; Soumagnac, M. T.</TD>
<TD>Physical Review Letters, Volume 124, Issue 25, article id.251102</TD>
<TD>2020-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020PhRvL.124y1102G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020PhRvL.124w1101M</TD>
<TD>Search for Axionlike-Particle-Induced Prompt γ -Ray Emission from Extragalactic Core-Collapse Supernovae with the Fermi Large Area Telescope</TD>
<TD>Meyer, Manuel; Petrushevska, Tanja; Fermi-LAT Collaboration</TD>
<TD>Physical Review Letters, Volume 124, Issue 23, article id.231101</TD>
<TD>2020-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020PhRvL.124w1101M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020PhR...866....1L</TD>
<TD>Physics of radiation mediated shocks and its applications to GRBs, supernovae, and neutron star mergers</TD>
<TD>Levinson, Amir; Nakar, Ehud</TD>
<TD>Physics Reports, Volume 866, p. 1-46.</TD>
<TD>2020-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020PhR...866....1L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020PASP..132f4502Z</TD>
<TD>Synthetic Tracking Using ZTF Deep Drilling Data Sets</TD>
<TD>Zhai, Chengxing; Ye, Quanzhi; Shao, Michael; Trahan, Russell; Saini, Navtej S.; Shen, Janice; Prince, Thomas A.; Bellm, Eric C.; Graham, Matthew J.; Helou, George; Kulkarni, Shrinivas R.; Kupfer, Thomas; Laher, Russ R.; Mahabal, Ashish; Masci, Frank J.; Rusholme, Ben; Rosnet, Philippe; Shupe, David L.</TD>
<TD>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 132, Issue 1012, id.064502, 8 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020PASP..132f4502Z</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020PASJ...72...49T</TD>
<TD>First detection of two superoutbursts during the rebrightening phase of a WZ Sge-type dwarf nova: TCP J21040470+4631129</TD>
<TD>Tampo, Yusuke; Naoto, Kojiguchi; Isogai, Keisuke; Kato, Taichi; Kimura, Mariko; Wakamatsu, Yasuyuki; Nogami, Daisaku; Vanmunster, Tonny; Tordai, Tamás; Akazawa, Hidehiko; Mugas, Felipe; Nishiumi, Taku; Béjar, Víctor J. S.; Kawauchi, Kiyoe; Crouzet, Nicolas; Watanabe, Noriharu; Casasayas-Barris, Núria; Terada, Yuka; Fukui, Akihiko; Narita, Norio; Palle, Enric; Tamura, Motohide; Kusakabe, Nobuhiko; Alonso, Roi; Itoh, Hiroshi; Sokolovsky, Kirill; McIntyre, Brandon; Leahy-McGregor, Jesse; Brincat, Stephen M.; Dubovsky, Pavol A.; Medulka, Tomáš; Kudzej, Igor; Pavlenko, Elena P.; Antonyuk, Kirill A.; Pit, Nikolaj V.; Antonyuk, Oksana I.; Babina, Julia V.; Baklanov, Aleksei V.; Sklyanov, Aleksander S.; Zubareva, Alexandra M.; Belinski, Aleksandr A.; Dodin, Alexandr V.; Burlak, Marina A.; Ikonnikova, Natalia P.; Mishin, Egor O.; Potanin, Sergey A.; Miller, Ian; Richmond, Michael; Pickard, Roger D.; Galdies, Charles; Mizutani, Masanori; Menzies, Kenneth; Stone, Geoffrey; Ruiz, Javier</TD>
<TD>Publications of the Astronomical Society of Japan, Volume 72, Issue 3, id.49</TD>
<TD>2020-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020PASJ...72...49T</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020NatSR..10.8895C</TD>
<TD>Fabrication and Piezoresistive/Piezoelectric Sensing Characteristics of Carbon Nanotube/PVA/Nano-ZnO Flexible Composite</TD>
<TD>Chen, Shuaichao; Luo, Jianlin; Wang, Xiaoli; Li, Qiuyi; Zhou, Liucong; Liu, Chao; Feng, Chao</TD>
<TD>Scientific Reports, Volume 10, article id. 8895</TD>
<TD>2020-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020NatSR..10.8895C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.495.1666R</TD>
<TD>On building a cluster watchlist for identifying strongly lensed supernovae, gravitational waves and kilonovae</TD>
<TD>Ryczanowski, Dan; Smith, Graham P.; Bianconi, Matteo; Massey, Richard; Robertson, Andrew; Jauzac, Mathilde</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 495, Issue 2, pp.1666-1671</TD>
<TD>2020-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.495.1666R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.495.1403X</TD>
<TD>Correlation between optical and UV variability of a large sample of quasars</TD>
<TD>Xin, Chengcheng; Charisi, Maria; Haiman, Zoltán; Schiminovich, David</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 495, Issue 1, pp.1403-1413</TD>
<TD>2020-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.495.1403X</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.495.1073D</TD>
<TD>AT 2016dah and AT 2017fyp: the first classical novae discovered within a tidal stream</TD>
<TD>Darnley, M. J.; Newsam, A. M.; Chinetti, K.; Hawkins, I. D. W.; Jannetta, A. L.; Kasliwal, M. M.; McGarry, J. C.; Shara, M. M.; Sitaram, M.; Williams, S. C.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 495, Issue 1, pp.1073-1092</TD>
<TD>2020-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.495.1073D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020EPJC...80..582F</TD>
<TD>The scattering of Dirac spinors in rotating spheroids</TD>
<TD>Fu, Gao Zhi; Xing, Chen Ci; Na, Wang</TD>
<TD>The European Physical Journal C, Volume 80, Issue 6, article id.582</TD>
<TD>2020-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020EPJC...80..582F</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020AstL...46..388B</TD>
<TD>Search for Evolutionary Changes in the Period of the Classical Cepheid EV Aql</TD>
<TD>Berdnikov, L. N.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy Letters, Volume 46, Issue 6, p.388-399</TD>
<TD>2020-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020AstL...46..388B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...896L...2A</TD>
<TD>Zwicky Transient Facility Constraints on the Optical Emission from the Nearby Repeating FRB 180916.J0158+65</TD>
<TD>Andreoni, Igor; Lu, Wenbin; Smith, Roger M.; Masci, Frank J.; Bellm, Eric C.; Graham, Matthew J.; Kaplan, David L.; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Kaye, Stephen; Kupfer, Thomas; Laher, Russ R.; Mahabal, Ashish A.; Nordin, Jakob; Porter, Michael; Prince, Thomas A.; Reiley, Dan; Riddle, Reed; Van Roestel, Joannes; Yao, Yuhan</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 896, Issue 1, id.L2, 6 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...896L...2A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...896...54C</TD>
<TD>A Machine Learning-based Source Property Inference for Compact Binary Mergers</TD>
<TD>Chatterjee, Deep; Ghosh, Shaon; Brady, Patrick R.; Kapadia, Shasvath J.; Miller, Andrew L.; Nissanke, Samaya; Pannarale, Francesco</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 896, Issue 1, id.54, 10 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...896...54C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...896...10B</TD>
<TD>A Search for Optical AGN Variability in 35,000 Low-mass Galaxies with the Palomar Transient Factory</TD>
<TD>Baldassare, Vivienne F.; Geha, Marla; Greene, Jenny</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 896, Issue 1, id.10, 13 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...896...10B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...895L..29L</TD>
<TD>Determining Model-independent H&lt;SUB&gt;0&lt;/SUB&gt; and Consistency Tests</TD>
<TD>Liao, Kai; Shafieloo, Arman; Keeley, Ryan E.; Linder, Eric V.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 895, Issue 2, id.L29, 8 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...895L..29L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...895..127B</TD>
<TD>Swift Monitoring of M51: A 38 day Superorbital Period for the Pulsar ULX7 and a New Transient Ultraluminous X-Ray Source</TD>
<TD>Brightman, Murray; Earnshaw, Hannah; Fürst, Felix; Harrison, Fiona A.; Heida, Marianne; Israel, Gianluca; Pike, Sean; Stern, Daniel; Walton, Dominic J.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 895, Issue 2, id.127, 10 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...895..127B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...895...96V</TD>
<TD>A Deep CFHT Optical Search for a Counterpart to the Possible Neutron Star-Black Hole Merger GW190814</TD>
<TD>Vieira, Nicholas; Ruan, John J.; Haggard, Daryl; Drout, Maria R.; Nynka, Melania C.; Boyce, Hope; Spekkens, Kristine; Safi-Harb, Samar; Carlberg, Raymond G.; Fernández, Rodrigo; Piro, Anthony L.; Afsariardchi, Niloufar; Moon, Dae-Sik</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 895, Issue 2, id.96, 18 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...895...96V</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020A&amp;A...638A..21V</TD>
<TD>Catalogue of new Herbig Ae/Be and classical Be stars. A machine learning approach to Gaia DR2</TD>
<TD>Vioque, M.; Oudmaijer, R. D.; Schreiner, M.; Mendigutía, I.; Baines, D.; Mowlavi, N.; Pérez-Martínez, R.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 638, id.A21, 24 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-06-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020A&amp;A...638A..21V</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020PhyOJ..13...74.</TD>
<TD>"Revolution" for Alternative Black Hole Probe</TD>
<TD />
<TD>Physics, Volume 13, article id. 74</TD>
<TD>2020-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020PhyOJ..13...74.</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020PASP..132e4502X</TD>
<TD>A Real-time Automatic Validation System for Optical Transients Detected by GWAC</TD>
<TD>Xu, Y.; Xin, L. P.; Wang, J.; Han, X. H.; Qiu, Y. L.; Huang, M. H.; Wei, J. Y.</TD>
<TD>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 132, Issue 1011, id.054502, 9 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020PASP..132e4502X</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.494L..91C</TD>
<TD>ZTF J1901+5309: a 40.6-min orbital period eclipsing double white dwarf system</TD>
<TD>Coughlin, Michael W.; Burdge, Kevin; Phinney, E. Sterl; van Roestel, Jan; Bellm, Eric C.; Dekany, Richard G.; Delacroix, Alexandre; Duev, Dmitry A.; Feeney, Michael; Graham, Matthew J.; Kulkarni, S. R.; Kupfer, Thomas; Laher, Russ R.; Masci, Frank J.; Prince, Thomas A.; Riddle, Reed; Rosnet, Philippe; Smith, Roger; Serabyn, Eugene; Walters, Richard</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 494, Issue 1, pp.L91-L96</TD>
<TD>2020-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.494L..91C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.494L..75S</TD>
<TD>Finding binary black holes in the Milky Way with LISA</TD>
<TD>Sesana, Alberto; Lamberts, Astrid; Petiteau, Antoine</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 494, Issue 1, pp.L75-L80</TD>
<TD>2020-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.494L..75S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.494L..17M</TD>
<TD>Asteroid belt survival through stellar evolution: dependence on the stellar mass</TD>
<TD>Martin, Rebecca G.; Livio, Mario; Smallwood, Jeremy L.; Chen, Cheng</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 494, Issue 1, pp.L17-L21</TD>
<TD>2020-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.494L..17M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.494L...6D</TD>
<TD>On the orbital evolution of 2020 AV&lt;SUB&gt;2&lt;/SUB&gt;, the first asteroid ever observed to go around the Sun inside the orbit of Venus</TD>
<TD>de la Fuente Marcos, C.; de la Fuente Marcos, R.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 494, Issue 1, pp.L6-L10</TD>
<TD>2020-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.494L...6D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.494.3799P</TD>
<TD>A Volume-limited Sample of Cataclysmic Variables from Gaia DR2: Space Density and Population Properties</TD>
<TD>Pala, A. F.; Gänsicke, B. T.; Breedt, E.; Knigge, C.; Hermes, J. J.; Gentile Fusillo, N. P.; Hollands, M. A.; Naylor, T.; Pelisoli, I.; Schreiber, M. R.; Toonen, S.; Aungwerojwit, A.; Cukanovaite, E.; Dennihy, E.; Manser, C. J.; Pretorius, M. L.; Scaringi, S.; Toloza, O.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 494, Issue 3, pp.3799-3827</TD>
<TD>2020-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.494.3799P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.494.2861R</TD>
<TD>Near-infrared variability in dusty white dwarfs: tracing the accretion of planetary material</TD>
<TD>Rogers, Laura K.; Xu, Siyi; Bonsor, Amy; Hodgkin, Simon; Su, Kate Y. L.; von Hippel, Ted; Jura, Michael</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 494, Issue 2, pp.2861-2874</TD>
<TD>2020-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.494.2861R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.494..442V</TD>
<TD>Generating metal-polluting debris in white dwarf planetary systems from small-impact crater ejecta</TD>
<TD>Veras, Dimitri; Kurosawa, Kosuke</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 494, Issue 1, pp.442-457</TD>
<TD>2020-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.494..442V</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJS..248....7C</TD>
<TD>An Extension of the Athena++ Framework for General Equations of State</TD>
<TD>Coleman, Matthew S. B.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 248, Issue 1, id.7, 24 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJS..248....7C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...895L..23C</TD>
<TD>A Mildly Relativistic Outflow from the Energetic, Fast-rising Blue Optical Transient CSS161010 in a Dwarf Galaxy</TD>
<TD>Coppejans, D. L.; Margutti, R.; Terreran, G.; Nayana, A. J.; Coughlin, E. R.; Laskar, T.; Alexander, K. D.; Bietenholz, M.; Caprioli, D.; Chandra, P.; Drout, M. R.; Frederiks, D.; Frohmaier, C.; Hurley, K. H.; Kochanek, C. S.; MacLeod, M.; Meisner, A.; Nugent, P. E.; Ridnaia, A.; Sand, D. J.; Svinkin, D.; Ward, C.; Yang, S.; Baldeschi, A.; Chilingarian, I. V.; Dong, Y.; Esquivia, C.; Fong, W.; Guidorzi, C.; Lundqvist, P.; Milisavljevic, D.; Paterson, K.; Reichart, D. E.; Shappee, B.; Stroh, M. C.; Valenti, S.; Zauderer, B. A.; Zhang, B.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 895, Issue 1, id.L23, 15 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...895L..23C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...895L..12A</TD>
<TD>The Rotation Curve, Mass Distribution, and Dark Matter Content of the Milky Way from Classical Cepheids</TD>
<TD>Ablimit, Iminhaji; Zhao, Gang; Flynn, Chris; Bird, Sarah A.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 895, Issue 1, id.L12, 8 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...895L..12A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...895L...3A</TD>
<TD>Carnegie Supernova Project-II: A New Method to Photometrically Identify Sub-types of Extreme Type Ia Supernovae</TD>
<TD>Ashall, C.; Lu, J.; Burns, C.; Hsiao, E. Y.; Stritzinger, M.; Suntzeff, N. B.; Phillips, M.; Baron, E.; Contreras, C.; Davis, S.; Galbany, L.; Hoeflich, P.; Holmbo, S.; Morrell, N.; Karamehmetoglu, E.; Krisciunas, K.; Kumar, S.; Shahbandeh, M.; Uddin, S.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 895, Issue 1, id.L3, 9 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...895L...3A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...895...49H</TD>
<TD>The Koala: A Fast Blue Optical Transient with Luminous Radio Emission from a Starburst Dwarf Galaxy at z = 0.27</TD>
<TD>Ho, Anna Y. Q.; Perley, Daniel A.; Kulkarni, S. R.; Dong, Dillon Z. J.; De, Kishalay; Chandra, Poonam; Andreoni, Igor; Bellm, Eric C.; Burdge, Kevin B.; Coughlin, Michael; Dekany, Richard; Feeney, Michael; Frederiks, Dmitry D.; Fremling, Christoffer; Golkhou, V. Zach; Graham, Matthew J.; Hale, David; Helou, George; Horesh, Assaf; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Laher, Russ R.; Masci, Frank J.; Miller, A. A.; Porter, Michael; Ridnaia, Anna; Rusholme, Ben; Shupe, David L.; Soumagnac, Maayane T.; Svinkin, Dmitry S.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 895, Issue 1, id.49, 16 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...895...49H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...895...40G</TD>
<TD>Evaluation of Automated Fermi GBM Localizations of Gamma-Ray Bursts</TD>
<TD>Goldstein, A.; Fletcher, C.; Veres, P.; Briggs, M. S.; Cleveland, W. H.; Gibby, M. H.; Hui, C. M.; Bissaldi, E.; Burns, E.; Hamburg, R.; Kienlin, A. von; Kocevski, D.; Mailyan, B.; Malacaria, C.; Paciesas, W. S.; Roberts, O. J.; Wilson-Hodge, C. A.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 895, Issue 1, id.40, 14 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...895...40G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...895...32F</TD>
<TD>The Zwicky Transient Facility Bright Transient Survey. I. Spectroscopic Classification and the Redshift Completeness of Local Galaxy Catalogs</TD>
<TD>Fremling, C.; Miller, A. A.; Sharma, Y.; Dugas, A.; Perley, D. A.; Taggart, K.; Sollerman, J.; Goobar, A.; Graham, M. L.; Neill, J. D.; Nordin, J.; Rigault, M.; Walters, R.; Andreoni, I.; Bagdasaryan, A.; Belicki, J.; Cannella, C.; Bellm, E. C.; Cenko, S. B.; De, K.; Dekany, R.; Frederick, S.; Golkhou, V. Z.; Graham, M. J.; Helou, G.; Ho, A. Y. Q.; Kasliwal, M. M.; Kupfer, T.; Laher, R. R.; Mahabal, A.; Masci, F. J.; Riddle, R.; Rusholme, B.; Schulze, S.; Shupe, D. L.; Smith, R. M.; van Velzen, S.; Yan, Lin; Yao, Y.; Zhuang, Z.; Kulkarni, S. R.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 895, Issue 1, id.32, 19 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...895...32F</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...894L..10H</TD>
<TD>Examining a Peak-luminosity/Decline-rate Relationship for Tidal Disruption Events</TD>
<TD>Hinkle, Jason T.; Holoien, Thomas W. -S.; Shappee, Benjamin. J.; Auchettl, Katie; Kochanek, Christopher S.; Stanek, K. Z.; Payne, Anna V.; Thompson, Todd A.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 894, Issue 1, id.L10, 7 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...894L..10H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...894..127W</TD>
<TD>The Gravitational Wave Treasure Map: A Tool to Coordinate, Visualize, and Assess the Electromagnetic Follow-up of Gravitational-wave Events</TD>
<TD>Wyatt, Samuel D.; Tohuvavohu, Aaron; Arcavi, Iair; Lundquist, Michael J.; Howell, D. Andrew; Sand, David J.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 894, Issue 2, id.127, 11 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...894..127W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...894...53K</TD>
<TD>The ELM Survey South. I. An Effective Search for Extremely Low Mass White Dwarfs</TD>
<TD>Kosakowski, Alekzander; Kilic, Mukremin; Brown, Warren R.; Gianninas, Alexandros</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 894, Issue 1, id.53, 14 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...894...53K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020AJ....159..205S</TD>
<TD>Improving the Lomb-Scargle Periodogram with the Thomson Multitaper</TD>
<TD>Springford, Aaron; Eadie, Gwendolyn M.; Thomson, David J.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 159, Issue 5, id.205, 12 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020AJ....159..205S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020AJ....159..198S</TD>
<TD>Cataclysmic Variables in the First Year of the Zwicky Transient Facility</TD>
<TD>Szkody, Paula; Dicenzo, Brooke; Ho, Anna Y. Q.; Hillenbrand, Lynne A.; van Roestel, Jan; Ridder, Margaret; DeJesus Lima, Isabel; Graham, Melissa L.; Bellm, Eric C.; Burdge, Kevin; Kupfer, Thomas; Prince, Thomas A.; Masci, Frank J.; Mróz, Przemyslaw J.; Golkhou, V. Zach; Coughlin, Michael; Cunningham, Virginia A.; Dekany, Richard; Graham, Matthew J.; Hale, David; Kaplan, David; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Miller, Adam A.; Neill, James D.; Patterson, Maria T.; Riddle, Reed; Smith, Roger; Soumagnac, Maayane T.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 159, Issue 5, id.198, 16 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020AJ....159..198S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020A&amp;A...637A..83G</TD>
<TD>Subsequent outbursts of the same EXor source possibly present similar features</TD>
<TD>Giannini, T.; Giunta, A.; Lorenzetti, D.; Altavilla, G.; Antoniucci, S.; Strafella, F.; Testa, V.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 637, id.A83, 7 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020A&amp;A...637A..83G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020A&amp;A...637A..35S</TD>
<TD>Identification of 3XMM J000511.8+634018 as a new polar at P&lt;SUB&gt;orb&lt;/SUB&gt; = 133.5 min - is it inside or outside the period gap?</TD>
<TD>Schwope, A. D.; Worpel, H.; Webb, N. A.; Koliopanos, F.; Guillot, S.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 637, id.A35, 7 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020A&amp;A...637A..35S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020A&amp;A...637A..20W</TD>
<TD>AT 2019abn: multi-wavelength observations over the first 200 days</TD>
<TD>Williams, S. C.; Jones, D.; Pessev, P.; Geier, S.; Corradi, R. L. M.; Hook, I. M.; Darnley, M. J.; Pejcha, O.; Núñez, A.; Meingast, S.; Moran, S.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 637, id.A20, 13 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-05-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020A&amp;A...637A..20W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020NewA...7601336W</TD>
<TD>DX Cygni: A triple system with mass transfer</TD>
<TD>Wolf, M.; Mašek, M.; Zasche, P.; Kučáková, H.; Hornoch, K.</TD>
<TD>New Astronomy, Volume 76, article id. 101336.</TD>
<TD>2020-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020NewA...7601336W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020NatAs...4..776A</TD>
<TD>Direct evidence for shock-powered optical emission in a nova</TD>
<TD>Aydi, Elias; Sokolovsky, Kirill V.; Chomiuk, Laura; Steinberg, Elad; Li, Kwan Lok; Vurm, Indrek; Metzger, Brian D.; Strader, Jay; Mukai, Koji; Pejcha, Ondřej; Shen, Ken J.; Wade, Gregg A.; Kuschnig, Rainer; Moffat, Anthony F. J.; Pablo, Herbert; Pigulski, Andrzej; Popowicz, Adam; Weiss, Werner; Zwintz, Konstanze; Izzo, Luca; Pollard, Karen R.; Handler, Gerald; Ryder, Stuart D.; Filipović, Miroslav D.; Alsaberi, Rami Z. E.; Manojlović, Perica; Lopes de Oliveira, Raimundo; Walter, Frederick M.; Vallely, Patrick J.; Buckley, David A. H.; Brown, Michael J. I.; Harvey, Eamonn J.; Kawash, Adam; Kniazev, Alexei; Kochanek, Christopher S.; Linford, Justin; Mikolajewska, Joanna; Molaro, Paolo; Orio, Marina; Page, Kim L.; Shappee, Benjamin J.; Sokoloski, Jennifer L.</TD>
<TD>Nature Astronomy, Volume 4, p. 776-780</TD>
<TD>2020-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020NatAs...4..776A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MPBu...47..151G</TD>
<TD>Photometry of 2729 Urumqi at the Xingming Observatory in Urumqi City</TD>
<TD>Gao, Xing; Tan, Hanjie</TD>
<TD>The Minor Planet Bulletin (ISSN 1052-8091). Bulletin of the Minor Planets Section of the Association of Lunar and Planetary Observers, Vol. 47, No. 2, p. 151 (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MPBu...47..151G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.493.6001L</TD>
<TD>First discovery of an ultra-cool white dwarf benchmark in common proper motion with an M dwarf</TD>
<TD>Lam, M. C.; Hambly, N. C.; Lodieu, N.; Blouin, S.; Harvey, E. J.; Smith, R. J.; Gálvez-Ortiz, M. C.; Zhang, Z. H.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 493, Issue 4, pp.6001-6010</TD>
<TD>2020-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.493.6001L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.493.4428A</TD>
<TD>Detection of gamma-ray transients with wild binary segmentation</TD>
<TD>Antier, S.; Barynova, K.; Fryzlewicz, P.; Lachaud, C.; Marchal-Duval, G.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 493, Issue 3, p.4428-4441</TD>
<TD>2020-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.493.4428A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.493.3956Z</TD>
<TD>Faint rapid red transients from neutron star-CO white dwarf mergers</TD>
<TD>Zenati, Yossef; Bobrick, Alexey; Perets, Hagai B.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 493, Issue 3, p.3956-3965</TD>
<TD>2020-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.493.3956Z</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.493.3825L</TD>
<TD>Variability and transient search in the SUDARE-VOICE field: a new method to extract the light curves</TD>
<TD>Liu, Dezi; Deng, Wenqiang; Fan, Zuhui; Fu, Liping; Covone, Giovanni; Vaccari, Mattia; Radovich, Mario; Capaccioli, Massimo; De Cicco, Demetra; Grado, Aniello; Marchetti, Lucia; Napolitano, Nicola; Paolillo, Maurizio; Pignata, Giuliano; Ragosta, Fabio</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 493, Issue 3, p.3825-3837</TD>
<TD>2020-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.493.3825L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020AstL...46..235B</TD>
<TD>Search for Evolutionary Changes in the Period the Cepheid ET Vul</TD>
<TD>Berdnikov, L. N.; Pastukhova, E. N.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy Letters, Volume 46, Issue 4, p.235-244</TD>
<TD>2020-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020AstL...46..235B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJS..247...50S</TD>
<TD>Physical Parameters of Late-type Contact Binaries in the Northern Catalina Sky Survey</TD>
<TD>Sun, Weijia; Chen, Xiaodian; Deng, Licai; de Grijs, Richard</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Supplement Series, Volume 247, Issue 2, id.50, 12 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJS..247...50S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...893..166D</TD>
<TD>Necroplanetology: Simulating the Tidal Disruption of Differentiated Planetary Material Orbiting WD 1145+017</TD>
<TD>Duvvuri, Girish M.; Redfield, Seth; Veras, Dimitri</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 893, Issue 2, id.166, 7 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...893..166D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...893..153K</TD>
<TD>Constraint on the Ejecta Mass for Black Hole-Neutron Star Merger Event Candidate S190814bv</TD>
<TD>Kawaguchi, Kyohei; Shibata, Masaru; Tanaka, Masaomi</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 893, Issue 2, id.153, 17 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...893..153K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...893..143K</TD>
<TD>SN 2019ein: New Insights into the Similarities and Diversity among High-velocity Type Ia Supernovae</TD>
<TD>Kawabata, Miho; Maeda, Keiichi; Yamanaka, Masayuki; Nakaoka, Tatsuya; Kawabata, Koji S.; Adachi, Ryo; Akitaya, Hiroshi; Burgaz, Umut; Hanayama, Hidekazu; Horiuchi, Takashi; Hosokawa, Ryohei; Iida, Kota; Imazato, Fumiya; Isogai, Keisuke; Jiang, Ji-an; Katoh, Noriyuki; Kimura, Hiroki; Kino, Masaru; Kuroda, Daisuke; Maehara, Hiroyuki; Matsubayashi, Kazuya; Morihana, Kumiko; Murata, Katsuhiro L.; Nagao, Takashi; Niwano, Masafumi; Nogami, Daisaku; Oeda, Motoki; Ono, Tatsuharu; Onozato, Hiroki; Otsuka, Masaaki; Saito, Tomoki; Sasada, Mahito; Shiraishi, Kazuki; Sugiyama, Haruki; Taguchi, Kenta; Takahashi, Jun; Takagi, Kengo; Takagi, Seiko; Takayama, Masaki; Tozuka, Miyako; Sekiguchi, Kazuhiro</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 893, Issue 2, id.143, 16 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...893..143K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...893..132H</TD>
<TD>The Broad-lined Ic Supernova ZTF18aaqjovh (SN 2018bvw): An Optically Discovered Engine-driven Supernova Candidate with Luminous Radio Emission</TD>
<TD>Ho, Anna Y. Q.; Corsi, Alessandra; Cenko, S. Bradley; Taddia, Francesco; Kulkarni, S. R.; Adams, Scott; De, Kishalay; Dekany, Richard; Frederiks, Dmitry D.; Fremling, Christoffer; Golkhou, V. Zach; Graham, Matthew J.; Hung, Tiara; Kupfer, Thomas; Laher, Russ R.; Mahabal, Ashish; Masci, Frank J.; Miller, Adam A.; Neill, James D.; Reiley, Daniel; Riddle, Reed; Ridnaia, Anna; Rusholme, Ben; Sharma, Yashvi; Sollerman, Jesper; Soumagnac, Maayane T.; Svinkin, Dmitry S.; Shupe, David L.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 893, Issue 2, id.132, 11 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...893..132H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...893..127S</TD>
<TD>Real-time, Value-driven Data Augmentation in the Era of LSST</TD>
<TD>Sravan, Niharika; Milisavljevic, Dan; Reynolds, Jack M.; Lentner, Geoffrey; Linvill, Mark</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 893, Issue 2, id.127, 11 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...893..127S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...893...99C</TD>
<TD>Three-dimensional Simulations of Magnetar-powered Superluminous Supernovae</TD>
<TD>Chen, Ke-Jung; Woosley, S. E.; Whalen, Daniel J.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 893, Issue 2, id.99, 10 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...893...99C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...893...11S</TD>
<TD>Variability of Massive Stars in M31 from the Palomar Transient Factory</TD>
<TD>Soraisam, Monika D.; Bildsten, Lars; Drout, Maria R.; Prince, Thomas A.; Kupfer, Thomas; Masci, Frank; Laher, Russ R.; Kulkarni, Shrinivas R.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 893, Issue 1, id.11, 27 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...893...11S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...893....2L</TD>
<TD>Gravitational-wave Radiation of Double Degenerates with Extremely Low-mass White Dwarf Companions</TD>
<TD>Li, Zhenwei; Chen, Xuefei; Chen, Hai-Liang; Li, Jiao; Yu, Shenghua; Han, Zhanwen</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 893, Issue 1, id.2, 13 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...893....2L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...892L..36M</TD>
<TD>The Low Earth Orbit Satellite Population and Impacts of the SpaceX Starlink Constellation</TD>
<TD>McDowell, Jonathan C.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 892, Issue 2, id.L36, 10 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...892L..36M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...892L..35B</TD>
<TD>A 1201 s Orbital Period Detached Binary: The First Double Helium Core White Dwarf LISA Verification Binary</TD>
<TD>Brown, Warren R.; Kilic, Mukremin; Bédard, A.; Kosakowski, Alekzander; Bergeron, P.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 892, Issue 2, id.L35, 5 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...892L..35B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...892L..26L</TD>
<TD>LAMOST J040643.69+542347.8: The Fastest Rotator in the Galaxy</TD>
<TD>Li, Guang-Wei</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 892, Issue 2, id.L26, 5 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...892L..26L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...892L..24S</TD>
<TD>The Lowest of the Low: Discovery of SN 2019gsc and the Nature of Faint Iax Supernovae</TD>
<TD>Srivastav, Shubham; Smartt, Stephen J.; Leloudas, Giorgos; Huber, Mark E.; Chambers, Ken; Malesani, Daniele B.; Hjorth, Jens; Gillanders, James H.; Schultz, A.; Sim, Stuart A.; Auchettl, Katie; Fynbo, Johan P. U.; Gall, Christa; McBrien, Owen R.; Rest, Armin; Smith, Ken W.; Wojtak, Radoslaw; Young, David R.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 892, Issue 2, id.L24, 9 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...892L..24S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...892..153M</TD>
<TD>Host Galaxies of Type Ic and Broad-lined Type Ic Supernovae from the Palomar Transient Factory: Implications for Jet Production</TD>
<TD>Modjaz, Maryam; Bianco, Federica B.; Siwek, Magdalena; Huang, Shan; Perley, Daniel A.; Fierroz, David; Liu, Yu-Qian; Arcavi, Iair; Gal-Yam, Avishay; Filippenko, Alexei V.; Blagorodnova, Nadia; Cenko, Bradley S.; Kasliwal, Mansi; Kulkarni, Shri; Schulze, Steve; Taggart, Kirsty; Zheng, Weikang</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 892, Issue 2, id.153, 48 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...892..153M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...892..142H</TD>
<TD>SN 2017cfd: A Normal Type Ia Supernova Discovered Very Young</TD>
<TD>Han, Xuhui; Zheng, WeiKang; Stahl, Benjamin E.; Burke, Jamison; Vinko, Jozsef; de Jaeger, Thomas; Arcavi, Iair; Brink, Thomas G.; Cseh, Borbala; Hiramatsu, Daichi; Hosseinzadeh, Griffin; Howell, D. Andrew; Ignacz, Bernadett; Konyves-Toth, Reka; Krezinger, Mate; McCully, Curtis; Ordasi, Andras; Pinter, Dora; Sarneczky, Krisztian; Szakats, Robert; Tang, Kevin; Vida, Krisztian; Wang, Jing; Wei, Jianyan; Wheeler, J. Craig; Xin, Liping; Filippenko, Alexei V.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 892, Issue 2, id.142, 10 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...892..142H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...892..112S</TD>
<TD>A Classification Algorithm for Time-domain Novelties in Preparation for LSST Alerts. Application to Variable Stars and Transients Detected with DECam in the Galactic Bulge</TD>
<TD>Soraisam, Monika D.; Saha, Abhijit; Matheson, Thomas; Lee, Chien-Hsiu; Narayan, Gautham; Vivas, A. Katherina; Scheidegger, Carlos; Oppermann, Niels; Olszewski, Edward W.; Sinha, Sukriti; Desantis, Sarah R.; ANTARES Collaboration</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 892, Issue 2, id.112, 19 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...892..112S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ARep...64..310B</TD>
<TD>BVI&lt;SUB&gt;c&lt;/SUB&gt; Observations and Search for Evolutionary Variations in the Cepheid V811 Oph Period</TD>
<TD>Berdnikov, L. N.; Belinskii, A. A.; Shatskii, N. I.; Burlak, M. A.; Ikonnikova, N. P.; Mishin, E. O.; Cheryasov, D. V.; Zhuiko, S. V.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy Reports, Volume 64, Issue 4, p.310-318</TD>
<TD>2020-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ARep...64..310B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020A&amp;A...636A..46L</TD>
<TD>SUGAR: An improved empirical model of Type Ia supernovae based on spectral features</TD>
<TD>Léget, P. -F.; Gangler, E.; Mondon, F.; Aldering, G.; Antilogus, P.; Aragon, C.; Bailey, S.; Baltay, C.; Barbary, K.; Bongard, S.; Boone, K.; Buton, C.; Chotard, N.; Copin, Y.; Dixon, S.; Fagrelius, P.; Feindt, U.; Fouchez, D.; Hayden, B.; Hillebrandt, W.; Kim, A.; Kowalski, M.; Kuesters, D.; Lombardo, S.; Lin, Q.; Nordin, J.; Pain, R.; Pecontal, E.; Pereira, R.; Perlmutter, S.; Ponder, K. A.; Pruzhinskaya, M. V.; Rabinowitz, D.; Rigault, M.; Runge, K.; Rubin, D.; Saunders, C.; Says, L. -P.; Smadja, G.; Sofiatti, C.; Suzuki, N.; Taubenberger, S.; Tao, C.; Thomas, R. C.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 636, id.A46, 24 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-04-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020A&amp;A...636A..46L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020SSRv..216...35S</TD>
<TD>Rates of Stellar Tidal Disruption</TD>
<TD>Stone, N. C.; Vasiliev, E.; Kesden, M.; Rossi, E. M.; Perets, H. B.; Amaro-Seoane, P.</TD>
<TD>Space Science Reviews, Volume 216, Issue 3, article id.35</TD>
<TD>2020-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020SSRv..216...35S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020SSRv..216...32F</TD>
<TD>The Host Galaxies of Tidal Disruption Events</TD>
<TD>French, K. Decker; Wevers, Thomas; Law-Smith, Jamie; Graur, Or; Zabludoff, Ann I.</TD>
<TD>Space Science Reviews, Volume 216, Issue 3, article id.32</TD>
<TD>2020-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020SSRv..216...32F</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020RuPhJ..62.1989B</TD>
<TD>Mechanism of High-Efficiency Electron Beam Generation in a High-Voltage Discharge in Helium and Its Mixtures with Oxygen and Nitrogen</TD>
<TD>Bokhan, P. A.; Gugin, P. P.; Zakrevsky, D. E.; Lavrukhin, M. A.</TD>
<TD>Russian Physics Journal, Volume 62, Issue 11, p.1989-1992</TD>
<TD>2020-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020RuPhJ..62.1989B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020PASP..132c8001D</TD>
<TD>The Zwicky Transient Facility: Observing System</TD>
<TD>Dekany, Richard; Smith, Roger M.; Riddle, Reed; Feeney, Michael; Porter, Michael; Hale, David; Zolkower, Jeffry; Belicki, Justin; Kaye, Stephen; Henning, John; Walters, Richard; Cromer, John; Delacroix, Alex; Rodriguez, Hector; Reiley, Daniel J.; Mao, Peter; Hover, David; Murphy, Patrick; Burruss, Rick; Baker, John; Kowalski, Marek; Reif, Klaus; Mueller, Phillip; Bellm, Eric; Graham, Matthew; Kulkarni, Shrinivas R.</TD>
<TD>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 132, Issue 1009, id. 038001 (2020)., 26 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020PASP..132c8001D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020PASP..132c5001L</TD>
<TD>The Karl G. Jansky Very Large Array Sky Survey (VLASS). Science Case and Survey Design</TD>
<TD>Lacy, M.; Baum, S. A.; Chandler, C. J.; Chatterjee, S.; Clarke, T. E.; Deustua, S.; English, J.; Farnes, J.; Gaensler, B. M.; Gugliucci, N.; Hallinan, G.; Kent, B. R.; Kimball, A.; Law, C. J.; Lazio, T. J. W.; Marvil, J.; Mao, S. A.; Medlin, D.; Mooley, K.; Murphy, E. J.; Myers, S.; Osten, R.; Richards, G. T.; Rosolowsky, E.; Rudnick, L.; Schinzel, F.; Sivakoff, G. R.; Sjouwerman, L. O.; Taylor, R.; White, R. L.; Wrobel, J.; Andernach, H.; Beasley, A. J.; Berger, E.; Bhatnager, S.; Birkinshaw, M.; Bower, G. C.; Brandt, W. N.; Brown, S.; Burke-Spolaor, S.; Butler, B. J.; Comerford, J.; Demorest, P. B.; Fu, H.; Giacintucci, S.; Golap, K.; Güth, T.; Hales, C. A.; Hiriart, R.; Hodge, J.; Horesh, A.; Ivezić, Ž.; Jarvis, M. J.; Kamble, A.; Kassim, N.; Liu, X.; Loinard, L.; Lyons, D. K.; Masters, J.; Mezcua, M.; Moellenbrock, G. A.; Mroczkowski, T.; Nyland, K.; O'Dea, C. P.; O'Sullivan, S. P.; Peters, W. M.; Radford, K.; Rao, U.; Robnett, J.; Salcido, J.; Shen, Y.; Sobotka, A.; Witz, S.; Vaccari, M.; van Weeren, R. J.; Vargas, A.; Williams, P. K. G.; Yoon, I.</TD>
<TD>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 132, Issue 1009, id. 035001 (2020)., 30 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020PASP..132c5001L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.493..765V</TD>
<TD>Constraining planet formation around 6-8 M&lt;SUB&gt;⊙&lt;/SUB&gt; stars</TD>
<TD>Veras, Dimitri; Tremblay, Pier-Emmanuel; Hermes, J. J.; McDonald, Catriona H.; Kennedy, Grant M.; Meru, Farzana; Gänsicke, Boris T.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 493, Issue 1, pp.765-775</TD>
<TD>2020-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.493..765V</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.493..698M</TD>
<TD>Tidal disruption of planetary bodies by white dwarfs - II. Debris disc structure and ejected interstellar asteroids</TD>
<TD>Malamud, Uri; Perets, Hagai B.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 493, Issue 1, p.698-712</TD>
<TD>2020-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.493..698M</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.492.5916W</TD>
<TD>Limits on the electromagnetic counterpart to S190814bv</TD>
<TD>Watson, A. M.; Butler, N. R.; Lee, W. H.; Becerra, R. L.; Pereyra, M.; Angeles, F.; Farah, A.; Figueroa, L.; Gónzalez-Buitrago, D.; Quirós, F.; Ruíz-Díaz-Soto, J.; Tejada de Vargas, C.; Tinoco, S. J.; Wolfram, T.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 492, Issue 4, p.5916-5921</TD>
<TD>2020-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.492.5916W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.492.5291V</TD>
<TD>Constraining the origin of the planetary debris surrounding ZTF J0139+5245 through rotational fission of a triaxial asteroid</TD>
<TD>Veras, Dimitri; McDonald, Catriona H.; Makarov, Valeri V.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 492, Issue 4, p.5291-5296</TD>
<TD>2020-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.492.5291V</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.492.3904A</TD>
<TD>The first six months of the Advanced LIGO's and Advanced Virgo's third observing run with GRANDMA</TD>
<TD>Antier, S.; Agayeva, S.; Aivazyan, V.; Alishov, S.; Arbouch, E.; Baransky, A.; Barynova, K.; Bai, J. M.; Basa, S.; Beradze, S.; Bertin, E.; Berthier, J.; Blažek, M.; Boër, M.; Burkhonov, O.; Burrell, A.; Cailleau, A.; Chabert, B.; Chen, J. C.; Christensen, N.; Coleiro, A.; Cordier, B.; Corre, D.; Coughlin, M. W.; Coward, D.; Crisp, H.; Delattre, C.; Dietrich, T.; Ducoin, J. -G.; Duverne, P. -A.; Marchal-Duval, G.; Gendre, B.; Eymar, L.; Fock-Hang, P.; Han, X.; Hello, P.; Howell, E. J.; Inasaridze, R.; Ismailov, N.; Kann, D. A.; Kapanadze, G.; Klotz, A.; Kochiashvili, N.; Lachaud, C.; Leroy, N.; Le Van Su, A.; Lin, W. L.; Li, W. X.; Lognone, P.; Marron, R.; Mo, J.; Moore, J.; Natsvlishvili, R.; Noysena, K.; Perrigault, S.; Peyrot, A.; Samadov, D.; Sadibekova, T.; Simon, A.; Stachie, C.; Teng, J. P.; Thierry, P.; Thöne, C. C.; Tillayev, Y.; Turpin, D.; de Ugarte Postigo, A.; Vachier, F.; Vardosanidze, M.; Vasylenko, V.; Vidadi, Z.; Wang, X. F.; Wang, C. J.; Wei, J.; Yan, S. Y.; Zhang, J. C.; Zhang, J. J.; Zhang, X. H.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 492, Issue 3, p.3904-3927</TD>
<TD>2020-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.492.3904A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.492.3229H</TD>
<TD>Luminous Red Novae: population models and future prospects</TD>
<TD>Howitt, George; Stevenson, Simon; Vigna-Gómez, Alejandro; Justham, Stephen; Ivanova, Natasha; Woods, Tyrone E.; Neijssel, Coenraad J.; Mandel, Ilya</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 492, Issue 3, p.3229-3240</TD>
<TD>2020-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.492.3229H</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020CoSka..50..565P</TD>
<TD>The brave new world of eclipsing binary modeling</TD>
<TD>Prša, A.</TD>
<TD>Contributions of the Astronomical Observatory Skalnaté Pleso, vol. 50, no. 2, p. 565-569.</TD>
<TD>2020-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020CoSka..50..565P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020CoSka..50..472R</TD>
<TD>The explosive life of massive binaries</TD>
<TD>Renzo, M.; Zapartas, E.</TD>
<TD>Contributions of the Astronomical Observatory Skalnaté Pleso, vol. 50, no. 2, p. 472-480.</TD>
<TD>2020-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020CoSka..50..472R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020AstL...46..156B</TD>
<TD>\boldsymbol{BVI}_{\boldsymbol{c}}\boldsymbol{g('r^'i^') Observations and Search for Evolutionary Changes in the Period of the Cepheid V1467 Cyg</TD>
<TD>Berdnikov, L. N.; Belinskii, A. A.; Pastukhova, E. N.; Burlak, M. A.; Ikonnikova, N. P.; Mishin, E. O.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy Letters, Volume 46, Issue 3, p.156-167</TD>
<TD>2020-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020AstL...46..156B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...892L...1L</TD>
<TD>Optical Polarimetry of the Tidal Disruption Event AT2019DSG</TD>
<TD>Lee, Chien-Hsiu; Hung, Tiara; Matheson, Thomas; Soraisam, Monika; Narayan, Gautham; Saha, Abhjita; Stubens, Carl; Wolf, Nicholas</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 892, Issue 1, id.L1, 5 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...892L...1L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...892...28K</TD>
<TD>SN 2010kd: Photometric and Spectroscopic Analysis of a Slow-decaying Superluminous Supernova</TD>
<TD>Kumar, Amit; Pandey, Shashi Bhushan; Konyves-Toth, Reka; Staten, Ryan; Vinko, Jozsef; Wheeler, J. Craig; Zheng, WeiKang; Filippenko, Alexei V.; Kehoe, Robert; Quimby, Robert; Fang, Yuan; Akerlof, Carl; McKay, Tim A.; Chatzopoulos, Emmanouil; Thomas, Benjamin P.; Dhungana, Govinda; Aryan, Amar; Dastidar, Raya; Gangopadhyay, Anjasha; Gupta, Rahul; Misra, Kuntal; Kumar, Brajesh; Brahme, Nameeta; Buckley, David</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 892, Issue 1, id.28, 23 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...892...28K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...892...25J</TD>
<TD>The HSC-SSP Transient Survey: Implications from Early Photometry and Rise Time of Normal Type Ia Supernovae</TD>
<TD>Jiang, Ji-an; Yasuda, Naoki; Maeda, Keiichi; Doi, Mamoru; Shigeyama, Toshikazu; Tominaga, Nozomu; Tanaka, Masaomi; Moriya, Takashi J.; Takahashi, Ichiro; Suzuki, Nao; Morokuma, Tomoki; Nomoto, Ken'ichi</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 892, Issue 1, id.25, 9 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...892...25J</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...891...45K</TD>
<TD>The First Ultracompact Roche Lobe-Filling Hot Subdwarf Binary</TD>
<TD>Kupfer, Thomas; Bauer, Evan B.; Marsh, Thomas R.; van Roestel, Jan; Bellm, Eric C.; Burdge, Kevin B.; Coughlin, Michael W.; Fuller, Jim; Hermes, JJ; Bildsten, Lars; Kulkarni, Shrinivas R.; Prince, Thomas A.; Szkody, Paula; Dhillon, Vik S.; Murawski, Gabriel; Burruss, Rick; Dekany, Richard; Delacroix, Alex; Drake, Andrew J.; Duev, Dmitry A.; Feeney, Michael; Graham, Matthew J.; Kaplan, David L.; Laher, Russ R.; Littlefair, S. P.; Masci, Frank J.; Riddle, Reed; Rusholme, Ben; Serabyn, Eugene; Smith, Roger M.; Shupe, David L.; Soumagnac, Maayane T.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 891, Issue 1, id.45, 15 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...891...45K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020A&amp;A...635A.186P</TD>
<TD>The rise and fall of an extraordinary Ca-rich transient. The discovery of ATLAS19dqr/SN 2019bkc</TD>
<TD>Prentice, S. J.; Maguire, K.; Flörs, A.; Taubenberger, S.; Inserra, C.; Frohmaier, C.; Chen, T. W.; Anderson, J. P.; Ashall, C.; Clark, P.; Fraser, M.; Galbany, L.; Gal-Yam, A.; Gromadzki, M.; Gutiérrez, C. P.; James, P. A.; Jonker, P. G.; Kankare, E.; Leloudas, G.; Magee, M. R.; Mazzali, P. A.; Nicholl, M.; Pursiainen, M.; Skillen, K.; Smartt, S. J.; Smith, K. W.; Vogl, C.; Young, D. R.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 635, id.A186, 17 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-03-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020A&amp;A...635A.186P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020PASP..132b5001D</TD>
<TD>Palomar Gattini-IR: Survey Overview, Data Processing System, On-sky Performance and First Results</TD>
<TD>De, Kishalay; Hankins, Matthew J.; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Moore, Anna M.; Ofek, Eran O.; Adams, Scott M.; Ashley, Michael C. B.; Babul, Aliya-Nur; Bagdasaryan, Ashot; Burdge, Kevin B.; Burnham, Jill; Dekany, Richard G.; Declacroix, Alexander; Galla, Antony; Greffe, Tim; Hale, David; Jencson, Jacob E.; Lau, Ryan M.; Mahabal, Ashish; McKenna, Daniel; Sharma, Manasi; Shopbell, Patrick L.; Smith, Roger M.; Soon, Jamie; Sokoloski, Jennifer; Soria, Roberto; Travouillon, Tony</TD>
<TD>Publications of the Astronomical Society of the Pacific, Volume 132, Issue 1008, id. 025001 (2020)., 31 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020PASP..132b5001D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.493L.129G</TD>
<TD>Orbital Dynamics of 2020 AV&lt;SUB&gt;2&lt;/SUB&gt;: the First Vatira Asteroid</TD>
<TD>Greenstreet, Sarah</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society: Letters, Volume 493, Issue 1, pp. L129-L131</TD>
<TD>2020-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.493L.129G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.492.2578S</TD>
<TD>Missing red supergiants and carbon burning</TD>
<TD>Sukhbold, Tuguldur; Adams, Scott</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 492, Issue 2, p.2578-2587</TD>
<TD>2020-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.492.2578S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.492.2437V</TD>
<TD>Post-main-sequence debris from rotation-induced YORP break-up of small bodies - II. Multiple fissions, internal strengths, and binary production</TD>
<TD>Veras, Dimitri; Scheeres, Daniel J.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 492, Issue 2, p.2437-2445</TD>
<TD>2020-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.492.2437V</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.492.2208C</TD>
<TD>LSQ13ddu: a rapidly evolving stripped-envelope supernova with early circumstellar interaction signatures</TD>
<TD>Clark, Peter; Maguire, Kate; Inserra, Cosimo; Prentice, Simon; Smartt, Stephen J.; Contreras, Carlos; Hossenizadeh, Griffin; Hsiao, Eric Y.; Kankare, Erkki; Kasliwal, Mansi; Nugent, Peter; Shahbandeh, Melissa; Baltay, Charles; Rabinowitz, David; Arcavi, Iair; Ashall, Chris; Burns, Christopher R.; Callis, Emma; Chen, Ting-Wan; Diamond, Tiara; Fraser, Morgan; Howell, D. Andrew; Karamehmetoglu, Emir; Kotak, Rubina; Lyman, Joseph; Morrell, Nidia; Phillips, Mark; Pignata, Giuliano; Pursiainen, Miika; Sollerman, Jesper; Stritzinger, Maximilian; Sullivan, Mark; Young, David</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 492, Issue 2, p.2208-2228</TD>
<TD>2020-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.492.2208C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.492..863C</TD>
<TD>Implications of the search for optical counterparts during the first six months of the Advanced LIGO's and Advanced Virgo's third observing run: possible limits on the ejecta mass and binary properties</TD>
<TD>Coughlin, Michael W.; Dietrich, Tim; Antier, Sarah; Bulla, Mattia; Foucart, Francois; Hotokezaka, Kenta; Raaijmakers, Geert; Hinderer, Tanja; Nissanke, Samaya</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 492, Issue 1, p.863-876</TD>
<TD>2020-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.492..863C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.492..843G</TD>
<TD>Constraining the fraction of core-collapse supernovae harbouring choked jets with high-energy neutrinos</TD>
<TD>Guetta, Dafne; Rahin, Roi; Bartos, Imre; Della Valle, Massimo</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 492, Issue 1, p.843-847</TD>
<TD>2020-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.492..843G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.492..686L</TD>
<TD>Self-intersection of the fallback stream in tidal disruption events</TD>
<TD>Lu, Wenbin; Bonnerot, Clément</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 492, Issue 1, p.686-707</TD>
<TD>2020-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.492..686L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.492..232B</TD>
<TD>Pulsation in faint blue stars</TD>
<TD>Byrne, Conor M.; Jeffery, C. Simon</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 492, Issue 1, p.232-244</TD>
<TD>2020-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.492..232B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.491.5852A</TD>
<TD>Probing the extragalactic fast transient sky at minute time-scales with DECam</TD>
<TD>Andreoni, I.; Cooke, J.; Webb, S.; Rest, A.; Pritchard, T.; Caleb, M.; Chang, S. -W.; Farah, W.; Lien, A.; Möller, A.; Ravasio, M. E.; Abbott, T. M. C.; Bhandari, S.; Cucchiara, A.; Flynn, C.; Jankowski, F.; Keane, E. F.; Moriya, T. J.; Onken, C. A.; Parthasarathy, A.; Price, D. C.; Petroff, E.; Ryder, S.; Vohl, D.; Wolf, C.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 491, Issue 4, p.5852-5866</TD>
<TD>2020-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.491.5852A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.491.4925G</TD>
<TD>Understanding extreme quasar optical variability with CRTS - II. Changing-state quasars</TD>
<TD>Graham, Matthew J.; Ross, Nicholas P.; Stern, Daniel; Drake, Andrew J.; McKernan, Barry; Ford, K. E. Saavik; Djorgovski, S. G.; Mahabal, Ashish A.; Glikman, Eilat; Larson, Steve; Christensen, Eric</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 491, Issue 4, p.4925-4948</TD>
<TD>2020-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.491.4925G</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020AstL...45..710P</TD>
<TD>Observation of the Second LIGO/Virgo Event Connected with a Binary Neutron Star Merger S190425z in the Gamma-Ray Range</TD>
<TD>Pozanenko, A. S.; Minaev, P. Yu.; Grebenev, S. A.; Chelovekov, I. V.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy Letters, Volume 45, Issue 11, p.710-727</TD>
<TD>2020-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020AstL...45..710P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...890L..26K</TD>
<TD>Rapid Transients Originating from Thermonuclear Explosions in Helium White Dwarf Tidal Disruption Events</TD>
<TD>Kawana, Kojiro; Maeda, Keiichi; Yoshida, Naoki; Tanikawa, Ataru</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 890, Issue 2, id.L26, 7 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...890L..26K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...890..177K</TD>
<TD>A New Method to Classify Type IIP/IIL Supernovae Based on Their Spectra</TD>
<TD>Kou, Shihao; Chen, Xingzhuo; Liu, Xuewen</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 890, Issue 2, id.177, 11 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...890..177K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...890..131A</TD>
<TD>GROWTH on S190814bv: Deep Synoptic Limits on the Optical/Near-infrared Counterpart to a Neutron Star-Black Hole Merger</TD>
<TD>Andreoni, Igor; Goldstein, Daniel A.; Kasliwal, Mansi M.; Nugent, Peter E.; Zhou, Rongpu; Newman, Jeffrey A.; Bulla, Mattia; Foucart, Francois; Hotokezaka, Kenta; Nakar, Ehud; Nissanke, Samaya; Raaijmakers, Geert; Bloom, Joshua S.; De, Kishalay; Jencson, Jacob E.; Ward, Charlotte; Ahumada, Tomás; Anand, Shreya; Buckley, David A. H.; Caballero-García, Maria D.; Castro-Tirado, Alberto J.; Copperwheat, Christopher M.; Coughlin, Michael W.; Cenko, S. Bradley; Gromadzki, Mariusz; Hu, Youdong; Karambelkar, Viraj R.; Perley, Daniel A.; Sharma, Yashvi; Valeev, Azamat F.; Cook, David O.; Fremling, U. Christoffer; Kumar, Harsh; Taggart, Kirsty; Bagdasaryan, Ashot; Cooke, Jeff; Dahiwale, Aishwarya; Dhawan, Suhail; Dobie, Dougal; Gatkine, Pradip; Golkhou, V. Zach; Goobar, Ariel; Chaves, Andreas Guerra; Hankins, Matthew; Kaplan, David L.; Kong, Albert K. H.; Kool, Erik C.; Mohite, Siddharth; Sollerman, Jesper; Tzanidakis, Anastasios; Webb, Sara; Zhang, Keming</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 890, Issue 2, id.131, 16 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...890..131A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...890..127C</TD>
<TD>Simulating Turbulence-aided Neutrino-driven Core-collapse Supernova Explosions in One Dimension</TD>
<TD>Couch, Sean M.; Warren, MacKenzie L.; O'Connor, Evan P.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 890, Issue 2, id.127, 24 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...890..127C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...890...73B</TD>
<TD>The Prospects of Observing Tidal Disruption Events with the Large Synoptic Survey Telescope</TD>
<TD>Bricman, Katja; Gomboc, Andreja</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 890, Issue 1, id.73, 10 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...890...73B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...890...69L</TD>
<TD>Possible Formation Scenarios of ZTF J153932.16+502738.8—A Gravitational Source Close to the Peak of LISA's Sensitivity</TD>
<TD>Lü, Guoliang; Zhu, Chunhua; Wang, Zhaojun; Liu, Helei; Li, Lin; Xie, Dian; Liu, Jinzhong</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 890, Issue 1, id.69, 6 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...890...69L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...890...46T</TD>
<TD>Superflares on Solar-type Stars from the First Year Observation of TESS</TD>
<TD>Tu, Zuo-Lin; Yang, Ming; Zhang, Z. J.; Wang, F. Y.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 890, Issue 1, id.46, 15 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...890...46T</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...889L..37N</TD>
<TD>An Extreme X-Ray Variability Event of a Weak-line Quasar</TD>
<TD>Ni, Q.; Brandt, W. N.; Yi, W.; Luo, B.; Timlin, J. D., III; Hall, P. B.; Liu, Hezhen; Plotkin, R. M.; Shemmer, O.; Vito, F.; Wu, Jianfeng</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 889, Issue 2, id.L37, 6 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...889L..37N</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...889..171K</TD>
<TD>Diversity of Kilonova Light Curves</TD>
<TD>Kawaguchi, Kyohei; Shibata, Masaru; Tanaka, Masaomi</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 889, Issue 2, id.171, 25 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...889..171K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020AJ....159...77Y</TD>
<TD>Pre-discovery Activity of New Interstellar Comet 2I/Borisov beyond 5 au</TD>
<TD>Ye, Quanzhi; Kelley, Michael S. P.; Bolin, Bryce T.; Bodewits, Dennis; Farnocchia, Davide; Masci, Frank J.; Meech, Karen J.; Micheli, Marco; Weryk, Robert; Bellm, Eric C.; Christensen, Eric; Dekany, Richard; Delacroix, Alexandre; Graham, Matthew J.; Kulkarni, Shrinivas R.; Laher, Russ R.; Rusholme, Ben; Smith, Roger M.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 159, Issue 2, id.77, 9 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020AJ....159...77Y</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020AJ....159...70Y</TD>
<TD>A Twilight Search for Atiras, Vatiras, and Co-orbital Asteroids: Preliminary Results</TD>
<TD>Ye, Quanzhi; Masci, Frank J.; Ip, Wing-Huen; Prince, Thomas A.; Helou, George; Farnocchia, Davide; Bellm, Eric C.; Dekany, Richard; Graham, Matthew J.; Kulkarni, Shrinivas R.; Kupfer, Thomas; Mahabal, Ashish; Ngeow, Chow-Choong; Reiley, Daniel J.; Soumagnac, Maayane T.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 159, Issue 2, id.70, 6 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020AJ....159...70Y</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020AJ....159...61L</TD>
<TD>ZTF18abhjrcf: The First R Coronae Borealis Star from the Zwicky Transient Facility Public Survey</TD>
<TD>Lee, Chien-Hsiu; Matheson, Thomas; Soraisam, Monika; Narayan, Gautham; Saha, Abhjita; Stubens, Carl; Wolf, Nicholas</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 159, Issue 2, id.61, 6 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020AJ....159...61L</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020A&amp;A...634A..93C</TD>
<TD>Gravity and limb-darkening coefficients for compact stars: DA, DB, and DBA eclipsing white dwarfs</TD>
<TD>Claret, A.; Cukanovaite, E.; Burdge, K.; Tremblay, P. -E.; Parsons, S.; Marsh, T. R.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 634, id.A93, 9 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020A&amp;A...634A..93C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020A&amp;A...634A..48P</TD>
<TD>MAXIMASK and MAXITRACK: Two new tools for identifying contaminants in astronomical images using convolutional neural networks</TD>
<TD>Paillassa, M.; Bertin, E.; Bouy, H.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 634, id.A48, 24 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020A&amp;A...634A..48P</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020A&amp;A...634A..32S</TD>
<TD>Web application for galaxy-targeted follow-up of electromagnetic counterparts to gravitational wave sources</TD>
<TD>Salmon, L.; Hanlon, L.; Jeffrey, R. M.; Martin-Carrillo, A.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 634, id.A32, 9 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020A&amp;A...634A..32S</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020A&amp;A...634A..14B</TD>
<TD>A search for the origin of the interstellar comet 2I/Borisov</TD>
<TD>Bailer-Jones, Coryn A. L.; Farnocchia, Davide; Ye, Quanzhi; Meech, Karen J.; Micheli, Marco</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 634, id.A14, 6 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-02-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020A&amp;A...634A..14B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020PhRvD.101b3516K</TD>
<TD>Complementarity of peculiar velocity surveys and redshift space distortions for testing gravity</TD>
<TD>Kim, Alex G.; Linder, Eric V.</TD>
<TD>Physical Review D, Volume 101, Issue 2, article id.023516</TD>
<TD>2020-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020PhRvD.101b3516K</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.491.2217R</TD>
<TD>A systematic study of spiral density waves in the accretion discs of cataclysmic variables</TD>
<TD>Ruiz-Carmona, R.; Groot, P. J.; Steeghs, D.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 491, Issue 2, pp.2217-2253</TD>
<TD>2020-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.491.2217R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.491.1771W</TD>
<TD>Polarimetry of relativistic tidal disruption event Swift J2058+0516</TD>
<TD>Wiersema, K.; Higgins, A. B.; Levan, A. J.; Eyles, R. A. J.; Starling, R. L. C.; Tanvir, N. R.; Cenko, S. B.; van der Horst, A. J.; Gompertz, B. P.; Greiner, J.; Pasham, D. R.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 491, Issue 2, p.1771-1776</TD>
<TD>2020-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.491.1771W</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.491.1506D</TD>
<TD>Detecting gravitational self-lensing from stellar-mass binaries composed of black holes or neutron stars</TD>
<TD>D'Orazio, Daniel J.; Di Stefano, Rosanne</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 491, Issue 1, p.1506-1517</TD>
<TD>2020-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.491.1506D</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020MNRAS.491..596C</TD>
<TD>Prospects of cosmic superstring detection through microlensing of extragalactic point-like sources</TD>
<TD>Chernoff, David F.; Goobar, Ariel; Renk, Janina J.</TD>
<TD>Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society, Volume 491, Issue 1, p.596-614</TD>
<TD>2020-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020MNRAS.491..596C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020JATIS...6a8002R</TD>
<TD>Robotilter: an automated lens/CCD alignment system for the Evryscope</TD>
<TD>Ratzloff, Jeffrey K.; Law, Nicholas M.; Corbett, Henry T.; Fors, Octavi; del Ser, Daniel</TD>
<TD>Journal of Astronomical Telescopes, Instruments, and Systems, Volume 6, id. 018002 (2020).</TD>
<TD>2020-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020JATIS...6a8002R</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...889L...6C</TD>
<TD>The Most Rapidly Declining Type I Supernova 2019bkc/ATLAS19dqr</TD>
<TD>Chen, Ping; Dong, Subo; Stritzinger, M. D.; Holmbo, Simon; Strader, Jay; Kochanek, C. S.; Peng, Eric W.; Benetti, S.; Bersier, D.; Brownsberger, Sasha; Buckley, David A. H.; Gromadzki, Mariusz; Moran, Shane; Pastorello, A.; Aydi, Elias; Bose, Subhash; Connor, Thomas; Boutsia, K.; Di Mille, F.; Elias-Rosa, N.; French, K. Decker; Holoien, Thomas W. -S.; Mattila, Seppo; Shappee, B. J.; Stark, Antony A.; Swihart, Samuel J.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 889, Issue 1, id.L6, 17 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...889L...6C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...889...49B</TD>
<TD>The ELM Survey. VIII. Ninety-eight Double White Dwarf Binaries</TD>
<TD>Brown, Warren R.; Kilic, Mukremin; Kosakowski, Alekzander; Andrews, Jeff J.; Heinke, Craig O.; Agüeros, Marcel A.; Camilo, Fernando; Gianninas, A.; Hermes, J. J.; Kenyon, Scott J.</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 889, Issue 1, id.49, 17 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...889...49B</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...889...36C</TD>
<TD>An Optimized Radio Follow-up Strategy for Stripped-envelope Core-collapse Supernovae</TD>
<TD>Carbone, Dario; Corsi, Alessandra</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal, Volume 889, Issue 1, id.36, 8 pp. (2020)</TD>
<TD>2020-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...889...36C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020ApJ...888L..14C</TD>
<TD>On Post-starburst Galaxies Dominating Tidal Disruption Events</TD>
<TD>Cen, Renyue</TD>
<TD>The Astrophysical Journal Letters, Volume 888, Issue 1, article id. L14, 11 pp. (2020).</TD>
<TD>2020-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020ApJ...888L..14C</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020AJ....159...16A</TD>
<TD>An Information Theory Approach on Deciding Spectroscopic Follow-ups</TD>
<TD>Astudillo, Javiera; Protopapas, Pavlos; Pichara, Karim; Huijse, Pablo</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 159, Issue 1, article id. 16, 14 pp. (2020).</TD>
<TD>2020-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020AJ....159...16A</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020AJ....159....8V</TD>
<TD>The Vanishing and Appearing Sources during a Century of Observations Project. I. USNO Objects Missing in Modern Sky Surveys and Follow-up Observations of a “Missing Star”</TD>
<TD>Villarroel, Beatriz; Soodla, Johan; Comerón, Sébastien; Mattsson, Lars; Pelckmans, Kristiaan; López-Corredoira, Martín; Krisciunas, Kevin; Guerras, Eduardo; Kochukhov, Oleg; Bergstedt, Josefine; Buelens, Bart; Bär, Rudolf E.; Cubo, Rubén; Enriquez, J. Emilio; Gupta, Alok C.; Imaz, Iñigo; Karlsson, Torgny; Prieto, M. Almudena; Shlyapnikov, Aleksey A.; de Souza, Rafael S.; Vavilova, Irina B.; Ward, Martin J.</TD>
<TD>The Astronomical Journal, Volume 159, Issue 1, article id. 8, 19 pp. (2020).</TD>
<TD>2020-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020AJ....159....8V</TD>
</TR>

<TR>
<TD>2020A&amp;A...633A..98W</TD>
<TD>Full orbital solution for the binary system in the northern Galactic disc microlensing event Gaia16aye</TD>
<TD>Wyrzykowski, Ł.; Mróz, P.; Rybicki, K. A.; Gromadzki, M.; Kołaczkowski, Z.; Zieliński, M.; Zieliński, P.; Britavskiy, N.; Gomboc, A.; Sokolovsky, K.; Hodgkin, S. T.; Abe, L.; Aldi, G. F.; AlMannaei, A.; Altavilla, G.; Al Qasim, A.; Anupama, G. C.; Awiphan, S.; Bachelet, E.; Bakış, V.; Baker, S.; Bartlett, S.; Bendjoya, P.; Benson, K.; Bikmaev, I. F.; Birenbaum, G.; Blagorodnova, N.; Blanco-Cuaresma, S.; Boeva, S.; Bonanos, A. Z.; Bozza, V.; Bramich, D. M.; Bruni, I.; Burenin, R. A.; Burgaz, U.; Butterley, T.; Caines, H. E.; Caton, D. B.; Calchi Novati, S.; Carrasco, J. M.; Cassan, A.; Čepas, V.; Cropper, M.; Chruślińska, M.; Clementini, G.; Clerici, A.; Conti, D.; Conti, M.; Cross, S.; Cusano, F.; Damljanovic, G.; Dapergolas, A.; D'Ago, G.; de Bruijne, J. H. J.; Dennefeld, M.; Dhillon, V. S.; Dominik, M.; Dziedzic, J.; Erece, O.; Eselevich, M. V.; Esenoglu, H.; Eyer, L.; Figuera Jaimes, R.; Fossey, S. J.; Galeev, A. I.; Grebenev, S. A.; Gupta, A. C.; Gutaev, A. G.; Hallakoun, N.; Hamanowicz, A.; Han, C.; Handzlik, B.; Haislip, J. B.; Hanlon, L.; Hardy, L. K.; Harrison, D. L.; van Heerden, H. J.; Hoette, V. L.; Horne, K.; Hudec, R.; Hundertmark, M.; Ihanec, N.; Irtuganov, E. N.; Itoh, R.; Iwanek, P.; Jovanovic, M. D.; Janulis, R.; Jelínek, M.; Jensen, E.; Kaczmarek, Z.; Katz, D.; Khamitov, I. M.; Kilic, Y.; Klencki, J.; Kolb, U.; Kopacki, G.; Kouprianov, V. V.; Kruszyńska, K.; Kurowski, S.; Latev, G.; Lee, C. -H.; Leonini, S.; Leto, G.; Lewis, F.; Li, Z.; Liakos, A.; Littlefair, S. P.; Lu, J.; Manser, C. J.; Mao, S.; Maoz, D.; Martin-Carrillo, A.; Marais, J. P.; Maskoliūnas, M.; Maund, J. R.; Meintjes, P. J.; Melnikov, S. S.; Ment, K.; Mikołajczyk, P.; Morrell, M.; Mowlavi, N.; Moździerski, D.; Murphy, D.; Nazarov, S.; Netzel, H.; Nesci, R.; Ngeow, C. -C.; Norton, A. J.; Ofek, E. O.; Pakštienė, E.; Palaversa, L.; Pandey, A.; Paraskeva, E.; Pawlak, M.; Penny, M. T.; Penprase, B. E.; Piascik, A.; Prieto, J. L.; Qvam, J. K. T.; Ranc, C.; Rebassa-Mansergas, A.; Reichart, D. E.; Reig, P.; Rhodes, L.; Rivet, J. -P.; Rixon, G.; Roberts, D.; Rosi, P.; Russell, D. M.; Zanmar Sanchez, R.; Scarpetta, G.; Seabroke, G.; Shappee, B. J.; Schmidt, R.; Shvartzvald, Y.; Sitek, M.; Skowron, J.; Śniegowska, M.; Snodgrass, C.; Soares, P. S.; van Soelen, B.; Spetsieri, Z. T.; Stankevičiūtė, A.; Steele, I. A.; Street, R. A.; Strobl, J.; Strubble, E.; Szegedi, H.; Tinjaca Ramirez, L. M.; Tomasella, L.; Tsapras, Y.; Vernet, D.; Villanueva, S.; Vince, O.; Wambsganss, J.; van der Westhuizen, I. P.; Wiersema, K.; Wium, D.; Wilson, R. W.; Yoldas, A.; Zhuchkov, R. Ya.; Zhukov, D. G.; Zdanavičius, J.; Zoła, S.; Zubareva, A.</TD>
<TD>Astronomy &amp;amp; Astrophysics, Volume 633, id.A98, 21 pp.</TD>
<TD>2020-01-1</TD>
<TD>https://ui.adsabs.harvard.edu/abs/2020A&amp;A...633A..98W</TD>
</TR>

</TABLEDATA>
</DATA>
</TABLE>
</RESOURCE>
</VOTABLE>